<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Kauri&apos;s BS</title>
    <description>placeholder text :)</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 15:00:12 +0200</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 15:00:12 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v4.3.2</generator>
    
      
        <item>
          
            <title>Die Kleinen Dinge&lt;br&gt;Ein Schreiben an Lucia&apos;s Vermieter</title>
          
          <author>fakeemail@gmail.com (Kauri's BS)</author>
          <description>
            &lt;h5 id=&quot;donnerstag-15-juni&quot;&gt;Donnerstag 15 Juni&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sehr geehrter Georg,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Ich habe über unseres Gespräch am Mittwoch nachgedacht. Das Gruppentreffen war notwendig - Lucia und ich habe die Köchen in ein inakzeptabel Status verlassen; nicht leer bins, ein paar schmutzig Tellern bei den Spüle verlessen. Es war den Weckruf wir gebraucht haben nachdem eine außergewöhnlich fleißig Nacht.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Sie sind Recht; wir solten die Küche die ganze Zeit fleckenfrei verlassen, aber insbesondere wann sie werde aus dem Urlaub zurückkehrer. Obgleich, Ich hoffe sie haben zum Häus mit fraiche lebensmittel zurückkehrer schätzen. Weil wann Sie letzte Mittwoch für Urlaub verlessen, Lucia habt Zuhause Rückkhern zu finden ranzig Milch, verrottend Paprikas in den Kühlschrank, und die Apfel, mehr ahnlich Kompost. Ahnlich die Restlichen, Sie werde wahrscheinlich nie wissen. Es ist nur eine der kleinen Dinge.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Sie sind Recht; als ein Gast für eine Woche, ich solte über der kleinen Dinge um das Haus mehr aufpassen, um die Tastache zu kompensieren, dass ich trinke deine Kaffee und miete nicht kaufen. Nachte Zeit ich werde sicherstellen zu sagen ihnen wenn ich die Toilette putzen, wenn ich gefallene Wäsche weider aufhänge, oder wenn ich wasche die schmutzig Tellern das Sie auf der Arbeitsplatte verlassen. Ich werde ihnen die Quittung für die Milch und Hafern und fraische Gemüse ich gekauft habe zeigen. Ich werde weiterhin zu anbeiten ihnen Abendessen, auch wenn die letzte zwei Zeit sie habe nicht ein Bisschen gegessen. Ich möchte nicht ein Schmarotzer weidergelten!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Sie sind Recht, in eine Garage mit acht Fahrrades und eine rostig Tischtennisplatte, Lucia&lt;strong&gt;’s&lt;/strong&gt; Fahrrad ist sehr unbequem; es viel zu viel Platz einnehmen. Beraten Sie ihr, wegbringen Sie es! Oh, und stören Sie nicht zu anbeiten irgendwelche auffällig Ausweg &lt;strong&gt;either&lt;/strong&gt;. Und wenn sie beherzigt es, und dezidiert das gleich Tag zu finden ein Ausweg… “Oh, was mascht du? Ich habe nicht es gemeint zu jetzt es machen!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Es ist nur ein kleinen Dinge, die weg Sie sprechen zu Leute. Intolerant, gefühllos, gefühllos; dennoch irgendwie so emotional. Es must nett sein zu Mitbewohner-Vermeiter sein. Du bist gleich, Sie sind überlegen. Was auch immer bequemer? Ich empfehlen Sie aus das Has von Deine Mutter und Fater nicht ausrücken - vile wenn Sie alles die Macht nicht halten, Sie sind am Arsch.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Ich aufgehe ich genau nicht gesagt habe, danke für die Gastfreundschaft. Nachte Zeit ich werde die Mülleimer für ihnen auch leeren.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Grüße,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Kauri&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
P.s: Enschuldigung ich habe nicht ihnen gezagt über meinen kommend Reiseplans bis Sie gefragt.&lt;/p&gt;

          </description>
          <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
          <link>http://localhost:4000/Ein-Schreiben-an-Lucia's-Vermieter.html</link>
          <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/Ein-Schreiben-an-Lucia's-Vermieter.html</guid>
          
          
        </item>
      
    
      
        <item>
          
            <title>The Little Things&lt;br&gt;A Letter to Lucia&apos;s Landlord</title>
          
          <author>fakeemail@gmail.com (Kauri's BS)</author>
          <description>
            &lt;h5 id=&quot;thursday-15th-june&quot;&gt;Thursday 15th June&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dear Georg,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
I’ve been reflecting on our conversation on Wednesday. The group meeting was really needed – Lucia and I did leave the kitchen in an unacceptable state; unemptied bins, a few dishes forgotten by the sink. It was exactly the wake-up call we needed after an exceptionally busy night.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
You are right; we should leave the kitchen spotless at all times, but especially when you are coming back from holiday. Though, I do hope you appreciated coming back to a house stocked with fresh food. Because when you left for holiday last Wednesday, Lucia arrived home to find rancid milk, peppers rotting in the fridge, and the apples, more like compost. Like the rest, you’ll probably never know. It’s just one of those little things.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
You are right; as a guest for one week, I should take more care of the little things around the house, to make up for the fact that I drink your coffee and don’t pay rent. Next time I’ll make sure to tell you  when I clean the toilet, when I rehang laundry fallen to the floor, or when I wash the dirty dishes you’ve left on the counter. I’m going to show you the receipt for the milk and oats and fresh vegetables I buy. I’ll keep offering you dinner, even though the last two times you didn’t eat any of it. I sure wouldn’t want to be called a freeloader again!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
You are right; in a garage with eight bikes, two cars and a rusty ping-pong table, Lucia’s second bike is incredibly inconvenient; it’s taking up far too much space. Berate her, take it away! Oh, and don’t bother offering any obvious solutions either. And when she takes it to heart and decides to find a solution the same day… “Oh, what are you doing? I didn’t mean for you to do it right now!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
It’s just a little thing, the way you talk to people. Intolerant, unempathetic, callous; yet somehow so emotional. It must be nice being flatmate-landlord. You’re an equal, you’re superior. Whatever’s more convenient? I suggest you don’t move out of mum and dad’s old home – because when you don’t hold all the power, you’re fucked.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
I realize I haven’t properly said, thanks for the hospitality. Next time I’ll empty the bins for you too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Cheers,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Kauri&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
P.s: Sorry for not telling you my upcoming travel plans until you asked.&lt;/p&gt;

          </description>
          <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
          <link>http://localhost:4000/A-Letter-to-Lucia's-Landlord-copy.html</link>
          <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/A-Letter-to-Lucia's-Landlord-copy.html</guid>
          
          
        </item>
      
    
      
        <item>
          
            <title>Hitchhiking 600km for a dentist appointment</title>
          
          <author>fakeemail@gmail.com (Kauri's BS)</author>
          <description>
            &lt;p&gt;Actually, this one is an English translation. You can read the &lt;a href=&quot;/test&quot;&gt;German Original here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;wednesday-7th-june&quot;&gt;Wednesday 7th June&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Three weeks ago I sent an email to a dental practice in Munich. To this dental practice, to eight others too. These practices replied immediately. Rather generic and impersonal response, to a rather specific email. Suspect, for a Friday afternoon….&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I put it on the back burner, and waited two weeks. The responses were overwhelming - with a grand tota of… zero responses. So, in the middle of some Polish bush, using the last of all my batteries, I started calling each dental office. No answer, no English, the dentist is on vacation. I book an appointment, 21st June, for a short initial consultation… 21 June!? How long might I have to wait for the actual procedures?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I thought back about Alldent. Immediate answer. I could have a booking just two days in advance. I’ll come to Munich to see Lucia. Oh, I find out, Lucia will not be there. Fuck it! How many people can say they hitchhiked 600km for a dentist appointment?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was not a simple 600km. Challenges with hitchhiking, a hammock torn in two, an epic battle with the mosquitoes - but these are stories for another time. On to Munich! To make good time, in the morning I took the regional train to the city. Remember, I gave them all the information - a report from my dentist in New Zealand, including Xrays, technical details for the implant buried under my gums, and an explanation of the remaining procedure - Restoration and Crowning. It’s an international standard system.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I arrive early, fill out the paperwork, and sit in the lobby for 30 minutes. They finally call me to the dentist. We talk and, within 30 seconds he tells me, “We can’t crown a third-party implant. It’s a liability issue, a risk we’re not allowed to take.” 30 seconds, 30 euro. Fuck off, why didn’t these wankers just tell me that on the phone!?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, long story short, I am now in a youth hostel waiting for Lucie. I have to stay in Munich tomorrow for another appointment with another doctor. We talked a lot on the phone, and at least they implied that they could complete the procedures. Wish me luck!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;friday-9th-june&quot;&gt;Friday 9th June&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Future update: It was good! There is a few details to sort out, but I think I will continue with them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;sunday-25th-september&quot;&gt;Sunday 25th September&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The last dentists in Germany wanted three-bloody-thousand euro! After scrutinizing their quotes, I decided to wait. Just ten-thousand kilometres later…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here in Tirana, Albania I was given a fixed quote at 1/3 of the price. Fast, good communication, excellent quality of work. Within a week of arriving I had my brand new tooth. I’m currently volunteering in a beautiful hostel here in Tirana, with a big new smile - but that’s a story for another time!&lt;/p&gt;

          </description>
          <pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
          <link>http://localhost:4000/Hitchhiking-600km-for-a-dentist-appointment.html</link>
          <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/Hitchhiking-600km-for-a-dentist-appointment.html</guid>
          
          
        </item>
      
    
      
        <item>
          
            <title>Fahren 600km per Anhalter für einen Zahnarzttermin</title>
          
          <author>fakeemail@gmail.com (Kauri's BS)</author>
          <description>
            &lt;h5 id=&quot;vorwort&quot;&gt;Vorwort&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wirklich, diese Geschicte ist ein Deutsches Original. Falls sie konnen auch ein Rechtschreibfehler oder Grammaticalischproblem finden, ich werde Sie eine Medaille geben.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;mittwoch-7-juni&quot;&gt;Mittwoch 7 Juni&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Drei wochen hinter ich habe ein Email zu einer Zahnarztpraxen in München gesendet. Zu dieser Zahnarztpraxen, zu acht andere auch. Dieser Praxen haben sofort geantwortet. Eher generisch und unpersönalich Antwort, zu ein sehr spezifisch Email. Suspekt, für ein Fritag nachmittag…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ich haben das auf Sparflamme stellen, und zwei Wochen gewartet, zu sehen viele Antworten, eine große Summe von… null. So, in den Mitte von manche Polnischer Busch, mit den letzten von meiner Batterei, ich fing an alles die Zahnarztpraxen anrufen. Kein Antwort, kein Englisch, der Zahnarzt ist im Urlaub. Ich hole ein Termin… 21 Juni… für erst eine kurze Initiale Beratung… 21 Juni!? Wie lang denn muss ich warten für die richtige Abläufe?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ich habe züruck über Alldent gedacht. Sofort Antwort. Ich könnte eine Buchung nur zwei Tagen im vorous haben. Leck mich am Arsch, ich werde nach München kommen zu sehen Lucia. Oh, aber, Lucia werde nicht da sein. Scheiß drauf! Wie viele Leute konnen sagen Sie 600km per Anhalter gefahren für einen Zahnarzttermin haben?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Es war nicht ein einfach 600km. Aufgaben mit Anhalter fahren, eine Hangingmatte in zwei gerissen, ein epischer Kampf mit die Mücken. Aber diese sind Geschichten für ein anderes Zeit. Nach München! Zu machen am Morgen gut Zeit ich habe das Regionalbahn nach die Stadt genommen. Bedenken Sie, ich habe alles Information ihnen gegeben – einen Bericht aus mein Zahnarzt in Neuseeland, mit Xrays, mit technische Erläuterung von die Implant unter meinem Zahnfleisch begraben, mit Erläuterung von die restlicken Verfahren – Restoration and Crowning. Ein internationals Standardsystem.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ich früh komme an, fulle den Papierkram, warte für 30 Minuten. Sie fragen mir endlich, der Zahnarzt kommt. Wir reden und, immerhalb 30 Sekunden er erzählet mir, “Wir konnen ein Drittzahnimplantat nicht Kronen. Es ist einen liability Haftungaspekte, ein Risiko wir nicht nehmen konnen.”  Leck mich am Arsch! Warum haben diese Wischern mich nicht bei das Telefon sagen?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, lang Geschichte kurz, ich bin jetzt in ein Jugendherberge, warte for Lucie, und muss morgen in München beliben für einen anderen Termin mit einen anderen Doktor. Ich habe viel angerufet, und Sie haben mindestens impliziert das Sie die Verfahren machen konnen. Wunschen mir Glück!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;freitag-9-juni&quot;&gt;Freitag 9 Juni&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, lang Geschichte kurz, ich bin jetzt in ein Jugendherberge, warte for Lucie, und muss morgen in München beliben für einen anderen Termin mit einen anderen Doktor. Ich habe viel angerufet, und Sie haben mindestens impliziert das Sie die Verfahren machen konnen. Wunschen mir Glück!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;sonntag-25th-september&quot;&gt;Sonntag 25th September&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Die letzte Zahnarzt in München mochten drei thousand euro, und nachdem ich habe ihre Angebot unter die Lupe genommen, ich beschloss zu warten, zu warten nur zehntausend Kilometer mehr.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hier in Tirana, Albanien, ich habe einen fixed Festpreisangebot erhalte, nur einen Drittel von den Preis. Schnell, gute Kommunikation, exzellente Qualität der Arbeit. Innerhalb einer Woche, ich hette mein brand neu Zahn. Jetzt ich Freiwillinger in einen schön Jugendherberge in Tirana zu arbeiten, mit ein groß neu Lächeln - aber das ist ein Geschichte für ein ander Zeit!&lt;/p&gt;

          </description>
          <pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
          <link>http://localhost:4000/Fahren-600km-mit-Anhalter-f%C3%BCr-einen-Zahnarzttermin.html</link>
          <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/Fahren-600km-mit-Anhalter-f%C3%BCr-einen-Zahnarzttermin.html</guid>
          
          
        </item>
      
    
      
        <item>
          
            <title>Asymmetrical Warfare</title>
          
          <author>fakeemail@gmail.com (Kauri's BS)</author>
          <description>
            &lt;h3 id=&quot;part-i&quot;&gt;Part I&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I didn’t even bother with my bugnet. The initial wave may have just been the scouts, but my defences were ready. For thirty minutes, the aerial ninjas intimidated and mercilessly drew blood, however their ranks sustained heavy casualties. Those stealthy enough to remain undetected flew home on a full belly, but after hearing of the decimation of their peers, the full ranks decided not to advance. Only the occasional hungry nomadic wanderer stumbled through, with whom I shared an intimate connection, freely offering sustenance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;part-ii&quot;&gt;Part II&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;\assets\images\warfare_jogenheim.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;warfare_jogenheim&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;12am at Jogenheim National Park, Norway.&lt;/figcaption&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Two unwitting fools sought out the perfect campsite stumble around the foothills of the mountain they’d climb tomorrow. He left to gather some wood, and returned to find her bewildered, surrounded by a cloud of nightmares. This was their territory. Wherever the fools went, nightmares followed. There was no escape.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Tonight the warriors would not sleep under the stars, nor would they forfeit. They camouflaged their skin with a heavy-duty gel brought from New Zealand, brought just for this day. They set up their fortress, the primary defensive structure, where they would take shelter during the night. But the weary warriors needed nourishment, and their fortress sat idly by.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
They got to cooking, but the smell of another juicy meal only lured more attackers. Their numbers were overwhelming. In one casual leg-slap, five passed, five more joined. They darted into the most unwelcome of places. One had to take care breathing, lest they may find themselves breathing more than air. The pasta, one could no longer call it vegetarian.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Entering the fortress was no easy task. To prepare, they packed their bags completely and waited a while, twenty metres away. The lure worked. They made a mad dash, with her diving headfirst, followed by flying bags, a second pair of lanky legs, a zipper furiously closed, a copious, contagious laughter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Peace.&lt;/p&gt;

          </description>
          <pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
          <link>http://localhost:4000/Asymmetrical-warfare.html</link>
          <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/Asymmetrical-warfare.html</guid>
          
          
        </item>
      
    
      
        <item>
          
            <title>Draft&amp;#58; Arrested by the Albanian Mafia</title>
          
          <author>fakeemail@gmail.com (Kauri's BS)</author>
          <description>
            &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Foreword&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I want to say a massive thankyou to my girlfriend Lucia. Without her I would have been alone and terrified, and this story would probably have gone quite differently. You’d think there’s not much she can do from San Francisco.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;part-i-lies-and-intimidation&quot;&gt;Part I: Lies and Intimidation&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;monday-18th-september&quot;&gt;Monday 18th September&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A productive start to a new week! It’s 4am, and I’m writing from jail in Tirana, Albania. Well, I’m smoking with the warden in his office. That privilege cost me nine euro. Potable water included.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Live music roars from the stage, thirty metres south. The crowd sings and hollers, beer stalls busy. I’m at an open-air concert in the heart of the city, lounging as comfortably as one can on a plastic couch; journaling, taking photos, enjoying the vibrant atmosphere. I’m enjoying this different perspective on the city. I find myself marvelling at the seamless organization, the fantastic music, the joy one night can bring. I contemplate the skyscrapers under construction; an optimism for this challenged city.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Policia.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I turn around back to face him. “Excuse me?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A muscular plain-clothed man looks back at me. He holds his badge forth. “I am the Policia. How is your night?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s hard to hear over the music, and we are raising our voices. “Fine. Isn’t it a lovely night. Is there a problem?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He raises one leg onto the plastic bench and leans in towards me. Behind him, the darkness of the lowly-lit stairs leading to the Opera House. Glancing around, I notice another man approaching from behind, barriering a carefree world behind us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“What’s in your bag?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Sorry, have I done something wrong?” I argue. “Do I have to consent? What are my rights? What the fuck is this?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think back to a recent acquaintance I made. I rode five hours with a Dutch man, a diplomat in Belgrade, for the Delegation of the European Union to Serbia. He is on diplomatic mission is to help the West Balkans one day join the EU, by improving the rule of law in the West Balkans. It’s no secret Albania faces challenges with corruption, a deep-rooted systemic issue affecting politics, the judiciary, public services, healthcare, education, business. In terms of law enforcement; bribery, extortion, abuse of power. In my mind, this hulking policeman is the embodiment. His intimidation works.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I begrudgingly remove items from my backpack, explaining each item. I do not want them to touch my shit. What’s in my bag? Well, fuck. With me I have everything of value. All day I’ve been writing emails, applying for jobs, chatting with friends and family. The city seems a right place for it. I have my phone, my cables, my passport. Brand new earbuds. My wallet, about 30,000 LEK (300€) in cash. A tote bag, inspected. An empty water bottle, sniffed. Half a can of Pringles, poured to the floor. I had my laptop too – but I didn’t take that out. On reflection, the most valuable item in there was my journal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A small snus container, the culprit. A snus pouch is a small, teabag-like sachet that contains tobacco product, a white powder. Swedish stuff. 100% legal. A snus container has two compartments: the bottom compartment holds the snus itself, and the top compartment is for discarding used pouches. This is what it looks like.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[image]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He picks it out of my backpack’s front pocket. Despite all those muscles, he simply couldn’t get it open. Pulling and twisting, not a budge. Begrudgingly I take it from his hands and pop the top flap open, pointing to the three used snus pouches. “This is snus,” I explain. “Nicotine. What else do you want?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Muscleman inspects it closely. “This is cocaine?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“NICOTINE. LEGAL.” I scowl.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Where did you buy this from?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I look at him blankly, confused by the line of questioning. “Is this man stupid?” I wonder. The second officer takes my passport off me. Soon three more officers join the scene, also working in the field. They pass around the snus container. “Cocaine” “cocaine” “cocaine”, I understand. What are we, parrots? They pick at a pouch, and the nicotine powder spills out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With a deep sigh, I clarify. “This is a nicotine pouch. It is a no-smoke tobacco product. You can buy this here in Albania at any tobacco store. You place it under your lip, and it releases nicotine. It smells like mint because it has a mint flavouring. You can see it here on the packaging.”
I reach for my phone and show them pictures of the product. A quick Google translate later, I present a web page in Albanian, explaining the product its legal status.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“We have to take it to the lab to test it for cocaine.” says Muscleman.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As if he’d just remembered something, the offending officer closes the snus container and starts to pry open the bottom compartment again. Pop. There’s the marijuana, a few flakes, half a gram. Jackpot.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now I don’t talk any more. They yell at me a bunch of questions about the weed, about the cocaine. They ask about I’m shitting myself. My internal monologue is blowing up. “How the fuck did you get yourself in this situation? Were you doing something wrong? Why did you let them search you? You didn’t – he just took it from your bag! Is that legal? Is any of this legal? Fuck, I don’t even know if snus is legal here! Why did you bring the weed? You don’t even smoke!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A police car is coming to take me to the station. This is going to be a problem.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“What, am I supposed to bribe these guys? How much do I bribe them? Twenty euro? Offensive. Fifty euro? Two-hundred? Fuck, that’s a lot of money. Shit, I might have told them I’m in Tirana to see the dentist. I’m dressed way too nicely. They think you have money. This is going to turn into an extortion case, isn’t it? At least it’s not the mafia, right? Why did you decide to wear your only shirt today? Why did you come here with all your valuables? You’ve been working on your laptop all day, right. And you were just on the phone with your girlfriend Lucia. Lucia? Lucia!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lucia and my sister Jade both receive a flurry of cryptic messages at 11.45pm. Lucie jumps on the phone. They let me talk for twenty-six seconds, before kicking me off. I fight for my right to “talk to my lawyer” and call her back. We get a few minutes where I can explain the situation, in all uncertain terms. I have no idea what’s going to happen when they take me to the station. Maybe they’re going to take my organs. “We will just fill the paperwork, twenty minutes and then you can go.” I know this is bullshit. How can I feel comfortable putting my life in the hands of people who are actively lying, knowingly misaccusing me in a country where the Police are nicknamed “the mafia”? They kick me off the phone, and Lucie calls right back. We steal another minute.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Two new officers arrive and cuff me. I’m still wearing my handcuff. They drive a few minutes to the station in relative silence. They uncuff me and sit me at a desk the middle of a bland, off-white concrete painted hallway with a handful of doors; in front of me, a door with a bar grill window. To my right, a new officer sits down in front of a stack of paperwork. I’ll call him Mr Illiterate, given how slowly he writes. The man who cuffed me, he can be Officer 13565, as displayed boldly on his uniform. 13565 wouldn’t tell me his name. He stands in front of me. His partner moseys around, and mingles with the new cops that have come out to greet us. Muscleman joins the party shortly later.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is a camera in one corner of the hallway, the type with a swivel head. I ask why it never moves. Mr Illiterate assures me it’s on. Bullshit, where’s the red light? It’s not on, is it? I put my water bottle on the table and ask for some water. “It’s not possible to drink the water here,” they tell me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I call Lucie for the last time. 12.02am, lasting six minutes. This time we were properly able to discuss what is going on. Lucie remembers this better than I. She describes the atmosphere as tense and chaotic. [@Lucie, any more detail you want to add here?] She talks to one of the officers, who maintains his aggressive demeanour. “This is Police station number 3!” “We are going to send it to the lab to test it for cocaine!” “He has marijuana, he is going to go to jail!” I have advised Lucie to get in contact with Jade and Dom, and together they will figure out what to do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mr Illiterate slowly fills out the police report. He takes a break and offers me a cigarette. He asks me the odd question. I refuse to tell him my father’s name. By now, I’m thinking, we all know the snus is legal. I realize they only care about the marijuana, and are using “cocaine” as a scare tactic. My phone is going nuts on the table, notifications on, ringing. A friend calls. Another friend calls. Lucie calls repeatedly. They won’t let me answer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They ask to search my bag again. I start pulling items out on the desk, dictating for them. “This is my shorts. This is my headband. This is a box for the headphones I bought today. Here’s the receipt, too. You want to see? And here’s my shopping bag.” I pull out everything down to the bottlecap, the shell, the tissue paper. I pull out more and more tissue paper. “Because, you never know when there’s going to be toilet paper here in Tirana. I bet you don’t have any here. Wonder how you lot wipe? Smells like shit in here.” They don’t have any toilet paper. Their toilet is a plastic hole in the ground. Muscleman suspiciously picks at a large clump of tissue paper. I seize the opportunity to spread tissue all across the table for his colleagues to see, there is no drugs in the toilet paper.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After half an hour, someone hands me a 300mL bottle of water from the mart next door. It’s too hot in here. I down it in one go. “How much costs another one?” But the mini-mart is now closed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;13565 me tries more questions. “Where did you get it from?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I play with it. “What do you mean? I told you already, this is legal nicotine. You can buy this in the tobacco store.” I turn to Muscleman. “You must be the only policeman in the world stupid enough to think this is cocaine. By the way, what do you mean you’re sending that off to the lab? You don’t have a lab here. You don’t even have running water in this building!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Yes, we are sending it to the lab to be tested!” Muscleman assures me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;13565 tries again. “Where did you buy the marijuana?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I don’t know what you’re talking about.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Why won’t you tell, what is your father’s name?” he asks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I know it doesn’t matter, it’s just for your report. But I don’t feel like telling you until you give me back my phone.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I start to pack my things away again. I have expressed that I am uncomfortable with them touching my stuff, because I think they are going to steal from me. Any excuse to kick a fuss. I leave the tissues strewn across the table. I leave my wallet wide open, this time with quite a bit more money in it. I leave my old headphones too, next to the brand-new box and receipt. I ask to use the toilet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At some point, they tell me I must go into the jail cell. I kick a fuss. I’m not moving; I want to stay here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Eventually they take me to another building, the headquarters “…to see your lawyer and police officer. It will take one hour.” Bullshit. They introduce me to the jail warden. He doesn’t speak English. They close the bars on us, and continue to chat, and hand over a copy of the police report. I remind them again, not for the first time – I need to use a phone, I need to call my lawyer, I need to call my embassy, I need to call my girlfriend; she is worried about the mafia. They keep my phone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;13565’s partner beckons, and I stick my hands through the bars. The others give him shit as he struggles, a minute to undo my shackles. The jail warden props me against the wall, pats me down, then searches my bag. He rummages a little, and produces my laptop. A laptop!? I was this close to smuggling it in! He yells at the embarrassed officers behind the bars. I wink at the man who brought me in. They keep my laptop.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;part-iii-jail&quot;&gt;Part III: Jail&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The warden takes my backpack to his office, and shows me to my cell. Same as the last station – this time I’m guided through the door with a bar grill window. [This time I’m behind the door. Describe it a little more. There’s no potable water in this station either.] Inside sit a couple other fellas, young local men. They smile. “So what’d they get you for?” We exchange stories. “Yeah, these guys are the mafia. They just do what they want”. Viktor was picked up outside his apartment building, carrying a little bit of weed. The other, Florian – I forget his story – but he was the same, a little bit of weed. He’s a lawyer. “They’re not going to take your stuff, they are too scared. You won’t have any problems; they can’t do anything about a little bit of weed. They will let you go,” he advises.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The warden pops his head in, and talks to us, Florian the translator. He can’t read my name on the papers! I start to spell, but the warden gives up and calls us into his office. The desk has two large ledgers on it. A sink lies in one corner of the room. I sit facing Florian, in front of the ledger, the warden to the side. Florian picks up a pen. “K-A-R-U-I”, I spell. “B-O-C-K-M-A-N.” The warden offers us a cigarette. Date of birth, slightly wrong. Father’s name, slightly wronger. Under instruction from the warden, Florian fills the rest of the ledger. We ash into a plastic cup with a little bit of water.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Florian explains to the warden, I need to call my embassy, I need to call my lawyer, I need to call my girlfriend; she is worried that I am kidnapped by the mafia; I have not told her everything will be fine. No phone here. I point at a half-empty water bottle on the table, and the warden nods. I down it in one go, and move toward the sink. The warden speaks up – you can’t drink the water here either. I ask for my notebook, and he agrees.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’re ushered back to the cell, a place with nothing but time and good company. I take notes. Prior to the collapse of the communist regime in the 1990’s the police were unwaveringly loyal to the regime. They were instrumental in enforcing the regime and maintaining control, with no transparency, accountability, or oversight. They were tasked with repressing political dissent and opposition,[problem, not tasked with this] harassing and imprisoning at will. They perpetuated a culture of fear and repression. Bribery, off-the-books payments, nepotism, and embezzlement were commonplace, tools for expediting bureaucratic processes, to gain access to services, to avoid legal consequences. Corruption was seen as an expected, even necessary way to navigate the bureaucratic systems.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Following the social and political collapse of the communist regime in the 1990’s, the country experienced a period of significant social and political upheaval, creating an environment conducive to the growth of organized crime. Notable activities included drug cultivation and trafficking, particularly cannabis, as well as human trafficking, smuggling, and theft. Corruption, collusion and infiltration between members of law enforcement and organized crime groups facilitated criminal activities, protecting criminal networks, and further eroding public trust in the police.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The warden peers his head in, and Viktor is taken away to be processed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With international support, the Albanian government, recognizing the severity of the problem, initiated efforts to combat corruption within law enforcement agencies. This included measures to strengthen internal oversight, improve training and professionalism, and implement anti-corruption reforms. Today, Albania is undergoing major judicial reform aimed at overhauling the judicial system, addressing issues such as corruption, political interference, and inefficiency. In the police force, Albania is now vetting and screening police officers, providing anti-corruption training and implementing transparency and accountability mechanisms. They have made significant progress, and the mafia no longer run rampant on the streets. However, these challenges have been deeply rooted, and clearly these problems still exist.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We become quiet, as commotion stirs outside. The warden peers his head in, and holds two fingers to pursed lips. We join him in his office for a cigarette. Florian tells me a large group of illegal immigrants have arrived; they now occupy the holding cell. We finish out discussion about corruption, with the warden explaining that he does not take bribes. The warden offers for us to stay, so as not to share a room together with the immigrants.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Around 3am, Florian is taken away by another officer. I ask this officer if I can make call, no luck. I’m advised I must wait for a “Licensed Translator” to arrive before I can be processed. I open my wallet, and the warden allows me to stay in his office and write, passing the time together over cigarettes and water. By the end, it cost me nine euro for the privilege.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;part-iii-a-big-ol-waste-of-everybodys-time&quot;&gt;Part III: A big ol’ waste of everybody’s time&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The morning glow peeks through jail cell’s the crusty barred window. A couple hours sleep on the half-broken chairs did its job, I can’t sleep any longer. The metaphorical clock passes. I say hello to the new warden. He doesn’t speak English either.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Eventually I am taken to be processed. I collect my bag from the warden. They lead me to an office, not more than ten metres from the holding cell. “New Zealand”, I understand, and the man inside shakes his head and points to his side. They lead me to the next office. Three men sit at their desks, a small room. A young man beckons me to sit down beside him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m all smiles. I have been preparing for this moment. “Hi, how are you?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I am good, and you?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Who are you?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I am Officer Kola. Narcotics department.” Kola? Is that a nickname?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“What time is it?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“9:45.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Where is my lawyer?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“He is coming. Here in a few minutes.” Sure, bro. “Passport.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I notice my phone on his desk, right in front of me. “I need to make a phone call.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“You cannot use your phone here. You will be out of here soon.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I need to charge my phone,” I scowl.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I produce a cable, and fumble around with my phone. It’s still on. I hurriedly message Lucie; “I’m ok. Not done yet. Going to meet Lawyer soon. They found 1g weed, that’s the main issue. I think I shouldn’t even get a fine. Talk to you soon. Story coming.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I skim my messages from Lucie. “In contact with the New Zealand Embassy in Rome. The Embassy will contact you. Here’s a list of lawyers in Tirana.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Enough,” barks Kola. “You cannot use your phone here.” I message Jade, “ASK LUCIE”. He shoos me off and I leave it to charge. For the first time, I truly feel relaxed. I hand Kola my passport, and he starts tapping at the keyboard. For a few minutes there is silence between us. He offers me a cigarette.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I study my surroundings. Inside this room lies three messy desks, a few computers, a dusty bookshelf. A large printer sits on a small table in the middle of the room. A small painting hangs on one wall, slightly crooked. Alongside stacks of papers, I see my laptop, snus container, and two plastic evidence bags on his desk. An officer nudges me, the leg of my wooden chair pinching an evidence bag on the floor, and I’d notice the jumbled stack of evidence behind me. A piss in a cup. In one corner, a man sits at his computer, same age as I am.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“What is in this bag?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“What do you think this is? Haven’t these idiots taken it to the lab yet? Why are you asking me?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;His face remains still. “Anyone can find out what this is with a quick Google search. There is no need to send it to the lab.” He puts down the snus and lifts the other bag. “And what is this?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I don’t understand what you are talking about. I need a, ✌Licensed Translator✌.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“We do not need a translator, we can –”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Oh,” I interject, raising my voice. I’ve never grinned harder. The sarcasm is dripping out of my mouth. “There’s no Licensed Translator? You mean to tell me I have been waiting in this jail cell for ten hours, waiting for a ✌Licensed Translator ✌to arrive, yet we do not need one? Problem is, I don’t understand you!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are other officers loitering around in the background, at the other desk, inside the room, outside the room. “I am not your enemy,” he says. “I have to follow the procedure. We are not going to charge you with anything. If you tell me it is for personal consumption, you can leave.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I have to follow the procedure too. Tell me, where is my lawyer?” I say angrily, cracking another wide smile.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“He will be here in two minutes.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I keep quiet. Kola’ asks some more questions, innocent ones too. “How long have you been here?” 
“What are you doing here in Tirana?” “What is your father’s name?” I start to feel a little bit sorry for Kola. He is just doing his job, but his colleagues brought me here. Each time I throw him shit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kola relaxes from his keyboard, and the printer starts to buzzing. Bzzz… “Yeah, I’d love a coffee thanks.” …Bzzz… I pass him his machine-made espresso and take a sip of my own. …Bzzz. The printer stops, and I hand them to him. Eighteen pages. These are for me!?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Like many of the people I have seen here, Kola wears plain clothes – black t-shirt, black pants, black shoes. In stark contrast, I am wearing an off-white linen shirt, my favourite pink shorts. I’d guess, best-dressed in the entire building. That is, until my lawyer arrives.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Petrin walks in, and Kola hands him the eighteen pages. They obviously already know eachother. Petrin and I take some time alone. He explains to me that this is a very simple case, and they’re going to let me go. In terms of marijuana, Albania has some of the harshest penalties in Europe. New reforms around legalization of medicinal cannabis passed just months ago, and there are now proposals for total legalization. Police still firmly treat marijuana strictly, though there are no penalties for possession of less than three grams, as long as it is for personal consumption. The system has a big problem: they must follow the same procedure, whether it’s one gram or one hundred kilos.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We start to go through the papers together. He translates sentence by sentence. The first two paragraphs consist of explanatory information gleamed from my passport, some references to laws, [xxxx – acquire and translate]. Then it describes how I was arrested – in possession of suspected cannabis, in possession of suspected nicotine. Nicotine?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I take Petrin through one part of the story – the accusation of cocaine. He suggests I can ask to have it altered if I want, but that, though it would not really matter, from a legal perspective, altering the page to suggest I might have had cocaine could only be a bad thing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I take Petrin through the rest; the approach, the accusation of cocaine, the first officer who rubs his thumb against his two fingers. I discuss the denial of water (to someone who is, in their view, probably on drugs), the denial of contact, holding me for far longer than necessary. He explains that there is no process here by which I can add this information. He suggests I can always send a formal complaint later, otherwise I would have to sue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We go through the rest of the pages. On each page, the first two paragraphs are repeated. Then there is a little section about the formal procedure that has or will be followed, and my acceptance of it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;… The suspected nicotine has been bagged in an evidence bag, in accordance with some standard… Fine, I’ll sign.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;… The suspected marijuana has been weighed. It weight 0.7 grams, including the plastic… Fine, I’ll sign.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;… You have the right to remain silent… Excuse me, I have rights? Nobody has told you your rights?… Fine, I’ll sign.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kola comes back and I talk freely. I briefly run him through the same story I’ve told Petrin, and advise him I will be submitting a formal complaint for unethical, probably illegal conduct leading up to my arrest and detention. For the first time, I see him crack a little smile. He offers me another cigarette as we chat about the absurdity of the situation, of the system. This has been a big ol’ waste of everybody’s time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The police officers who arrested me knew I was going to walk away with no charge. Muscleman, 13565, Mr Illiterate, and all the other officers involved in my case. How many police resources have been wasted on me? How many policeman were involved, how many man hours? Over twenty pages of paperwork – someone at the prosecution office is supposed to read these. A lawyer, a civil servant – it’s not my responsibility to pay him! Twelve hours of my personal time. But not just my time - my girlfriend was up all night searching for how to defend me. My sister, too. I have in my inbox, emails from the New Zealand Embassy in Rome that I shall reply to. Lucie tried, Jade tried, the Embassy tried, but nobody could reach the police station. They send how many police officers to detain and arrest me, but not a single officer to answer the phone? That this happened to at least two other people last night; that this is normal; that this happens on a completely regular basis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I sign all the paperwork except for one. I consent for my piss to be tested for narcotic content in the lab. But I refuse to consent to giving a urine sample. I had argued with Petrin. “It doesn’t matter. Positive for marijuana, personal consumption. Negative, you were going to smoke it. Positive for heroin? Where’s the heroin? There’s no evidence.” “I don’t want to piss in a cup. Let me refuse, they will make me anyway, and I will piss all over it!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They gave me a plastic cup anyway. Kola tells me, “Just a little is enough.” I haven’t pissed in six hours. Another police officer took me to the bathroom and waited outside. I fill it to the brim, tighten the lid, then wash it in the sink. The officer outside holds a plastic evidence bag open. I bend down, place it on the ground, then shake the water off my hands.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Laughing his ass off, Kola gives me his number. “You can contact me about anything, it does not have to be about this case.” Petrin and I head out for coffee.&lt;/p&gt;

          </description>
          <pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
          <link>http://localhost:4000/Jail-In-Tirana-EN.html</link>
          <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/Jail-In-Tirana-EN.html</guid>
          
          
        </item>
      
    
      
        <item>
          
            <title>Marseilles is not the same as Versailles</title>
          
          <author>fakeemail@gmail.com (Kauri's BS)</author>
          <description>
            &lt;h5 id=&quot;thursday-13th-april&quot;&gt;Thursday 13th April&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was sitting atop a little hill in the middle of a roundabout, making lunch, overlooking the quiet roads, enjoying the view of the distant rolling hills. “Wait, is that a pack cover? That’s a bloody hitchhiker!” He stepped out of the car near the roundabout, a young Frenchman. We chatted over a couple dry sandwiches. He had a week off work, to go hiking, camping and surfing. We were both headed to Bordeaux and the West Coast, and decided to try travel together together… I figured, surely with two people, two guys none the less, it &lt;strong&gt;must&lt;/strong&gt; be harder. I was utterly stunned when literally the first car to drive by stopped.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Seems many people in this area only speak French, so having Arthur to translate was a big bonus. He is a brilliant conversationalist, always talking to people and making them laugh. We are similar in many ways, and got along well. After waiting for fifteen minutes on a bus with no driver, we decided there must be cameras; they’re just fucking with us. That’s what we’d do, if we had control. Fuck with people. I pull out one of Callum’s standard lines; “What would you do if you were a dictator?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course, it’s important that people are highly educated. Everybody would have to study math for one hour a day. It’s important that the government is transparent with its people. The government website would have the answer to literally anything you, a citizen, might need. All the laws and the regulations, the bus timetables, the answers to the weekly math test. It’s all there, everything, on the home page. The only page. Ctrl-f would zoom in.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We were dropped at a major toll booth and waited for ~15 minutes for someone to stop. Arthur chatted up the driver, then asked me, “Do you want to go to the coast, or do you want to go to Marseilles?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With a little hesitation – “Fuck it – let’s go to Marseilles!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We squeezed into this raggedy little car, five people, my head cocked against the ceiling. Almost immediately, we took a wrong turn. We were headed backwards, to Lyon, where Arthur had started his journey. It didn’t take me long to realize Versailles and Marseilles are not the same place…
Fuck it, be like the wind.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our driver was kind, and dropped us near the base of Mont Carpiagne. A fair deal, in exchange to listening to your mix tapes for two hours. It took us three hours to the peak, including detours and exploration. But considering that, despite our giant backpacks we kept pace with a large group of joggers, your mileage may vary.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With a stunning 270° sunset – sunrise view of the city, and pitched camp nearby, the wind battering us, howling. I strapped up between the legs of a power pylon, uneven ground, with one end of the tarp a good metre above the ground. I knew it was a bad idea – but determined to have the coolest-ever-hammock setup, and armed with Arthur’s rock-stacking alternative to pegs, my stubborn ass stood ground.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;\assets\images\marseilles_hammock_sunset.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;marseilles_hammock_sunset&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Look out for the stubborn monkey!&lt;/figcaption&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;friday-14th-april&quot;&gt;Friday 14th April&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3.00 am – One of the tarpaulin tie-downs snaps. The flapping tarp wakes me up. I secure it to my backpack.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3.15 am – The adjacent tie-down breaks. The lazy fucker I am, I knot it around my feet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3.45 am – My butt is freezing. Something has shifted, I’m not certain how. I restack some rocks upwind.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;6.00 am – I need a piss. I can’t leave my hammock without the tarpaulin going haywire, so I decide to pack down. I notice, those rocks I restacked… one of those lines is broken too, but by some miracle it still held together. I’m not sure even I understand how that could happen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;6:05 am – I discover the fourth upwind line has broken too. This one broke in-between the shock cord, which is how it’s intended to work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
The next day, the lady in the outdoor store is confused as to why on earth I need ten metres of this specific camping line. She was rather sweet, and gave us an amazing camping recommendation!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We climbed back down the mountain towards the city, wandered the streets of Marseilles, went for a swim, and retired in the prettiest hostel I’ve ever seen. [Editor’s note: I really should have written more about Marseilles, but alas.]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;saturday-15th-april&quot;&gt;Saturday 15th April&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We went on to Montparnasse and did much of the same – though far prettier a city! We set up camp  at a local rock-climbing place, just a short bus ride on the city outskirts. After a few drinks at the top of the baby cliff, Arthur said something I shall not forget. “Your mind is like a garden. The more you nurture it, the more it will grow, the more resilient it will become. You must plant it with solid, diverse, healthy plants, such that even in absence of conscious effort, it can continue to flourish, a stable ecosystem.” Easier said than done?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;sunday-16th-april&quot;&gt;Sunday 16th April&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Arthur and I split ways in the morning. It’s late here at the train station in Perpignan, “the centre of the universe”. I’m prepared to find these secret hot pools, deep in the Pyrenees Mountains.&lt;/p&gt;

          </description>
          <pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
          <link>http://localhost:4000/Marseilles-is-not-the-same-as-Versailles.html</link>
          <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/Marseilles-is-not-the-same-as-Versailles.html</guid>
          
          
        </item>
      
    
      
        <item>
          
            <title>Draft&amp;#58; Today I Fucked Up&amp;#58; Hammock</title>
          
          <author>fakeemail@gmail.com (Kauri's BS)</author>
          <description>
            &lt;p&gt;Needs a better title&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;friday-26th-june&quot;&gt;Friday 26th June&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, technically I fucked up three weeks ago when I put my name on the delivery for a rather special type of fabric. Or maybe I fucked up when I put a little hole in my hammock, or when I thought Decathlon had the solution. In any case, a culmination of little fuck-ups has led me to sleeping on the ground for the next month.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Travelling by hitchhike, you have to be flexible. I don’t always know where I’m going to sleep. Sometimes it’s with friends, sometimes with strangers, but my hammock has been the shining star. Though I usually take time to find a beautiful spot, in a pinch it sets up almost anywhere with two trees. And if there’s no trees, then a power pylon… but that’s another story. It’s quick to set up, warm, more comfortable than my own bed. By -5° I’m getting too cold. Made of a particular material specifically designed for hammocks - strong, lightweight, breathable. Flammable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;\assets\images\hammock_example.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;hammock_example&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt; A pretty typical hammock setup. Tarpaulin above for the rain and wind, underquilt beneath for insulation.&lt;/figcaption&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first fuckup occurred in Salzberg, Austria. I stayed in a hostel a couple nights to sort out some admin. Regrettably, I hardly saw the city, other than on a couple runs. Regrettably, I forgot to stock up on gas for my camping stove; key for dinners and coffee. I was running critically low, and didn’t even realize.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first night back on the road, I headed to Obenburgau, at the base of of Schafberg, a mountain in Austria. Tomorrow I’d do a mountain crossing - but tonight, well, I’d found in the foothills a cave overlooking a roaring waterfall. There’s no good trees in this cave; fuck the hammock.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;\assets\images\Hammock_schlafberg_waterfall.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;hammock_schlafberg_waterfall&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;In hindsight, I should have considered the hearing damage - though it didn&apos;t stop me falling asleep!&lt;/figcaption&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now I’ve just noticed the gas situation. I’m hungry, I want some bloody pasta! No problem - I’ll save it, I’m going to build a campfire instead. Tomorrow will be Saturday, and you’d better make pace tomorrow and get to the other side of this mountain - because on Sunday, because fucking Germany, everything’s closed. The Monday’s a public holiday too. I’ll save the last dregs of gas for coffee tomorrow morning.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;saturday-27th-june&quot;&gt;Saturday 27th June&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;discuss the hike more!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Schlafberg – gorgeous, gruelling. One-way crossing, lake-to-lake. Nice to get the legs properly working. Not so many people on the trail, but you get to the top, and there’s everybody and their mum. Literally. A cable car takes you to the restaurant at the top! A skifield in winter, bustling it seems. And for good reason – 360 degree views of the Lakes, the Alps, Austrian towns.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Magnificent views from the top! I hiked down the other side to St Wolfgang at reasonable pace too, to catch the shops before they closed. Time crunch to make it back to town, St Wolfgang. There’s an outdoor store there, I’ll top up my gas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Actually, I do take an hour-long nap on the trail. I hear noisy, obnoxious people draw closer – and decide not to be stuck behind them. At one point I waited for a few moments for some others to catch up, at an intersection between an unpaved road, and a typical forest path. I asked them which was faster to St Wolfgang – more an icebreaker than a genuine question. They switched to English, and he said, in all seriousness, “We are going this way, but considering the shoes you’re wearing, maybe you should go the other way.” HI was, jogging down a gnarly mountain with my giant backpack, and I’m told my shoes are inadequate? Do I look like such a rookie? They only caught up with me because I took a 30 minute nap on a log! Stunned, all I could muster was a lousy “Come on?” I followed them briefly down the forest trail, then pulled a controlled jog-slide down a short, steep bypass, leaving them in the dust. Though, the rest of the walk I only felt embarrassment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I made it to St Wolfgang before the outdoor store closed. And who would have known, the only outdoor store in this down doesn’t sell gas. Bother. Well, There’s one supermarket here - I’ll eat cold for the meanwhile – better stock up! What do I need - fresh fruit, cheese, bread, spread, salami… Those few minutes writing down a shopping list ticked me over to 5:01pm, and supermarket closed its doors. For fucks sake.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I went for a swim in the lake, then ordered myself a large pizza.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;monday-29th-june&quot;&gt;Monday 29th June&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The mesmeric lighting, comforting warmth, smoky atmosphere, delightful smell, the humble crackle. Fuck, I love fire.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m strung up in my hammock in a nicely wooded area, nearby some creepy abandoned building in Germany. I’ve gotten pretty good at cooking myself one-pot meals. Recipe: Fry onions, capsicum and garlic until onions turn gold. Add herbs &amp;amp; spices per preference. Add water and bring to boil, add carb of choice, stir, boil, drain. Optional extras include pasta sauce, cheese, salami, chickpeas, beans, vegetables of choice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most of the time I’m carrying two-to-three day supply of food. I ate the last of my fresh food today. I’m hungry. These days I’m always hungry (Editor’s note: hungry in a good way - I’m not bloody starving myself!) Cold coffee and cheese-salami this morning just hasn’t cut it. Let’s fucking cook us a meal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All that to say, I made a little campfire. It was a crackly one, and I definitely built it too close. One stray ember put a garlic-sized hole in my hammock, an onion-shaped tear in my eye. I’m going to sleep in my hammock, a paranoid statue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;sunday-4th-june&quot;&gt;Sunday 4th June&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The last week I’ve been in Poznan, Poland to celebrate my friend Sachin’s graduation. During that time I ordered a sheet of Hexon 1.6, hammock material, to Lucia’s place in Munich. With it coming from the USA, the shipping time is uncertain. So, the other day I popped into a Decathlon for some repair patches.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;\assets\images\hammock_graduation.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;hammock_graduation&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;kjhlkjh&lt;/figcaption&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This evening I found a lovely spot by a river beach near Bamberg, Germany, and set up shop. I went for a run upstream, then swam back down. Then I retired into my hammock, and – RIIIIP!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;\assets\images\hammock_tear.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;hammock_tear&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;&quot;I&apos;ll just use a Decathlon repair patch.&quot;&lt;/figcaption&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In slow motion, I felt myself fall, my ass hitting the soft sandy floor. Defeated, I lay down on the ground beneath me, contemplating my choices in life, blissfully unaware of the brewing storm - the Battle Against the Mosquitoes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;date-must-have-been-a-weekday--1-day&quot;&gt;date? must have been a weekday + 1 day&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After a couple nights on the ground, I made it to Munich, where I waited out the timer. In this time I co-authored a research paper, aced my GMAT (General Management Admissions Test, generally used for MBA admission) and found a new bone to pick with Lucia’s pretentious landlord-flatmate. Oh, and I ordered a replacement keyboard for my surface, too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s been too long in the city, I’ve been itching to head back into the Bavarian Alps. I’ve studied the maps as usual, and there’s so many options for multi-day hikes. I need my hammock material. I pack my bags and plan to go bivvy mode, but the material, it arrives! Well, it being a slip of paper in the mailbox. Excuse me? I was at home, ya lazy bugger. Alright, let’s go to the PO Box three kilometeres away.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;\assets\images\hammock_bivvy_mode.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;hammock_bivvy_mode&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;funny caption&lt;/figcaption&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lucia accompanies me, her name on the slip. We open the PO Box and, aha! A box, printed with “the United States Postal Service”! It’s rather large and heavy, for a bit of material. Precious stuff, amirite? We head to a coffee shop nearby to relax, bringing the average age down at least a decade. We chat, and then open the box, full of paper shreds threatening to blow away in the wind. The waitress finally takes our coffee order, and help us chase down the stragglers. The look on Lucia’s face as she unveils the bubblewrap. A keyboard!?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We check the shipping label, sent from Berlin. This motherfucker had used an old USPS box from a shipment from Berlin! Bewildered, I check the shipment tracking details again, to discover, despite having been made two weeks apart, both shipments had been delivered at the exact same time. That means only one thing: the hammock material must still be in the PO Box! Our coffees arrive, and we smash them faster than two bored bunnies could, and say bye-bye to the wait staff. I wonder what they thought. Worst - or best date ever?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course, we can’t open the PO Box again. Eventually we get some help on the phone, but they would have to open it tomorrow. Bear in mind, this whole time I’m carrying my rucksack, ready to jump on the next train out of Munich. And there’s no way I’m allowed to stay another night with Lucia’s landlord breathing down her neck. Fuck’s sake. We call again to get more clarity, wandering the street as we wait on hold, transferred between departments. Eventually Lucia gives them the international tracking code, and I see her face drop…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Oh, nein, nein, nein, nein, nein, nein nein!” Her tone immediately shifts to one of urgency. After some back-and-forth, she asks the other side to wait. She explains, “The mailman tried to deliver it, but couldn’t see your name on the mailbox. It’s going to be shipped back to the States; there’s nothing she can do!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I take my pack off and collapse on the sidewalk. What the fuck is this bureaucracy? The package is still in Munich but, but what? Your system is so fucking automated you can’t pull a product off the shelf? This fucking mailman - you didn’t even knock! I was there, an open window apart, working on my laptop - you can literally see me from the road! This package flew halfway across the world, to make it less than five metres away… No email, no notification, not even an update in the tracking system, which just says… “Delivered at 3:29pm.” Well fuck you too!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m writing from my farmland campsite in the mountains of Immerstadt, with the most brilliant view of tomorrow’s mountains. I do now have Lucia’s inflatable mattress, compact little thing, which I only brought after much heated debate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;\assets\images\hammock_ground_campsite.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;hammock_ground_campsite&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Tomorrow&apos;s mountain hike&lt;/figcaption&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“But I’m TOUGH! How will anyone know how TOUGH I am if I choose to bring a sleeping mat?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“…What the fuck is wrong with you?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Her argument did not resonate, but I lost that game of Paper, Scissors, Rock.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;date-&quot;&gt;date ??&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My plan was flawed anyway. It took me three hours of stitching to realize;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1) I barely know how to handstitch
2) Even if I knew how to handstitch, I don’t have the time for this; it’s going to take forever!
3) Even if I had the time to handstitch, I have no bloody idea if this is going to work at all!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bear in mind, this tear is almost the entire width of the hammock, and it goes under a lot of stress, 100% of which needs to be transferred through the patch. This wonky backstitch just isn’t going to cut it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A shitty 10€ hammock from Kiwi (a supermarket chain in Norway) carried me through the next month, until I arrived at Cologne to stay with Lucia’s family. I must say a big thankyou to Lucia’s mother, who took it into the tailor for me. And to my surprise, it’s still holding on!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;\assets\images\hammock_patch.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;hammock_patch&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;funny caption&lt;/figcaption&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;\assets\images\hammock_croatia.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;hammock_croatia&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Another sunset with my hammock.&lt;/figcaption&gt;

          </description>
          <pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
          <link>http://localhost:4000/TIFU-Hammock.html</link>
          <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/TIFU-Hammock.html</guid>
          
          
        </item>
      
    
      
        <item>
          
            <title>TEMPLATE</title>
          
          <author>fakeemail@gmail.com (Kauri's BS)</author>
          <description>
            &lt;h5 id=&quot;date&quot;&gt;Date&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Body text goes here&lt;/p&gt;

          </description>
          <pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
          <link>http://localhost:4000/Template.html</link>
          <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/Template.html</guid>
          
          
        </item>
      
    
      
        <item>
          
            <title>Dear Emil&apos;s Mother</title>
          
          <author>fakeemail@gmail.com (Kauri's BS)</author>
          <description>
            &lt;h5 id=&quot;tuesday-23rd-may&quot;&gt;Tuesday 23rd May&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dear Emil’s mother,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
I just wanted to say a proper thankyou for everything – your kindness has not been lost on me! 
When Emil and his girlfriend Paula asked me if I was hungry – and suggested we detour to a specific kebab shop in Brussels – I did not expect Paula to return with just one giant kebab for me! Somehow I feel you have been a wonderful mother… your kindness is certainly reflected in your son!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
I’m sorry about the night prior. I was camped thirty metres into a rather beautiful bush behind a construction site, where Emil and Paula dropped me off. (I was definitely not supposed to be there!) Not recognizing Emil and Paula, but shadowed strangers calling in the distance, I turned my head torch off and hid!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
And the breakfast, lunch and constant snacks – you really stuffed all three of us kids! I have never been offered a full change of clothes before after a shower – let alone a brand new vape!
My friends ask me to tell stories – and it seems, for some reason, now they all want to meet you and your family. Though we could not speak directly, I felt your motherly warmth and kindness. I really enjoyed spending the afternoon with you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
What is it about your culture, that makes you so kind to strangers? Along my travels I met many Ukranian people, and they have all been so friendly, emotionally open, curious, kind, caring, charitable to me. One day, when this is all over, I must visit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
I wish all the best for you, your family and your countrymen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Until I see you again,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Kauri&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Ps: I ate all your chocolate in two days.&lt;/p&gt;

          </description>
          <pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
          <link>http://localhost:4000/Dear-Emil's-Mother.html</link>
          <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/Dear-Emil's-Mother.html</guid>
          
          
        </item>
      
    
      
        <item>
          
            <title>Intro</title>
          
          <author>fakeemail@gmail.com (Kauri's BS)</author>
          <description>
            &lt;p&gt;XXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXX&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Saturday 17th June 2023&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dear friends and family, and to those of you I’ve met along the way,
As you may or may not know, for the last five months I’ve been travelling around Europe. I’ve been skiing in Austria and France, exploring the German/Austrian Alps, and spent days searching for secret hot springs in the Pyrenees Mountains.  I’ve attempted to live in the UK, attended a graduation ceremony in Poland, and (unofficially) co-authored a research paper in Germany. I’ve hitchhiked over 9,000km to date. I’ve contemplated life, battered by howling winds, hanging beneath the legs of a mountaintop power pylon. It’s been a quarter-life crisis of an adventure, and I’d like to share that with you.
I’m ashamed to say, I’m not exactly great at sharing my life. I think about you a lot. (Some of you, more than others.) That’s why I’ve decided to create this blog, to share with you some of my favourite stories from my travels. Some are stories of love and kindness, of the beautiful people I’ve met along the way. Others are of failure and frustration, or chaos and absurdity. Some yet are simply a documentation of the beauty of nature.
I hope you enjoy snf get s glimplse into my life here snf the advdenture I call life – align with blog name/cargchphrase 
Love,
Kauri
Ps: For those of you wondering, I’ve also decided, fuck the plans to work in the UK. I’ll be doing a Masters degree in Germany, come October. You can read more about that here.
Pps: Some stories will have German translations. In fact, some stories are English translations. To you Germans, if you want a proper laugh, feel free to check out the originals.&lt;/p&gt;

          </description>
          <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
          <link>http://localhost:4000/Introduction.html</link>
          <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/Introduction.html</guid>
          
          
        </item>
      
    
      
        <item>
          
            <title>Intro</title>
          
          <author>fakeemail@gmail.com (Kauri's BS)</author>
          <description>
            &lt;p&gt;XXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXX&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Saturday 17th June 2023&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dear friends and family, and to those of you I’ve met along the way,
As you may or may not know, for the last five months I’ve been travelling around Europe. I’ve been skiing in Austria and France, exploring the German/Austrian Alps, and spent days searching for secret hot springs in the Pyrenees Mountains.  I’ve attempted to live in the UK, attended a graduation ceremony in Poland, and (unofficially) co-authored a research paper in Germany. I’ve hitchhiked over 9,000km to date. I’ve contemplated life, battered by howling winds, hanging beneath the legs of a mountaintop power pylon. It’s been a quarter-life crisis of an adventure, and I’d like to share that with you.
I’m ashamed to say, I’m not exactly great at sharing my life. I think about you a lot. (Some of you, more than others.) That’s why I’ve decided to create this blog, to share with you some of my favourite stories from my travels. Some are stories of love and kindness, of the beautiful people I’ve met along the way. Others are of failure and frustration, or chaos and absurdity. Some yet are simply a documentation of the beauty of nature.
I hope you enjoy snf get s glimplse into my life here snf the advdenture I call life – align with blog name/cargchphrase 
Love,
Kauri
Ps: For those of you wondering, I’ve also decided, fuck the plans to work in the UK. I’ll be doing a Masters degree in Germany, come October. You can read more about that here.
Pps: Some stories will have German translations. In fact, some stories are English translations. To you Germans, if you want a proper laugh, feel free to check out the originals.&lt;/p&gt;

          </description>
          <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
          <link>http://localhost:4000/Introduction-DE.html</link>
          <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/Introduction-DE.html</guid>
          
          
        </item>
      
    
      
        <item>
          
            <title>Language1 EN</title>
          
          <author>fakeemail@gmail.com (Kauri's BS)</author>
          <description>
            &lt;p&gt;donkey kong&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;asdojskd;fla
askljfe3;lk2j;4lk2j34po23uj 
@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@K#J@O*&amp;amp;$U#IO@JKL@J#???&lt;/p&gt;

          </description>
          <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
          <link>http://localhost:4000/Langtest-EN.html</link>
          <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/Langtest-EN.html</guid>
          
          
        </item>
      
    
      
        <item>
          
            <title>Deutschsprache2</title>
          
          <author>fakeemail@gmail.com (Kauri's BS)</author>
          <description>
            &lt;p&gt;donkey kong&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;asdojskd;fla
askljfe3;lk2j;4lk2j34po23uj 
@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@K#J@O*&amp;amp;$U#IO@JKL@J#???&lt;/p&gt;

          </description>
          <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
          <link>http://localhost:4000/Langtest-DE.html</link>
          <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/Langtest-DE.html</guid>
          
          
        </item>
      
    
      
        <item>
          
            <title>The Adventure of the Cardboard Box and a longer word poop 12312312</title>
          
          <author>fakeemail@gmail.com (Kauri's BS)</author>
          <description>
            &lt;p&gt;In choosing a few typical cases which illustrate the remarkable mental qualities of my friend, Sherlock Holmes&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:1&quot; role=&quot;doc-noteref&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:1&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot; rel=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;, I have endeavoured, as far as possible, to select those which presented the minimum of sensationalism, while offering a fair field for his talents. It is, however, unfortunately impossible entirely to separate the sensational from the criminal, and a chronicler is left in the dilemma that he must either sacrifice details which are essential to his statement and so give a false impression of the problem, or he must use matter which chance, and not choice, has provided him with. With this short preface I shall turn to my notes of what proved to be a strange, though a peculiarly terrible, chain of events.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was a blazing hot day in August. Baker Street was like an oven, and the glare of the sunlight upon the yellow brickwork of the house across the road was painful to the eye. It was hard to believe that these were the same walls which loomed so gloomily through the fogs of winter. Our blinds were half-drawn, and Holmes lay curled upon the sofa, reading and re-reading a letter which he had received by the morning post. For myself, my term of service in India had trained me to stand heat better than cold, and a thermometer at ninety was no hardship. But the morning paper was uninteresting. Parliament had risen. Everybody was out of town, and I yearned for the glades of the New Forest or the shingle of Southsea. A depleted bank account had caused me to postpone my holiday, and as to my companion, neither the country nor the sea presented the slightest attraction to him. He loved to lie in the very center of five millions of people, with his filaments stretching out and running through them, responsive to every little rumour or suspicion of unsolved crime. Appreciation of nature found no place among his many gifts, and his only change was when he turned his mind from the evil-doer of the town to track down his brother of the country.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;footnotes&quot; role=&quot;doc-endnotes&quot;&gt;
  &lt;ol&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:1&quot; role=&quot;doc-endnote&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;This is some text for a footnote. &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:1&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot; role=&quot;doc-backlink&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

          </description>
          <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
          <link>http://localhost:4000/the-adventure-of-the-cardboard-box.html</link>
          <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/the-adventure-of-the-cardboard-box.html</guid>
          
          
          <category>literature</category>
          
        </item>
      
    
  </channel>
</rss>
