<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Kauri&apos;s BS</title>
    <description>...that&apos;s Brilliant Stories, duh</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 03:35:52 +0100</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 03:35:52 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v4.3.2</generator>
    
      
        <item>
          
            <title>An Albanian Cycle Tour&lt;br&gt;Week Two</title>
          
          <author>fakeemail@gmail.com (Kauri's BS)</author>
          <description>
            &lt;h5 id=&quot;thursday-19th-octoberday-11-beginning-of-week-two&quot;&gt;Thursday 19th October&lt;br /&gt;Day 11, beginning of Week Two&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Days 8-10 we were back in Tirana, catching up with Ebony and other friends and ex-colleagues. We made some adjustments to our gear and stocked up on resources, then headed back out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;\assets\images\cycle2\leavingtirana.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;leavingtirana&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt; Excited to leave Tirana. &lt;/figcaption&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After having both of us been in Tirana (and its county outskirts) for more than a month, we’re finally leaving the city, possibly for good. This time we just bolted it south, direction Vlore, gateway to the Albanian Riviera, 180km to the south. To take a faster route than before, we decided to finally cycle the highway we’d managed so long avoiding. It was wide and there were surprisingly few cars on it. Makes sense, considering the price of gas is the same here as in Europe.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A new road took us into the next valley over, one big step deeper into this Tirana County’s mountaneous terrain. A short detour off this reasonably-main road would take us to a waterfall we’d wanted to visit last week. But the road became steeper, and quickly its condition deteriorated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At first, I could manage, but eventually the legs gave in. I hadn’t expected such a challenge today, and had already cycled the earlier roads at pace enough to impress the lifelong cyclist in Zak. I developed technique to wrestle down the head of the rear-heavy beast, but on the steepest bits the beast was stronger than me. Pushing it was as difficult as riding. After trying some different strategies to progress, including Zak helping to ram my back up the hills, he took a turn on my bike, and was blown away by its ridiculous instability. Tomorrow I’ll pack some weight on the front.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We haven’t reached our waterfall yet, just 1km sky - but here’s a gorgeous spot to camp in the olive gardens, and I’m too exhausted to be interested in gambling against the dying light.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;friday-20th-october&quot;&gt;Friday 20th October&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After hiking down for a swim in the waterfall, we could have turned back and ridden out the way we came. Or, we could go deeper into the mountains, and try to find another way out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As expected, the path grew steeper, and wilder in condition. Rocky, rugged and overgrown. We pushed our bikes more than we rode, oftentimes both pushing one bike up the most challenging parts of the “road”, according to Google maps. The locals ride this road on donkeys and dirt bikes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;\assets\images\cycle2\arealroad.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;arealroad&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt; This is the road, seriously. &lt;/figcaption&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I had to rewire how I thought about the challenge. Sure, I’m reasonably fit and strong, but I’m a novice when it comes to cycle touring, and hadn’t expected such difficult challenge. I’d shifted some weight to the front of the bike which seemed to calm the beast, but couldn’t solve these demonous hills. I was becoming increasingly frustrated with the absurd difficulty. But after realizing I could simply treat this like one of my strenuous hikes - but instead of carrying it, you awkwardly push your luggage uphill - I began to appreciate the beauty of the challenge. We also had some brief, beautiful downhills today, and tomorrow we’re formally descending.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;\assets\images\cycle2\theroadbehind.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;theroadbehind&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt; A view of our today&apos;s journey. &lt;/figcaption&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We stopped to chat with a lone farmer, who offered us some pomegranites. Unbeknownst to him, we’d just demolished three, the only food we ate during the day. We’d held off a formal meal, with promise of finding bread in the upcoming town.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;\assets\images\cycle2\juicy.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;juicy&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt; Juicy. &lt;/figcaption&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bread, we found. We encountered the town, a village consisting of a few houses, families, poultry and land. We chatted with some locals, seeking a campsite for the night. Before departing they offered us two warm buns, topped with fried egg and sheep cheese.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tonight I have what I call a “wild hang”. Finding a spot when there’s only shrubs usually requires creativity. In the photo below, the left strap is extended just as long as the right - it’s hidden in the bushes. I’ve never spanned the full length of both straps before. Fingers crossed we hold through the nights.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;\assets\images\cycle2\windy.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;windy&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt; The hammock blowing on the side of a windy mountain. &lt;/figcaption&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;saturday-21st-october&quot;&gt;Saturday 21st October&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve fallen in love with downhill biking. I always knew I would. So much fucking fun. I’ll probably write more about it another time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;\assets\images\cycle2\theroadahead.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;theroadahead&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt; The road ahead. &lt;/figcaption&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;\assets\images\cycle2\uphilldownhill.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;uphilldownhill&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt; Gotta go uphill to go downhill. &lt;/figcaption&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tonight though, the flickering in the sky is back. We’re on a farm in the valley toward Berat, but this time we have no animals. I can’t be bothered with this wild hang tonight. Though, if I ever have to, I’ve come up with an idea for how to hang a hammock within bamboo trees that’s probably quite dangerous.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last night, I hadn’t been able to hang high enough, because there wasn’t any higher in the rocky shrubs to tie the hammock’s long anchors to. I’d slept with the side of my bottom nudging the ground. This happens occasionally when the trees are a bit too close together, or if one of them is flexing too much. It typically drops in height zero to five inches during the night, depending on the flex of the trees it’s supported by.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tonight, one end was perfectly fine, tied high to a thick tree trunk. The other, looped and cranked tight around a large bunch of bamboo trees. I could crank my straps with all my body weight, and use that tension to hold the trees in a bunch, to pull them backwards from their resting position. The hammock wasn’t heavy enough on it’s own to hold the tension in place, and the bamboo trees bent and stretched the hammock in the opposing direction. But when I’d sit in it, my weight was enough to bend fifteen bamboo trees toward me, losing all of the tension in the hammock. I failed with three methods to hold the tension in place. One method snapped a bamboo tree in half. All methods ended with my bum eventually touching the ground. Though I still like it, the resulting hang is not particularly comfortable. If I had a rope strong enough I could first anchor the bamboo anchor the bamboo in place,
 in the other direction, cranking it similarly to my hammock, but in the other direction and to the ground. Failure would be potentially sudden and catastrophic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyway, my bottom’s nudging the ground again. Under normal circumstances I wouldn’t be too worried; the fabric is shielded from the ground by my insulating layer, and the material is easily strong enough to endure a lack of tension. But now, the stitching on my hammock’s enormous repair is starting to show further signs of failure. And when it gets a little worse than this, any repairs will become substantially more difficult.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve made the decision to sleep on the ground, a possibility I had considered when I’d chosen this ridiculous spot. In the dark I demonstrated for Zak how to lower the tarpaulin; efficiently and methodically tying and untying knots around bushy bamboo trees, dodging thorns with my hands and bare feet, and pitching a surprisingly perfect tarp setup, adjusted only slightly from where my hammock hung.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s something Zak’s been really interested in, tarp camping. I don’t really know why he doesn’t want to swap though; I have offered. I think he really doesn’t like the idea of bugs. I don’t mind.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;wednesday-25th-octoberdays-14-17&quot;&gt;Wednesday 25th October&lt;br /&gt;Days 14-17&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I haven’t written much these last days, and I probably never will. I hope you enjoy the photos.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We reached Berat, gorgeous city, and decided to stay two nights. I was reasonably antisocial, working on my laptop. We had souvlaki (like kebab) twice a day and made friends with all the volunteers working in the hostel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;\assets\images\cycle2\beratcity.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;beratcity&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;One side of Berat city.&lt;/figcaption&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;\assets\images\cycle2\beratmaya.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;beratmaya&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;The volunteers in Berat.&lt;/figcaption&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On Tuesday we cycled out of Berat through pretty patchwork farmland, the road opened to stunning views of what awaits, of what the locals call The Accursed Moutanins. By now I’m powering up hills; they feel like less of a challenge. We camped in an olive grove on the side of a mountain.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;\assets\images\cycle2\accursedmountains.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;accursedmountains&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;A backdrop of The Accursed Mountains.&lt;/figcaption&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;\assets\images\cycle2\patchworkfarmland.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;patchworkfarmland&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Pretty patchwork farmland.&lt;/figcaption&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today we continued further south, entering Tomorri Mountain National Park in the rain. This must be the most beautiful mountaineous region I’ve seen since the Austrian Alps, and the downhill cycles through the forests gave us a huge rush. We’re headed to camp at a waterfall, hidden at the base of these Accursed Mountains.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;\assets\images\cycle2\tomorripark.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;tomorripark&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Tomorri Mountain National Park.&lt;/figcaption&gt;

          </description>
          <pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
          <link>http://localhost:4000/An-Albanian-Cycle-Tour-Week-Two.html</link>
          <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/An-Albanian-Cycle-Tour-Week-Two.html</guid>
          
          
        </item>
      
    
      
        <item>
          
            <title>An Albanian Cycle Tour&lt;br&gt;Week One</title>
          
          <author>fakeemail@gmail.com (Kauri's BS)</author>
          <description>
            &lt;h5 id=&quot;monday-9th-october&quot;&gt;Monday 9th October&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Day one of cycle touring through Albania.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve never cycle toured before.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I just carry my rucksack.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And this is how I carry my rucksack on a bicycle.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;\assets\images\cycle1\cycle1_rucksack.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;cycle1_rucksack&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Bungee cords.&lt;/figcaption&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zak and I left Tirana mid-day, headed to Pëllumbas, twenty kilometres south-east. On the road we met a couple of German cycle tourists who’d cycled here from somewhere in Bavaria, Germany. Sven helped fixed an issue with my rear derailleur.
Sebastian and Zak rode uphill for some imaginary medal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A good trial for the legs. By the end, the cramps wouldn’t stop.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A good trial for the bicycle. 100€; somehow twice the price of Ebony’s bicycle, yet twice as good of a deal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We followed the street of Pëllumbas in search of a campground.
As the sun set we set camp, overlooking the mouth of the valley, Tirana well in view.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;\assets\images\cycle1\cycle1_viewvalley.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;cycle1_viewvalley&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;The mouth of Pëllumbasit Valley.&lt;/figcaption&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;tuesday-10th-october&quot;&gt;Tuesday 10th October&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’d camped at the beginning of a hike to some spooky cave, as “Black Cave Adventures” advertises it. We packed our bags, ditched our bikes in town, then started hiking up. Sebastian and I turned the hike into a trail run that almost felt as if it hadn’t been so long since my last proper run.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The mouth of Black Cave invites us into it’s darkness.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The throat tightens, the soiled floor becomes a little slippery.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A camoflagued pit threatens to break the ankles of the unprepared.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The bouncer greets us with vicious teeth.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The interior is decorated by the actions of time.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A noisy flock of bats dance along the ceiling.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The private room requires a sacrifice; muddy your knees to enter.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The depths, some few hundred metres, open up high and wide.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bats roost on the ceiling. A couple hundred of them, at least.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The slippery, clayey ground graduates into a twenty-metre-high,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A million-year-old shit in a pile at the back of the cave.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We slobber to the top, just to slide our way down.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;\assets\images\cycle1\cycle1_smile.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;cycle1_smile&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;The Bouncer&apos;s Smile&lt;/figcaption&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the afternoon, Sebastian and Sven departed Pëllumbas to make progress on their journey South.
Zak and I stayed for lunch, then went to find a campsite in Pëllumbasit valley.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;\assets\images\cycle1\cycle1_sebandsven.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;cycle1_sebandsven&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Lunch with Sven and Sebastian&lt;/figcaption&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;wednesday-11th-october&quot;&gt;Wednesday 11th October&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;News from Joe and Ebony, they’re coming south to meet us! They’ve chosen a new destination - Greece. (Well actually Turkey, but now Greece as opposed to North-East through Kosovo.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We stopped for beer at a cafe in a town called Mullet, Zak insisted we must visit. We found camp down a local side street, invited by our new neighbours. Children played games in the yard across from us. A lad brought us a bottle of water.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We filled our bellies with my usual vegetable stew, and shared Zak’s tent. There were no trees for the hammock today.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;thursday-12th-october&quot;&gt;Thursday 12th October&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;News from Joe and Ebony, they’re going to see my dentist in Tirana first.
We’d wait for further intruction.
I cycled to a cafe for the day, whilst Zak took care of camp.
On return, I found we had a new member of the party, Rupert.
In addition to our usual vegetables, we bought a whole chicken.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A neighbour walking past spoke with Zak, whose Albanian has been improving quickly. Zak returned with a heavy bag of gifted fruits. The grapes were gone before morn, but the persimmons would become better with time. The pomegranites, I might have had already nicked a few from the tree…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My eyes grew tired and I couldn’t move.
I slept beneath the stars with Rupert.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;thursday-12th-october-1&quot;&gt;Thursday 12th October&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today we rode just ten kilometres. It took us five hours, because Rupee had decided to followed us the whole way to our next campsite.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rupert joined us while we watched the local mechanic effortlessly patch up a hole in my tire, then took Rupee to the supermarket. He seemed hungry, but too spoilt to eat even sausage! We’d ummed and ahhed about letting him follow on our journey, but in the end, he made the decision for us. We let him follow because we’re headed closer to Tirana, to wait for Joe and Ebony. We’ll take him home when we undoubtedly return to Mullet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;\assets\images\cycle1\cycle1_rupee.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;cycle1_rupee&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Me, Zak and Rupee!&lt;/figcaption&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We stopped a lot for rest and water; I suppose it was a huge journey for him! I even made a cardboard-box passenger seat on the back of my bike, but he hated it. We’d tried, but Rupee quickly jumped out, so we cycled ahead and let him trail us again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Suddenly some barking dogs darted from the bushes behind us, cutting Rupert off. Rupert sprinted backwards, three hungry dogs on tail. Immediately I pulled a u-turn, shouting, hogging the road, holding up cars as I pedalled full-speed. Just as the first dog caught up I was there. I dropped my bike and threatened him with all my might. Like the others, he backed off into the fields, as I cuddled Rupee, cars finally passing by.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This wasn’t the only time this happened, either: the real reason the journey took so long is because we spent half our time escorting this cute, timid doggy past hungry, territorial hounds.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We still had to get past, so this time we walked with him. The dogs continued their harrassing comments, and I threw their aggression back. The commotion brought out the neighbours, and they understood our situation. We finally passed the hounds, but one neighbour followed us, yelling in our direction. Shs smiled at us sweetly as we waited for her to catch up - she was yelling at her neighbours, who in the distance were stamping and smacking the ground, putting out a small fire in the field next door! The smell was nauseous, poisoned by the litter on the side of the road. As we approached we decided to help, stamping the offshoots, spraying the fire with dirt. We left, the largest flames still licking their lips.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Alas, we’d taken a wrong turn, and had to pass back the exact same way fifteen minutes later. By now the fire was reduced to a small flicker. We waved again at the poor men who seemed not to care for the fumes they were standing it. We had to go past the dogs. This time we put Rupee in his passenger seat, and Zak held him as I pedalled at walking pace. The dogs barked furiously, and trailed beside and beside us, but daren’t come near.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We cycled up to a bar at the top of this hill, and a man on the table next to us helped us order the two most expensive beers on the menu. We chatted a while with Klinton. He lives in the UK, family in Tirana. He brought the double-decker bus that sits atop this hill; he brought it from London himself. The waiter brought out the bill… 9 euro!? Did the bus take us back to London? Paulaner Helles, most expensive beers in Albania! Zak and I looked at eachother in panic. We’re down to 6.55 euro between us. But before we could say anything, Klinton announced the beers are on him. He also advised us, if we ever need anything while we’re in Albania, he’s our man.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;\assets\images\cycle1\cycle1_viewtirana.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;cycle1_viewtirana&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;A view of Tirana from the cafe.&lt;/figcaption&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We climbed the hill just a little bit higher, to the ruins of a military base, and set camp. Now we’ll sit tight and wait for Joe to join us, but Ebony might need a bit longer in the city, for her teeth. For tonight I have a wild hang on the hammock across the opening of the old military tunnels, overlooking the mountains of Tirana.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;\assets\images\cycle1\cycle1_viewhammock.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;cycle1_viewhammock&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Zak plays his ukelele.&lt;/figcaption&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;friday-13th-october&quot;&gt;Friday 13th October&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s one of those days.
We lazed all day around the campsite waiting for Joe to turn up.
With a such a beautiful view of Tirana and mountains, why should we move?
I’ve been writing and playing chess, while hiding from the sun.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zak left to get water an hour ago; it should have been a fifteen-minute return.
Joe couldn’t get in due to a security guard watching the road leading up the old military base.
Therefore, Joe cycled to the bottom of the hill, the direction Zak and I had come from.
I waited in my hammock, hopelessly trying to coordinate the boys.
Zak returned with tattered trousers, and Joe pitched tent twenty kilometres away.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As I gave him a bedtime rub, I discovered why all the dogs had been chasing Rupert. Rupee has nipples! Rupert soon acquired another nickname.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;saturday-14th-october&quot;&gt;Saturday 14th October&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was really annoyed today. It took until 4pm to finally link up with Joe, who unknowingly had all our money and food.
We camped by a river back back by Mullet, the same town where we’d picked up Ruby.
In the river I took a much-needed shower, and drief off around our campfire on the beach.
We caught up over the usual food and cheap beer, laughing at the troubles of the day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;sunday-15th-october&quot;&gt;Sunday 15th October&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;\assets\images\cycle1\cycle1_viewcastle.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;cycle1_viewcastle&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Preparing to cycle to the castle in the background.&lt;/figcaption&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’d ummed and ahhed about taking Ruby up to the castle. It’d be a return journey, she’d be as fast as us on the ascent, and we’d come back to camp in the same spot again. But she made the decision for us; while we were stocking up in town she simply disappeared. Fair enough, we hardly fed her breakfast. She didn’t really like the sardines Joe brought her, and they’d made the evidently questionable decision of leaving her dog food on the beach overnight, for fear of attracting some other local wildlife.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The ascent up the castle I made in one go, four hundred metres, I’m rather proud of. As much as I love it, I’m not really a cyclist. The castle was very little, clearly renovated multiple times - the last renovation rather pretty with timber, turned into sort of restaurant.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After some time at the cafe we cycled the winding, exhilirating downhill. As we crossed the bridge back to town, there was Ruby, lying on an island in the roundabout, facing our direction! Of course we stopped for a long belly rub, then went to the market to stock up on dinner, to buy her a chicken.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We came back to the same campsite we were at last night, in the grasses by the river. We set camp and scavenged for firewood, then sat around the riverside fireplace cooking dinner. The typical, but with an extra smoky flavour.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Caramelise onions and whole bulb of garlic, dry-fry paprika then stir together; later add tomatoes then tomato paste. Patience; reasonably low heat. For dry-fry paprika, medium-high. Multiple pasta bases: spaghetti, fusilli and spaghetti. Beef or chicken stock to salt.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We sipped our beers as it got dark, sharing stories and banter. Zak and Joe are friends from high school, and they’ve developed a great storytelling routine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our steaming food was smelling sweet. A lonely cat flickered behind the fire, skulking around the rocks. Of course it had noticed us. “Pass the dog food” Zak asks calmly. “The spiced ham roll, dog food,  human food.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Joe and Zak lure it closer as I lounge behind and comment. After several pieces, she starts to become comfortable, and starts snuggling with Joe’s hands and legs. The cat wanders affectionately to Zak, who’s in charge of distributing Ruby’s breakfast.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I get up and dish out our first serving of pasta, then take my original seat. Now the cat takes an interest in me. Admittedly, I do wolf down that first serving rather selfishly. I’m starving. She nuzzles me nonetheless. Engels, after communism, Zak named her. Later I would have Engles in my lap, playfully clawing and nibbling my fingers as I gave her a rough massage. And after she’d had her fun with us, she was gone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;\assets\images\cycle1\cycle1_campfire.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;cycle1_campfire&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;A campfire on the beach. Left to right: Engles, Zak, Rupert, Joe.&lt;/figcaption&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ruby was gone, too. Tonight she lay with us by the fire. We’d taken our turns cuddling with her. She’s been with us for five nights tonight, tonight the last. I really enjoyed the adventures with her. She was happy, honest, and just so friendly. The locals treat her in kind. She is just a little bit chubby, and her hair is shedding for winter. She’ll be just fine. I reckon she made a quiet departure to the nearby shell-of-a-building as soon as the sky started flickering.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It hasn’t hardly rained here in some while, but finally there’s a storm on the horizon. Thinking back, I haven’t faced one now in months. At first, the looming clouds, the occasional flicker in the sky. The thunder grows, and the first spits come. We gather our belongings around the fireplace, preparing for the formal eviction notice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We don’t feel like going to bed quite yet; there’s space under my tarpaulin. The tarpaulin is set with one corner pegged high to create an open space. The area is somewhat sheltered by the trees, and we feel the uneven pitter-patter of water falling through the branches. Zak sits on the ground, and Joe takes my rucksack. We huddle around our last beer, and ponder the beauty of the situation, the rain falling around us, to feel so close to the outside, the gentle cool draft. They’re experiencing of the best parts about hammock camping.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We wonder about their tents. Zak’s tent has leaked a little bit too, and Joe’s one is definitely not waterproof. Then I feel a drop of water on my face.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s not supposed to happen! I find that water’s slowly leaking through the stitching of the taurpaulin’s ridgeline. Umm… It had that musty smell when I opened it out. I might have left it damp for a month or so. The last time I used it was in Croatia, shit…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyway, tonight is a good trial for all of us. If something’s just not working, maybe it has to change. Speaking of which, my backpack, dear backpack I’ve had for five years, it’s zipper isn’t zipping anymore. I tried to fix it myself a few times, but I think she really needs a tailor to fix her teeth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The tarpaulin being set with just one corner pegged high creates a natural flow path of water draining into my bag of washing. Cold wash, eight hour setting. I think there’s been a powercut - the internet is down. I snuggle into my sleeping bag, accompanied by my notebook.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;monday-16th-october&quot;&gt;Monday 16th October&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The storm has passed, and all is fine. Rupert turned up at 5am smelling suspiciously like fish. Both tents had gotten a little damp last night, but they’ll make do for the rest of the trip.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Joe has to go back to Tirana to stay with Ebony. Zak and I, we’re planning our next moves - bolt it down south to the next city, camp in some cool places along the way. We want to leave this city, but eventually accept that a short detour back to Tirana might be in order - if not to see Ebony then at least for a few needed supplies and adjustments.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;\assets\images\cycle1\cycle1_byerupee.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;cycle1_byerupee&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Goodbye Ruby.&lt;/figcaption&gt;

          </description>
          <pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
          <link>http://localhost:4000/An-Albanian-Cycle-Tour-Week-One.html</link>
          <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/An-Albanian-Cycle-Tour-Week-One.html</guid>
          
          
        </item>
      
    
      
        <item>
          
            <title>Audio Recordings Transcribed</title>
          
          <author>fakeemail@gmail.com (Kauri's BS)</author>
          <description>
            &lt;h5 id=&quot;plan-to-get-arrested-again&quot;&gt;PLAN TO GET ARRESTED AGAIN&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I reckon I could get arrested on false charges pretty easily.
I’ll orepare for it. I’ll talk to my girlfriend and explain everything.
I’ll let Petrin know or just have him on speed dial&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ll record all the audio. Connect in my AirPods, put one in my pocket, one in my backpack.
Figure out how to use them as dual microphones.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ll walk past a police officer and discreetly flash the snus.
Pop one in my mouth when they see me.
Notice them, and freak out, stuff it down my pants, act scared as fuck.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Maybe go for a run first, get all sweaty for them, make them search me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think some of the police officers just didn’t know what it was.
I don’t know what I’ll say. I’ll just, like, not explain it what it was.
Just insult cops and shit. Make it as unpleasant as you can.
Make them never even realize what it is.
They’ll find what, thirty grams of “cocaine”.
Make them think I’ve got serious distribution levels.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They just take you to jail.
Go back and sit with Officer Kola again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now I’ve got experience.
I’m like, a hardened criminal
There’s just one flaw with the plan.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This time they might take my fucking organs.
By the time the fucking New Zealand Embassy gets word, 
I’ve got no liver anymore.
Transplant in me the heart of some 70 year old chainsmoker.
Good trade!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;part-1m4a&quot;&gt;Part 1.m4a&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am the police. Okay?
Is there a problem?
Yeah.
And we talk about it a little bit.
And he says, what is in your bag?
Yeah.
And I was thinking, like, in my bag?
Okay.
I’ve got my laptop and my phone and my
charger and my cables and I’ve got my Toggs
because I’m from New Zealand, I just always carry
my and like, I’ve got empty bottle of water.
Just random shit in my and thinking like, what
the fuck are you trying to search me for?
Is this legal?
And I asked him, Do I have to consent to this?
Why are you doing this?
Do I have to say yes?
And I ask I can’t remember.
Anyway, for context, he’s like,
standing almost over me. Okay. Yeah.
And I can see his friend has come
and his friend is, like, standing very nearby.
Okay.
I don’t want them to touch my shit.
Look, I don’t have actually, I wasn’t smiling at all.
I’m just like, what the fuck is this?
This is my attitude.
Yeah, this is bullshit.
What are we doing?
And like annoyed and angry and
a little bit probably non compliant.
I’m not happy with this and I don’t know why.
The front pocket of my backpack was
also unload and pulls out my container. You know what?
Smooth?
Yeah, of course.
But that’s not illegal, right?
No, it’s not.
Inside the smooth, there’s something else.
He’s, like, pulling at the container.
They can be difficult for pulling at it. Twisting.
Yeah, twisting.
Just pop the top open. Okay.
And then there’s three empty pouches.
And he looks at me.
What is this?
Smooth?
Nicotine.
What else?
Cocaine.
Because there is in the bags.
Fucking yeah.
They have never seen it before. Okay.
You can buy it. Yeah.
And this is smooth.
This is legal nicotine tobacco.
You can buy this.
It’s completely legal. Yeah.
And he passes it to his buddy.
Okay, so more police officers are coming around.
Two more police officers kind of join in.
So they must have just been working, right? Next. Yeah.
And okay, I pull it up on my phone.
I pull up first depiction.
I’m like, here’s a picture.
Wait 1 minute.
I go to Google Translator.
I pull up a web page in Albanian albanian
language that explains what is what is this?
And they’re just giving me shit.
The officer starts, like, prying.
He starts trying the case again.
And he’s struggling, and he’s struggling.
And he pops it open.
Half a gram of marijuana.
Fucking jackpoto.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Okay, so then they start
really giving really hard time.
Yeah, because it’s legal here, but
everyone does it really ridiculous.
And so where did you buy that?
I shut the not saying anything else.
I realize I’m probably in trouble. Yeah. You heard.
And I’m like thinking this internal monologue,
like, what the fuck is going on?
Yeah, actually, I call my girlfriend and for
26 seconds we’re on the phone, but in
this time you can’t understand anything that’s going.
Yeah, because the connections aren’t leaving.
Yeah, okay.
I managed to call her again for a few minutes
and okay, I kind of explained to her cocaine.
We read a little bit about Albania.
I guess everybody knows Albania is
like a fucking grew up country.
Yeah, they kicked me off my phone. Right.
You can’t talk.
So my girlfriend Lucy and I think we’re
both kind of thinking the same thing.
What the fuck is going on?
Are these guys the police?
Why on earth are they stopping me?
I’m literally probably the best
dressed person in Tirana.
And you’re giving big trouble.
Are they actually the police or are they the mafia?
Yeah, scammers or scammers.
And if they are the police, why
the fuck are they arresting me?
What, do they want out?
Am I supposed to bribe them?
How much money do I have to give to €20? €50?
Like, I don’t know.
Yeah, and they’re trying to
fucking extort me, aren’t they?
Well, they’re going to take all my shit.
Either that or they’re trying to extort me.
What is going on out there?
Okay, so they take me to the police station.
They put me in handcuffs, take me in a
police car and take me to the police station.
Fucking Christ.
Okay, this was at 1145.
I hung up in the call with my
girlfriend and they took me fucking Christ.
11:45 P.m.
Sitting down in the jail.
So, for context, it’s like a long hallway, maybe
15 meters long, a couple of meters wide, all
white concrete, fucking ugly, like, not even a painting.
And they set me down at a
desk in the middle of this hallway.
One officer on my right, kind of towards
the door and me on the left.
And then the entire evening, between five and
seven officers are kind of floating around.
Some of them, I don’t know what the fuck they’re doing.
Apparently they’re working.
And so the story is so far from over, my friend.
Okay.
So they sent me down and they’re asking
me questions, giving me a hard time.
And I’m not saying much.
I answer some basic questions.
I’m just not saying anything about the drugs.
I’m telling them about this mess.
Actually, we’re talking about the snooze legal.
Yeah.
Fighting stupid police.
Yeah, exactly.
No, we have to take it to the left.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can actually but you can actually see what is madeof in the back of the fucking of the fucking container.You can see what is made of,like fucking stupid fucking hate them. Right?To be fair, it was in a different language.
The container.It seems like I’m translatedthis fucking fucking christ.Yeah, whatever.It I call my girlfriend again.They actually let me while they’re all trying to talk tome and the other officers taking down my so I callmy girlfriend and sorry, I call my girlfriend and this timeI think it was like five minutes long.I get to explain the situation.We’re talking like, what do we do?I’ve messaged my sister as well, and anotherfriend, and I tell her that the otherfriend I shouldn’t have even messaged her anyway.
I say, like, talk to my sister, talk to her boyfriend.You have to call the empathy inthat case for the lawyer, maybe. Yeah.And I’m like, yeah, you guys will work it out together.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think you need to call me a lawyer.Yeah, stuff like that.At some point, I actually gift him thephone so she can understand it, and sheasks good questions like, who are you?What’s your name?Where is he?Yeah, stuff like that.Clever girl.Okay.They kicked me off the phone&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;.The last phone call, that was the last time Ispoke to anybody, and that was at twelve two. Okay.That was 15 minutes after 17 minutesafter I first called my girlfriend.They wouldn’t let me use the phone, so Iput my water bottle on the table and Isaid, can you fill this up to me?No, you can’t drink the water in this building.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I can’t okay.We’re still talking about this is I’mkind of mixing up with times. Exactly. That’s okay.No worries.At some point, he’s reminding me we have to take it to thelab to test it for you have to take this what lab?Like, where are you taking this to?You don’t even have a fucking lab.Like, you don’t even have running water.Come on.You’re going to take this as a laboratory?Come on.Um what else? What else?I can say.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You’ve call your girlfriend?Yes, I call my girlfriend.After that, what else happens?Oh, they search my bag.This is the yeah.So they asked to see inside my bag again to be sure.Start taking out all this junk again.I got nothing else.I’m also very nervous about them touching my stuff becauseI still think they’re trying to steal my shit.So I pull it all out of my bag, like, everythingdown to down to the bottle cap in my bag.I pull out my headphones.I pull out a second pair of headphonesand then the box and then the receipt.I’m like, yeah, look, I went shopping today.Um what else?Oh, yeah, I pull out my I pullout my wallet, not for the first time.I pull out all these tissue papersfrom the front of my bag.I pull out some tissue papers, and thenI pull out more tissue papers, and Ipull out a larger wad of tissue papers.And I say to them, like, yeah, you never know if atoilet in Tizard is going to have toilet paper or not.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s oh, man.And then did he let you go? No. Wait.Story is no anime.And one of the officers goes to pick atthe toilet paper and see nothing’s inside it.And I take the toilet paper, like,all over the table for it’s actually.Fine.How tired are you?No, you continue.Put this bitter because I don’t want to damage it.No, I won’t smoke another one.I will sleep here.Okay.So they spread the toilet paper. I think.I just try to think because I havean order and I don’t want to forgetanything else that happened at the police station.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first police station.Spoiler alert.Well, this is yeah, okay.I can’t think of anything else.So they say, yeah, we have totake you to the next station.You’re going to be there for 20 minutes, andyou’ll meet with the police officer and you discussthis, and you have to sign some documents.20 minutes?Yeah, fuck off. Yeah, right. Yeah.Bullshit.So take me they take me in another policecar for me and have a couple of nights.They take me to jail standing in front of thislarge building and can see the jailer in the distance.And I’m, like, trying to talk tohim, like, hey, this is fucking bullshit.They fucking got me for, like, nothing.Like, what is going on here?I need to speak to my lawyer.I need to use the phone.I need to speak to my lawyer. And I’m giving, like, bro, canpolice I’m just gonna pause this.Wait one moment because.
&lt;strong&gt;__&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;__&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;__&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;__&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;__&lt;/strong&gt;___&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;part-2m4a&quot;&gt;Part 2.m4a&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&quot;part-2m4a-1&quot;&gt;Part 2.m4a&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&quot;part-2m4a-2&quot;&gt;Part 2.m4a&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&quot;part-2m4a-3&quot;&gt;Part 2.m4a&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I should retell that joke for the audio. I don’t remember. I remember where it is. I really like this frame of telling. So part two is titled Jail. So I’ve just met the warden, okay? They take me behind bars.They’ve got my phone, they’ve got myspace, and I’ve got everything else.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Everything’s kind of all mixed through my backpackby now because I’ve been searched twice.Um, and okay, they’re talking, and they hand oversome papers, like the you know how, like, youwrite on paper and there’s one underneath?And what do you call this?I’ll search up what it’s called.They hand in the copies, and he takes me in.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They close a big bar window bar metal door on us.And okay, the warden wants to search me, so standup like this, and he gets in behind me, andthe four officers behind the door are watching.Yeah, you like that?What do you want to find?I’ve got my glasses there.I’ve got my ear pods earbuds in my pocketbecause I was trying to do some sneaky shitwith the audio, but it didn’t work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Didn’t work out.Um and then he goes to search my bag, searches,and he looks a little bit and then he pullsup my laptop, and he’s like, what the fuck?There’s a laptop in here?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He’s saying, there’s an opening I can understand.And the police, what the fuck?How did he get a laptop in there?You were supposed to have searched him.How did you miss, like, the biggest thing in his bag?You know, because I did it all myself.I did it all myself, okay?When I take out the stuff for my bagfor them to see they’re not touching my bag.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hide this from he takes it out again, gives it to them.Oh, before this, I forgot to say before, they’d,like, completely they wanted to take my handcuffs off,and they closed the metal door on us already.And I put my hands the officer takes a cuff off, okay?And then he takes the second one.He tries to take the second one off for, like,half a minute while his police officers are standing aroundlike, what the fuck are you doing, bro?Just unlock it.This I can understand as well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In Albanian.Okay.So he takes me to the same like, aboat, and he takes me to the cell.And then there I meet a couple ofyoung guys, albanians, locals, and they tell me,yeah, these guys are the fucking Mafia.They just do what they want, you know?Um so the the first guy, he waspicked up he was picked up outside hisapartment, right outside his home, okay?And the second guy I can’t remember exactly why.Try this.I don’t know exactly why.I don’t know exactly the context in whichhe was arrested, but he was also forthe same just a little bit of marijuana.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He’s a fucking lawyer, okay?I’m going to be fine.They tell me like, yeah, you’re going to be fine.You’re going to walk out of here in the morning.You’re not even going to get a fine.Yeah, they’re not going to steal your shit.I can relax.Well, this isn’t completely true.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I can’t relax because my girlfriend thinks I’ve beenkidnapped by fucking Mafia guilt, but also just concernfor her because I realized, okay, I’m going tobe in here for a while. This entire time, she’s going to be exactly.And she’s going to be reading and calling and figuring outwhat the fuck is going on until I get out.Until the moment I get out, she’s goingto be working on this, you know?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh, I’m really glad I’m recording this audio.This is a beautiful way to describe it.I want to write this stuff.Where are we?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Okay, so meet the guys.We chat. Chat.And the water pokes his head through the door.It’s got a metal grille, like, window. Yes.Sounds like you’ve been in one before.Another story.Okay, yeah.So the water pokes his head around thewindow, and he asked me some question.The lawyer is translating for us.He wants to know, how do you spell my name, stupid?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yeah.Oh, my God. Sorry.I spell it for him.He can’t really understand me.Give us the pen and paper to thelawyer, and I spell my name for him.K-A-R-U-I.This is spelt wrong switch. Two letters.What a fuck.Not I did the same thing with my last name.But this is ridiculous because the lawyers,they’re, like, writing on the door, andhe’s kind of struggling to understand me.I’m not being so clear in the water.Like, come, come to the office.Sit down facing the door.And the lawyer sits in front of theledger, the entire, like, police jail ledger.And how fucking thick is that book, bro, I told you.And he sits down next to the lawyer, andI tell the lawyer, again, my name wrong.Again my date of birth, wrong.And my dad’s name, like, completely wrong.And then there’s more things thatI don’t need to fill out.I don’t need to tell him.But the warden starts, like, telling him what to write.Warden’s telling the lawyer what to write.It’s a beautiful metaphor.And I asked for some water, and heproduces a small bottle of water for me.And, oh, I will say one thing I forgotat the first police station, they also offered mea bottle of water, but only one.And I ask, how much is the other one?And they say that the Mini Martyrs closed it stupid.So I just had to put.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do this.
So the water produces a small bottle of water for me,
and I drink the water, and he offers me a cigarette.
Yeah, I think I’m making a mistake.
I think he had more trouble
getting the water than I recall.
Anyway, where are we?
He offers us water and cigarettes, and we sit and chat
for a little bit, and this time, I take my channel.
Okay.
And we go and sit in there, and
we go and sit in the cell again.
There’s nothing but tidying. Good company.
So I’m writing, and we’re speaking a
lot about all sorts of different topics,
but especially the situation in Albania.
And they tell me about the historical context.
I don’t remember it somewhere, but I wrote it all down.
And they remind me they tell me of the following.
Wow, I’m struggling with my history.
I think if I’m not high, I can recall history.
Anyway, recent political history and how it
relates to corruption and policing, the judicial
system, how it has this today.
They say, like, yes, it used to be very
visibly corrupt, and now you just can’t see it.
What else have we got?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And at some point, they take one
of the guys to be processed.
Later, they take the other.
Not yet. They don’t take the other. Yet.
They take one, and we keep shutting, and
then there’s a lot of noise and commotion.
It’s been quiet, like, the entire time now.
There’s a lot of noise and commotion outside, and we kind
of stick our heads through and see what’s going on.
The lawyer is translating again for me, and
he’s listening, and he explains, yeah, this group
of twelve illegal immigrants has been detained.
So the warden comes, and he calls us into
his office, and he comes a he comes there.
He can’t have a separate and I understand, okay,
he’s taken away taken us away from the Brim
because it’s going to be occupied, and I guess
he took some liking to us.
We chatted with him a lot, and okay, we finished
this story about corruption in Albania with the police officer
concluding, like, no, I never took bribes in my life.
Like, 60 years old.
Like, what else?
And they take the other the
other guy away to be processed.
And I ask the officer if that comes.
I need to speak to my girlfriend again.
This is the first time I’ve seen, like, anybody else
official, so I need to speak to my girlfriend.
I need this I need to speak to my lawyer.
Oh, sorry.
I don’t say, I need to speak to my lawyer.
Of course not.
And no, you can’t use it in front of you.
That was at 04:00 A.m..
And the warden lets me, like, sit and write in
his office, and we try and communicate with each other.
He’s giving me cigarettes, and he gets me water.
That privilege cost me €9.
Okay. Shall I leave? Good story.
There it’s getting late and there’s still a third part.
Is the third part it?
Yeah, reasonably.
We can leave it for tomorrow.
No, I put forward and I keep going if you want it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;part-3m4a&quot;&gt;Part 3.m4a&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&quot;part-3m4a-1&quot;&gt;Part 3.m4a&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&quot;part-3m4a-2&quot;&gt;Part 3.m4a&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&quot;part-3m4a-3&quot;&gt;Part 3.m4a&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just sure.Yeah.So we’re at part three, endinga waste of everybody’s time.Oh, God, take me to the to meet that police officer.And he’s sitting in a room.It he’s got his disc and he’s like, inone corner, there’s a disc in the other corner.The room with a printer on it.Bookshelves over the fuck is this arrangement?Dog bars each other.It’s like so granddaddish.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Okay, fine. I’m not surprised.I’m not surprised, but it’s funny nonetheless.And okay.And they communicate and I hear like, New Zealand.And the guy’s like, nah, next onedon’t even know you’re taking me.Take me to the next room.And guy calls me in.It fucking you from the narcotics development.I’m like, yeah, of course.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fucking offer the cola.Look at you, bro.I didn’t say that.I didn’t say that.Broad chirp chirping 10:00.Where am I going?Thinks I’ll be kidnapped for the budy love 10 hours.Fuck are you doing?Fucking mega focal. Fuck you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I asked to charge it.If I can’t fucking send a message, atleast let me fucking charge it because I’mgoing to have to leave anyway.Charge my phone.And as I’m charging, I’m like, fucking andI read my messages from my girlfriend.The New Zealand embassy in Romegot me a fucking lawyer.When I say got me a lawyer, theygave me a name and a number.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yeah.And I should have fucking called it. No, sorry.It’s because they gave me a list of numbers. Okay?Yeah, sorry.It wasn’t just a name and a number.Because they gave me a list.I’m just like, what the fuck?They don’t even know, you know?Um anyways, asking me questions holdsup and say, what is this?Like, why did you sit it to the fucking lab?You know?Fuck with it.I know what this is.Anybody can find out with aquick Google search what this is.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fuck your cops accusing me of having cocaine.I don’t ask them this.I don’t ask him this yet because I don’twant to talk about cocaine with my lawyer.And you don’t want to be beaten up. Exactly.It’s like, okay, tell her heals of the marijuana.What is this?I don’t understand.And fuck my license translator.I don’t understand what you’re saying.We don’t need a translator.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why are you telling me?I waited till like, 10:00 in themorning for a lizard to strange.Where’s my login?5 minutes away.Yeah, 5 minutes.It was like 15.And he takes my passport and he’s liketypically he’s like, what are you doing here?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t understand English.I don’t understand English.It’s eventually the lawyer comes andhe tells me, yeah, it’s fine.The police officer told me the same thing before.Basically it’s so little amounted it doesn’t matter.You just say it’s for personal consumption.Then they can’t do shit.If it’s just for personal consumption anyway.You’re fucking tourists.Like, they don’t really want to then.We’re not trying to get you anyway.What the fuck do you mean?You’re the best dress person in Tirada. Like what?It started recording this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve got some bangers of I don’t know if they fitin the story that I have to change the once Itake out the swear words, it’s a little bit less funny.I don’t mind swearing, but where am I?You’ll be right, okay.We go back to the go back to the officer.And I complained to him aboutall the issues that I’ve had.He’s quite a serious officer. What the fuck is going on?This is ridiculous.I’m just going to get over fucking stupid.The cops stupid.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They know each other.He doesn’t want to be doing this to you.He just has to follow the perception.Later we discuss, like, why the fuck did your copseven bother picking me up then if they they knowI’m just going to get the go in the morning.What the fuck is the whole point ofthis is a waste of everybody’s time.I’ve got six police officers in the field using halfan hour of their time on average to arrest meand then two to take me to the station.Bloody police car.Two police cars.And when I’m sitting at that table, like zebbing peoplearound me, I’m like, half a gram of weed.And like, in that room, we all knew it’s. Nicotine.That’s the thing.They’re giving me shit.They’re trying to intimidate me.I realized this, like, halfway through.I’m like, bro, they’re just fucking like oh, my God.In the police report.In the police report? Yeah.Suspected, Nicotine.Suspected. Fuck.You 5 minutes away.Fucking fucking suspected.Coffee?Yeah, okay.With my lawyer, I start to answer some questions.I’m going to dentist, bro.Of course I want to smoke some weed.You just legalized, like, medicinalmarijuana and your government’s like.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Prints.
Like, I don’t know.
There’s major talk about overhauling making it legal.
Lost my train of thought.
He eventually prints out, like, the kicks back, and
he prints out, like, 18 pages of documentation.
I’m like what?
The printer is so slow and noisy.
We literally order a coffee.
We get the coffee before the printer’s done.
Anyway, 18 pages on each page, the first two,
and, like, the header, the first two paragraphs, like,
identical, except sometimes it’s, like, formatting differences.
Why the fuck are you putting so much paper?
Why don’t you just follow them all along?
Each one’s like, oh, I have
to accept all these different anyway.
They make me accept all this different shit.
I refuse to accept.
I accept like, okay, I’ll give you
my what do I have to accept?
I’ll give you my sorry, lost my train of thought.
What was I talking about?
Printer 18 pages of the ad.
Okay?
So I don’t sign one of them.
This one, I sign that.
They can test my piss in the content.
And the lawyers like, even if you come back
positive, fuck, you know, they can’t do shit.
What is the point of this?
I sign this. I sign this.
I refuse to take a Pacific Cup.
I just write reviews on it.
They still make me take a Pacific up, right?
And I don’t care.
I’m happy to take a Pacific and I piss in it.
And I flipped to the premise.
I mean, I tightened up tight, wash hands, because I
put some and I walk outside holding a plastic bag
for me to put it in and hold it up,
put it on the ground and start shaking my head.
Bro, the the police officer that
was, like, taking my details.
I never saw him smile, and he was laughing his ass off.
He gave me his phone number.
Call me about anything.
It doesn’t have to be related to the case.
Coming back to wasting all the police officers time.
How many police officers I’m wasting everybody’s time.
Like, your police officer arrested knows that
nothing is going to happen to me.
It’s just a little weed.
Why they why are they bothering to arrest me?
If they find weed on you, they have to arrest you.
This is the procedure, right?
What?
Just change fucking procedure then.
What are you doing?
All you have to do is change two words.
Make it a 50 year fine or something.
Um, and yes, there’s so many police
officers around at each stage, and then
now I’m wasting these police officers time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m not paying this fucking lawyer.
What did you do?
You just told me to do exactly
what the police told me to do.
That I would have done if I was by myself.
Anyway, bro, obviously I can understand
this makes perfectly reasonable sense.
I probably want to see a bit of proof, but
if I can just say it for personal use. Okay? Fuck.
I don’t fucking need a lawyer to tell me this.
I draw my lawyer, ask him
everything, but he’s not getting paid.
I don’t know how he gets paid.
So I understand he doesn’t want to be there any longer.
But, I mean, he was nice.
He was nice and answered my question. Yeah.
The police have to follow them because women
going through these papers this is so stupid.
And he tells me I lost my train of thought.
Anyway, so the lawyer, we went out for coffee
afterwards and coming back to waste of everybody time,
they have to send these 18 pages.
Every page is the half the
same to the prosecution office.
Somebody has to read that shit.
Your police officers accusing me of cocaine
in addition, what the fuck, bro?
And then on my side, whatever, it’s
fine, but I impact other people.
My girlfriend for 10 hours thinks I’m kidnapped
and she’s called the New Zealand emphasis rope.
I told you this already, didn’t I?
Okay, sorry.
And got emails from the embassy.
So they’ve spent time in this as well.
And they’re, like, all of us tried to
contact the police, the jail cell, you’re in
the headquarters and nobody picked up.
And they all were trying again and again.
Bro, you felt like, all these
police and nobody can pick up.
A seriously?
Seriously?
Um, yeah.
So my sister wasted a time.
My embassy wasted time.
Other people, my sister and
girlfriend, both of us, actually.
My sister fell asleep right
before she ignored my messages.
And then her phone went on.
Do not disturb.
And then with a gap of, like,
three minutes, I checked all the books.
Her phone went on.
Do not disturb.
And I called her and she
just didn’t, like doesn’t hear anything.
Hey, how are you?
So head.
Do not disturb.
Fucked up.
Fucked her because I played mini grudge.
She wasn’t there for my girlfriend seven or 8 hours.
My girlfriend was alone.
I was alone, but I knew I was going to be fine.
She didn’t know this.
They didn’t communicate. Shit.
She can’t call the police.
Of course she’s going to tear up.
And then Albania.
And she’s, like, talking to people.
She gets in contact with different Albanian people.
She gets in contact with one Albanian.
My sister boyfriend gets in
contact with somebody from Montenegro.
Kind of explained.
Yeah, it was, like kind of helped out
and helped made them assured, didn’t it?
It’s probably fine. Yeah.
So, yeah, it’s a big fucking waste of time.
It’s such a waste of resources.
What half a gram of weed but half a joint?
Women like threat.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your bleed up having to pay anything much.
No, I didn’t pay anything.
I thought I was going to get fine.
Yeah, that’s the thing.
It’s not even a fine.
You wasted probably hundreds of dollars
in, like, man hours for this.
Why don’t they when they just put a winning Euro fight?
I tried to break so many dice.
It’s a win win for everyone.
You guys save time, you save money.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s the problem with corruption is sometimes
it’s effective and you got broken systems
can be a necessary tool.
Nice experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can tell your grandkids I enjoyed it.
Yeah, good fun.
You can say you got arrested in Albania,
you spent tonight in Albanian jail cell.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There’s no good way to shorten that story, really.
It’s all the details.
That inner ada, the intricacies of
the Albanian police department inner workings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When are you going to tell your parents this?
Probably I’m going to publish it.
I’ve got a lot of working drafts
that I just need to flesh out.
Then I can actually put together semi funny blog.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ll just backdate it. I don’t know.
Is that like, internet ethically acceptable?
According to the internet to backdate stuff, to just say
it was published like six months ago if it wasn’t?
Because I’ve finished the story six months ago.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And that’s to me what’s important.
I just don’t have a place to publish it, you know? Yeah.
All it takes is a Google search.
They’re not going to fuck with you at the airport.
They might give you a little bit of a
hard time, but in theory it’s possible, right?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Theory it’s possible.
The officer sees he doesn’t like it and the
two officers around him like, yeah, fuck this guy.
Like we racially profiled.
Exactly.
Like, I’m like, I mean, it’s only two.
I’m not I don’t even want throw in bombs.
Be like, I’m going to take it home.
Be like, fuck you guys.
What are you going to do about it?
Two pouches of tobacco.
Can you not buy it there or it’s just cheaper.
What do you mean?
You’re bringing it home? Why? To Australia?
Because yeah, it’s illegal.
Okay, yeah, that’s stupid.
That doesn’t really like, Sweden’s got one
of the lowest smoking rates in the
world because they just sold these.
They banned vaping as well.
Selling vapes and whatnot.
You can buy a pack of sigs for like,
$50, but anything else like that is illegal.
So, like, you’re just forcing people the thing
is, they have nicotine gum in the pharmacy.
Nicotine gum for probably free $5.03.
Yeah, but shall we at least the like the tobacco free?
That and nicotine pouch that has like this
I don’t know how these laws get passed.
Illegal to selling like, everywhere in the EU.
Except it’s not true.
I’ve ordered in Montana.
Sweden’s the only one I know.
Germany’s kind of fluctuated with its laws.
Yeah, Sweden’s the only country.
Seriously? Yeah.
No, I bought it in Croatia. Wait.
Did I seriously?
How didn’t I buy it in Croatia?
Trying to calculate now.
Then I must have bought it in Hungary.
Or I mustn’t I didn’t buy it in Hungary.
I couldn’t have sworn the same
when I bought it somewhere.
All that to say, credible evidence that you’re wrong.
My apologies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No, it&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They didn’t even take a picture of my passport.
The fuck don’t even know who you are anymore.
They just wrote it all down on the paper.
The water couldn’t read it.
He called in one of my mates from the
jail cell, the lawyer, to help to write down
the name, called us into his office, like Karuibock.
And I spelled wrong, like, just.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wrong.
Like, just a little wrong way.
I don’t think you’ll find me with that name. Really?
I know this doesn’t matter.
This is just a literate job. Doesn’t matter.
They’ve already gone and given my date of birth wrong.
My dad’s name wrong.
Just, like, slightly wrong. My dad’s name.
I just make up.
I never told them. They asked me.
I’m like no, I’m not telling you.
Anyway, what was I talking about before? The water?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&quot;parts-12m4a&quot;&gt;Parts 1&amp;amp;2.m4a&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&quot;asdf&quot;&gt;asdf&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&quot;345a&quot;&gt;345a&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&quot;asdf-1&quot;&gt;asdf&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Okay.
The day I rode with, like, a diplomat from
the Netherlands who’s working in Serbia to improve the
rule of law in the west Balkans.
And he’s told me about the West Balkans in
general, about history and about Albania as well.
He was told me about the
corruption in the judiciary system.
And this is one of the
big problems these countries have.
And he tells me about the police and how
historically they’ve been corrupted, involved in extortion and bribery
and tell me something I don’t know.
Yeah, and like, organ trades, I’m like, Yo, dude,
the police were involved in the organ trade.
I’m shitting myself.
What the fuck?
I’m just sitting here, right?
But okay, I don’t want them to search my
bag, but I start to take some things out.
I don’t have shit.
I obviously have shit, but I take out, like,
look, I’ve got my tote bag, I’ve got my
shorts, I’ve got my water bottle, my water bottle.
I’ve got this half can of Pringles.
I give it to him and he pours
it on the ground like, what the fuck?
I take out this stuff from the main compartment
of my bag and just like, random junk.
And somehow the front hi, mate.
Somehow the front pocket of my bag was open.
I don’t remember why, but he just picks it
up, my Snoop’s container, and I’m like, fuck, I
wasn’t going to take this out for him.
Fuck, I was high at the time,
but I don’t think it okay.
I was more paranoid, but I don’t
think they knew I was high.
He takes my snakes container and he starts,
like, pulling at it, twisting at it.
This fucker can’t open it, doesn’t know how to open it.
Looking at him like, bro, this is snooze Nicotine.
Legal.
You can see the package and he just can’t open it.
You have to pry.
He’s like this big, muscular
dude, like, hard, tough case.
He’s working the streets of Tirada
and he can’t open the snooze.
So I take it off and I’m like, look.
And I just popped the top flap open.
I should have struggled and made it
really hard to pop the top flap.
But I pop it open and there’s
sitting three empty pouches of snooze.
And he looks at it and
I’m like, look, snoots legal, Nicotine.
He’s like cocaine.
Okay.
I’m like, bro, I don’t know.
What are you on?
Some more officers start to arrive and they start passing
it around and I can’t understand anything, but they’re talking
to each other like, go gain, go gain.
So I explained to him, like, look, this is legal nicotine,
and you can buy this in the stores in Tirana.
And I explain a little bit about the product.
We have to take this to the lab to test it.
So I pull up on my phone pictures of
this, and I go to Google Translate and I
find a website that explains what this is in
Albania and it explains it’s legal in Albania.
And go, game.
We have to take this to the he
closes it’s like he completely forgot about it.
But he closes the lid, they pick it open and the
white powder falls out because this is what smooth is.
It’s the white powder and little
sachets, like a tea bag.
Why would you ever put it in a Sasha?
And he starts prying and he
starts pulling and twisting again.
And he finally, like, tears it open later in the
police station, like, when I saw this loose container, it
had been, like, half destroyed because they could I guess
they had trouble opening it again, you know?
Um and then there’s, like, my marijuana fucking jackpot half
a grab and okay, now I shut the fuck up.
Asking me a question.
Where did you buy this? Who did you get that?
You get this here in Tirana?
I don’t say shit. What are you doing here?
I don’t say shit.
I think at some point, okay, so I call my
girlfriend and I’m like, what the fuck is going on?
They let me on the phone for like, 20
seconds and there’s like a mumble, what the fuck?
I send her some freaked out messages.
First I need mum, dad, lawyer.
What the fuck is going on?
I need Dom.
My sister’s boyfriend is from Greece.
So I thought maybe if I messaged
my sister as well this fucking girl.
This fucking girl.
She hears my messages and then her phone goes on.
Do not disturb.
And then I call her.
So she’s fast asleep.
She’s fast asleep during this entire ordeal.
So my girlfriend’s there my girlfriend calls me back.
She’s like, hey, what is going on?
They let me on the phone for, like,
20 seconds and it’s like mumbled Chumble.
Okay, I get another few minutes.
I get another minute on the phone, but it’s
chaos and she doesn’t know what’s going on, really.
And both of us are thinking like,
dude, how fucking corrupt is this shit?
Wait, I read you my internal monologue.
I’m going to pull it up
because I’ve written it quite nicely.
Okay?
So my internal monologue what am I supposed to do?
Bribe these guys?
How much do I bribe them?
20 euro census, 50 euro. $200.
That’s a lot of money. Shit. I might have told them I’m
in Tirana to see the dentist.
I’m sure it’s way too nicely.
They think you have money.
This is going to turn into an extortion case, isn’t it?
At least it’s not the Mafia, right?
Why did you decide to wear your only shirt today?
Why did you come here with all your volleyballs?
You’ve been working on your laptop all day and you
were just on the phone with your girlfriend lucia.
Lucia.
Lucia.
Lucia and my sister Jade both
received a flurry of crystals.
They kicked me off the phone with my girlfriend, okay?
They take me to the police.
They put me in cuffs.
I’m still wearing my bag on my front.
And they put me in cuffs.
I don’t want them to touch my shit, right?
They take me to the police station and they uncuff me.
Sit me down at a desk in a rather empty hallway.
Middle of a hallway.
I sit down here’s.
The hallway here’s the desk.
The doors over there, I can see.
They sit me at the desk.
Here another officer here,
officers standing all around.
The officer here is filling out some paperwork.
And the officer here is questioning me.
And the officers there, one of them
is the one that arrested me.
Or that who approached me, giving me shit. Cocaine.
Cocaine.
Marijuana.
Have to send it to the left.
Okay?
In one corner, there’s a security camera. I’m like.
Is that on?
Yeah, it’s on. It’s on.
Security camera. Fuck off.
It’s not on. It’s not moving.
It’s one of these, like, silver. It’s never moved.
I never see it move.
It I don’t see a red light. This isn’t fucking on.
Fuck you.
I put my water bottle on the table.
I need some water.
No, you can’t drink the water in this.
Okay, where are we?
And they’re asking me questions.
And I don’t say shit anymore.
Saying, okay, this is legal machine.
I don’t know what the fuck this is.
Trying to think what else happens.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Where are we?
And they ask me questions and I don’t say shit anymore.
This is legal thing.
This one. I call Mr.
Illiterate because he’s so slow at writing.
So slow.
The one asking me questions, call him Officer
13565 because he won’t tell me his name.
Oh, yes. Okay.
So I’m sitting down there asking some
questions, and I call my girlfriend again.
The first time I called my girlfriend
was at 1145 in the park.
The last time I called anybody,
my girlfriend at twelve 02:00 a.m..
And this phone call lasts six minutes.
And we only talk three of them.
This time we’re properly able
to discuss what’s going on.
Is she in New Zealand or is she in Toronto?
San Francisco, actually.
Kind of.
My memory is saying that she spoke
to the officer at like, ten.
She’s giving me a full description.
She talked to one of the police officers.
This is police station number three.
We’re going to send it to the
lab to test it for cocaine. He has marijuana.
He’s going to jail.
And then we end up hanging up.
Give me a fucking lawyer.
And the police officer’s like, you bring me a
lawyer here at this time, no lawyer coming.
Fucking hell.
Get in contact with my sister, with her boyfriend.
Jesus Christ.
Mr.
Illiterate slowly fills out.
He takes a break and offers me his finger.
He asked me the OD question.
I refuse to tell him.
My father by now I’m thinking, we all know this.
I realize I only care about
marijuana and they’re using cocaine.
My son is going nuts on the cane.
They won’t let me.
They also search my bag again.
They also search my bag again.
Wait, is it too far in? Can you fill me in? Like really?
Yeah, I’ll fill you in really quickly.
So I was out at the open Air concert, relaxing
on a plastic couch, writing in maternal pick me up.
Whoa. Okay. Interesting.
We need to search your back.
And I pull the shit out and he
picks out you know what Snooze is, right? Yeah.
And he can’t open it, so I pop it open for him.
Top flat.
They say it’s cocaine.
And then they pass it around. Cocaine. Cocaine.
We have to test it in the lab work or something.
Call my girlfriend 11.58, freaking out.
Finally opens it to find half a gram.
No.
So now we’re in the police
station and I’m not answering questions.
Is this in Albania?
Yeah.
They’re starting to clamp down.
And we’re at the point they’re
asking to touch my package.
Start pulling out of my items, out of my bag. Dictating.
This is my shorts.
This is my headbreaks.
This is a box of headphones I bought today.
Here’s the receipt. Want to see?
Here’s my shopping.
Pull out everything down to the bottle
cap, the shell, the tissue paper.
I pull out more and more tissue paper.
You never know when there’s going to be a fucking when.
The toilet is not going to have to when there’s
going to be toilet paper here in TV right now.
You don’t have any hair.
Wonder how you look. White.
Smells like shit in here.
Paul, they don’t have any
toilet paper in this building.
They shit in a plastic hole in the ground.
Yeah, and Muscle Man, I call him Episode, suspiciously picked
out a clump of toilet paper on the desk.
I spread it all over the desk.
You want to see the fucking toilet paper?
Half an hour of doing that, somebody
hands me a 300 mil bottle.
And I doubt more.
I’m thirsty.
You’re arresting me for drugs?
I might be on drugs.
I’m thirsty.
I already tried to get water from no,
there’s no potable water in this filter.
They get me how much?
How much for another one?
The bug and okay, so Officer 13565, the one who put cuffs
on me, he asked me again, where did you get it from?
And I tell her. Tells him? What do you mean?
I told you already.
This is legal, Nicotine.
You can buy this with the tobacco.
He’s asking about the marijuana.
You must be the only policeman in the
world stupid enough to think this is cocaine.
Tell him.
What do you mean you’re sending this off to the lab?
Sending it to the lab? You don’t have a lab.
You don’t even have running water.
We’ve got to send it.
Where did you buy the marijuana?
I don’t know what you’re talking about.
What is your father’s name?
Why won’t you tell us?
I know it doesn’t matter just for your
report, but I don’t feel like telling me
until you give me back my phone.
They said, who is your father?
They need to know.
I start packing my bag and I’ve expressed them I’m
uncomfortable with them touching my shit once it’s on the
table, but I don’t want you to touch it.
I still don’t know.
I’m still worried they’re going to jack all my shit.
Why am I here for half a gram?
This is ridiculous.
So what do you want from me?
Thinking, are they going to fucking install me?
I think even the police, they
have a nickname in Albania.
They call the police the Mafia.
And my girlfriend, the last time I
called her, I got picked up.
I called her at 1145 in the park.
Last time I talked to her, twelve, 02:00 a.m.
So the entire time, she’s no idea what’s going
they don’t let me use the phone ever again.
Um okay, so they moved me to the they
moved me to the police headquarters and they tell
me, oh, yeah, you’re going to see your lawyer,
you’re going to see a police officer.
You’ll be out of here in an hour.
Yeah, fuck you.
What are you order an hour? Fuck off.
I know this is bullshit.
They introduced me to the jail warden.
He doesn’t speak any English, and
they close the bars on us.
They’ve got my phone and they’ve got my
and they continue to chat and hand the
warden a copy of the police report.
I remind them again, I need to use the phone.
I need to call my lawyer.
I need to call my embassy.
I need to call my girlfriend.
She’s worried that you are the mafia.
It. It.
So the police officer’s partner who they
took me in the police car.
I put my hands back through the
bars, and he starts undoing my shackles.
That he can’t do.
It the.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Trying to think what else is oh yeah.
This one I call Mr.
Illiterate because he’s so slow at writing.
So slow.
The one asking the questions full of officer
13565 because he won’t tell me his name.
It’s his bad.
Oh, yes. Okay.
So I’m sitting down there asking some
questions, and I call my girlfriend again.
The first time I called my girlfriend
was at 1145 in the park.
The last time I called anybody,
my girlfriend at twelve 02:00 a.m..
And this phone call lasts six minutes.
And we only talk for three of them.
This time we’re properly able
to discuss what’s going on.
Is she in New Zealand or is she in Toronto?
San Francisco, actually.
I’ll probably this time we’re properly able to discuss what’s
going she kind of my memory is saying that she
spoke to the officer at, like, ten chaotic.
She’s giving me a full description.
She talks to one of the police officers.
This is police station number three.
We’re going to send it to the lab to test it for coca.
Cocaine. He has marijuana.
He’s going to jail.
And then we end up hanging up.
Get me a fucking lawyer.
Yeah, you bring me a lawyer here
at this time, no lawyer coming.
Fucking hell.
Get in contact with my sister with a boyfriend.
Jesus Christ.
Mr.
Illiterate slowly fills out the police.
He takes a break and offers me his cigarette.
He asked me the OD question.
I refuse to tell him.
My father by now I’m thinking, we all know that.
I realize I only care about
marijuana and they’re using cocaine.
My son is going nuts on this cane.
They won’t let me.
They also search my bag again.
They also search my bag again.
Wait, is it too far in? Can you fill me in? Like really?
Yeah, I’ll fill you in really quickly.
So I was out at the open air concert, relaxing
on a plastic couch, writing in maternal pick me up.
Whoa. Okay. Interesting.
We need to search your back.
And I pulled the shit out, and he
picks out you know what Snooze is, right? Yeah.
And he can’t open it, so I pop it open for him.
Top flat says cocaine.
They say it’s cocaine.
And then they pass it around. Cocaine. Cocaine.
We have to test it in the lab work or something.
Call my girlfriend.
11.58, freaking out, finally opens it to
find half a gram of no.
So now we’re in the police
station and I’m not answering questions.
Is this in Albania? Yes.
They’re starting to clamp down.
And we’re at the point they’re
asking to touch my back again.
Start pulling out of my items, out of my back.
Dictating.
This is my shorts.
This is my head.
This is a box of headphones I bought today.
Here’s the receipt. You want to see?
Here’s my shopping.
Pull up everything down to the bottle
cap, the shell, the tissue paper.
I pull out more and more tissue paper.
You never know when there’s going to be a fucking when.
When the toilet is not going to have to
know when there’s going to be toilet paper.
You don’t have any hair.
Wonder how you look white.
Smells like shit in here.
Paul’s, you fucker.
They don’t have any toilet paper in this building.
They shit in a plastic hole in the ground.
Yeah, and muscle man, I call him the
police officer who stopped me suspiciously suspiciously picked
out a quantum toilet paper on the desk.
I spread it all over the desk.
You want to see the fucking toilet paper?
Half an hour of being there, somebody
hands me a 300 mil bottle.
And I doubt more.
I’m thirsty.
You’re arresting me for drugs?
I might be on drugs.
I’m so I already tried to get water from
no, there’s no potable water in this building.
How much?
How much for another one?
The bug and okay, so officer 13565, the one who put cuffs
on me, he asked me again, where did you get it from?
And I tell her.
Tells him what do you mean? I told you already.
This is legal nicotine.
You can buy this in the tobacco.
He’s asking about the marijuana.
I tell the muscle man, you must be the only policeman
in the world stupid enough to think this is cocaine.
Tell him.
What do you mean you’re sending this off to the lab?
Sending it to the lab? You don’t have a lab.
You don’t even have running water.
We’ve got to send it.
Where did you buy the marijuana?
I don’t know what you talked about.
What is your father’s name?
Why won’t you tell us?
I know it doesn’t matter just for your
report, but I don’t feel like telling me
until you give me back my phone.
They said, who is your father?
They need to know.
I start packing my bag and I’ve expressed them.
I’m uncomfortable touching my shit once it’s on the
table, but I don’t want you to touch it.
I still don’t know.
I’m still worried they’re going to jack all my shit.
Why am I here for half a grand?
This is ridiculous.
So what do you want from me? Thinking?
Are they going to fucking insult me?
Are these even the police?
They have a nickname in Albania.
They call the police the Mafia.
And my girlfriend, the last time I
called her, I got picked up.
I called her at 1145 in the park.
Last time I talked to her, twelve 02:00 a.m.
So the entire time, she’s no idea what’s going on.
They don’t let me use the phone ever again.
Um okay, so they moved me to the they
moved me to the police headquarters and they they
tell me, oh, yeah, you’re gonna see your lawyer.
You’re going to see a police officer.
You’ll be out of here in an hour.
Yeah, fuck you.
What do you order an hour? Fuck off.
I know this is bullshit.
They introduced me to the jail warden.
He doesn’t speak any English.
And they close the files on us.
They’ve got my phone, and they’ve got my
and they continue to chat and hand the
warden a copy of the police report.
I remind them again, I need to use the phone.
I need to call my lawyer.
I need to call my embassy.
I need to call my girlfriend.
She’s worried that you are the mafia.
So the police officer’s partner who they
took me in the police car.
I put my hands back through the bars, and he starts
undoing my shackles that he can’t up to it, police around.
And she’s like, what the fuck is this?
What I’m propsing up against like this.
He starts batting me down against the wall
like this, with four police officers watching.
And he’s, like, patting me down, like, what do you want?
You want my glasses?
I don’t have anything.
And then he searches my bag, and
he rummages around a little bit.
He pulls out my laptop.
He’s like, what the fuck?
You’ve got a laptop this closed this smuggling it.
And he starts yelling at the officers
behind the bars, what the fuck?
And they opened it up, and there’s a laptop.
And they’re just embarrassed, like, quiet.
And I wink. Get this.
And they take my laptop.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cocaine.
My son is going nuts on this camera.
A friend calls, another friend calls.
They won’t let me.
They also search my bag again.
They also search my bag again.
Wait, is it too far in? Can you fill me in?
Like, really?
Yeah, I’ll fill you in really quickly.
So I’ve been I was out at the open Air concert,
relaxing on a plastic couch, writing in maternal pick me up.
Whoa.
Okay, interesting.
We need to search your back.
And I pull the shit out and he
picks out you know what Snooze is, right? Yeah.
And he can’t open it, so I pop it open for him.
Top flat says, cocaine.
They say it’s cocaine.
And then they pass it around. Cocaine. Cocaine.
We have to test it in the lab work or something.
Call my girlfriend, 11.58, freaking out, finally opens
it to find half a gram of no.
So now we’re in the police
station, and I’m not answering questions.
Is this in Albania?
Oh, it’s in Toronto. Yeah.
They’re starting to clamp down, and we’re at
the point they’re asking to touch pulling out
of my items, out of my back. Dictating.
This is my shorts.
This is my headbreaks.
This is a box of headphones I bought today.
Here’s the receipt. You want to see?
Here’s my shopping.
Pull up everything down to the bottle
cap, the shell, the tissue paper.
I pull out more and more tissue paper.
You never know when there’s going to be a fucking when.
The toilet is not going to have to
know when there’s going to be toilet paper.
You don’t have any hair.
Wonder how you look white.
Smells like shit in here.
Paul’s, you fucker.
They don’t have any toilet paper in this building.
They shit in a plastic hole in the ground.
Yeah, and Muscle Man, I call him
the police officer stopped me suspiciously.
Picked out a quantum toilet paper on the desk.
I spread it all over the desk.
You want to see the fucking toilet paper?
Half an hour of doing that, somebody
hands me a 300 mil bottle.
And I doubt more.
I’m thirsty.
You’re arresting me for drugs?
I might be on drugs.
I’m thirsty.
I already tried to get water from my nose.
There’s no potable water in this filter.
How much for another one?
Another pretty much the bug.
And okay, so Officer 13565, the one who put cuffs on
me, he asked me again, Where did you get it from?
And I tell her, what do you mean? I told you already.
This is legal, nicotine.
You can buy this with the tobacco.
He’s asking about the marijuana.
I tell the Muscle Man, you must be the only policeman
in the world stupid enough to think this is cocaine.
Tell him.
What do you mean you’re sending this off to the lab?
Sending it to the lab? You don’t have a lab.
You don’t even have running water.
We’ve got to send it where did you buy the marijuana?
I don’t know what you talked about.
What is your father’s name?
Why won’t you tell us?
I know it doesn’t matter just for your
report, but I don’t feel like telling me
until you give me back my phone.
They said, who is your father?
They need to know who’s your father?
I start packing my bag, and I’ve expressed them.
I’m uncomfortable touching my shit once it’s on the
table, but I don’t want you to touch it.
I still don’t know.
I’m still worried they’re going to jack all my shit.
Why am I here?
What, half a grand?
This is ridiculous.
So what do you want from me?
Thinking, are they going to fucking install me?
I think even the police, they
have a nickname in Albania.
They call the police the Mafia.
And my girlfriend, the last time I
called her, I got picked up.
I called her 1145 in the park.
Last time I talked to her, twelve 02:00 a.m.
So the entire time, she’s no idea what’s going on.
They don’t let me use the phone ever again.
Um okay.
So they moved me to the they
moved me to the police headquarters.
And they they tell me, oh,
yeah, you’re gonna see your lawyer.
You’re going to see a police officer.
You’ll be out of here in an hour.
Yeah, fuck you.
What do you order an hour? Fuck off.
I know this is bullshit.
They introduced me to the jail warden.
He doesn’t speak any English.
And they close the bars on us.
They’ve got my phone and they’ve got my
and they continue to chat and hand the
warden a copy of the police report.
I remind them again, I need to use the phone.
I need to call my lawyer.
I need to call my embassy.
I need to call my girlfriend.
She’s worried that you are the map.
So the police officer’s partner who they
took me in the police car.
I put my hands back through the bars, and he starts
undoing my shackles that he can’t up to it, police around.
And she’s like, what the fuck is this?
What?
I props it up against the wall like this.
He starts patting me down against the wall
like this, with four police officers watching.
And he’s like patting me down like, what do you want?
You want my glasses?
I don’t have anything.
And then he searches my bag.
He rummages around a little bit.
He pulls out my laptop.
He’s like, what the fuck?
You’ve got a laptop this close this, smuggling it.
And he starts yelling at the officers
behind the bars, what the fuck?
And they opened it up, and there’s a laptop.
And they’re just embarrassed, like, quiet.
And I wink at this, and they take
my laptop as now I’m in jail.
Part two jail.
The warden takes me backpack to this office
and puts me in a jail cell here.
I make a couple of young guys, like, smiling.
What did they get you for?
Okay, so these guys, we exchange stories.
These guys are just fucking up here.
They just these guys have both been picked
up, like, right outside of the park.
He’s walking inside, and the other
one I can’t remember exactly.
Fucking I’ll get it.
I’m technically off shift, though.
Is it?
I don’t know.
Technically not on shift anymore.
Hi, guys. They’re the big guys. Oh.
They do it themselves. Okay. See? Sorry.
And they tell me everything’s going to be fine.
Like, you’re going to get your stuff back.
You’re scared to do anything.
You’re just going to walk out there.
What is the point of all of this?
Okay.
Now I’m comfortable.
Now I know I’m going to be bothers me at this point.
My girlfriend has no idea.
Yeah, of course.
Apparently there’s a sign, or um, no,
I think they just do it themselves. To be honest.
That’s what’s always happened.
Need to get in touch with a girlfriend.
Need to get in touch with a girlfriend.
Yeah, the jail cops have hit around the corner.
Sorry.
They need to pay.
I’ve no, I’ve no, we have no.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Touching my shit once it’s on the table,
but I don’t want you to touch it.
I still don’t know.
I’m still worried they’re going to jack all my shit.
I’m like, Why am I here for half a grand?
This is ridiculous.
So what do you want from me?
Thinking, are they going to fucking install me?
Are these even the police?
They have a nickname in Albania here.
They call the police the Mafia.
And my girlfriend, the last time I
called her, I got picked up.
I called her at 1145 in the park.
Last time I talked to her, twelve 02:00 A.m..
So the entire time, she’s no idea what’s going on.
They don’t let me use the phone ever again.
Um okay.
So they move me to the they
move me to the police headquarters.
And they they tell me, oh,
yeah, you’re gonna see your lawyer.
You’re going to see a police officer.
You’ll be out of here in an hour.
Yeah, fuck you.
What are you on an hour? Fuck off.
I know this is bullshit.
They introduced me to the jail warden.
He doesn’t speak any English.
And they close the bars on us.
And they’ve got my phone, and they’ve got
my and they continue to chat and hand
the warden a copy of the police report.
I remind them again, I need to use the phone.
I need to call my lawyer.
I need to call my embassy.
I need to call my girlfriend.
She’s worried that you are the malpa.
So the police officer’s partner, who they took me
in the police car, I put my hands back
through the bars, and he starts undoing my shackles
that he can’t do it, police around.
And she’s like, what the fuck is it?
Props it up against like this.
He starts patting me down against the wall
like this, with four police officers watching.
And he’s, like, patting me down like, what do you want?
You want my glasses?
I don’t have anything.
And then he searches my bag.
He rummages around a little bit.
He pulls out my laptop.
He’s like, what the fuck?
You’ve got a laptop this closed this, smuggling it.
And he starts yelling at the officers
behind the bars, what the fuck?
And they opened it up, and there’s a laptop.
And they’re just embarrassed, like, quiet.
And I wink at this, and they take my laptop.
My laptop is now I’m in jail.
Part two jail.
The warden takes me back back to his
office and puts me in a chair on.
So there I meet a couple of young guys and smiling.
What did they get you for?
Okay, so these guys, we exchange stories.
These guys are just fucking up here.
They just these guys have both been picked up.
One, like, right outside of the park.
He’s walking inside, and the
other one, I can’t remember.
Fucking I get it.
I’m technically off shift, though.
Was it?
I don’t know.
Technically, not on shift anymore.
Hi, guys. They’re the beer guys. Oh.
They do it themselves. Sorry.
And they tell me everything’s going to be fine.
Like you’re going to get your stuff
back, you’re scared to do anything.
You’re just going to walk out there.
What is the point of all of this?
Okay.
Now I’m comfortable.
Now I know I’m going to be fine.
Only thing that bothers me at this
point, my girlfriend has no idea.
Yeah, of course.
Apparently.
No.
I think they just do it themselves.
To be honest, that’s what’s always happened.
Need to get in touch with a girlfriend.
Need to get in touch with a girlfriend.
Yeah, the jail cops have hit around the corner.
Are you asking me to pay? Sorry.
They need to pay.
We have no.
&lt;strong&gt;__&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;__&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;__&lt;/strong&gt;___&lt;/p&gt;


          </description>
          <pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
          <link>http://localhost:4000/Audio-recordings-transcribed.html</link>
          <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/Audio-recordings-transcribed.html</guid>
          
          
        </item>
      
    
      
        <item>
          
            <title>Arrested by the Albanian Mafia</title>
          
          <author>fakeemail@gmail.com (Kauri's BS)</author>
          <description>
            &lt;ul id=&quot;markdown-toc&quot;&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#part-i-lies-and-intimidation&quot; id=&quot;markdown-toc-part-i-lies-and-intimidation&quot;&gt;Part I: Lies and Intimidation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#part-ii-jail&quot; id=&quot;markdown-toc-part-ii-jail&quot;&gt;Part II: Jail&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#part-iii-a-big-ol-waste-of-everybodys-time&quot; id=&quot;markdown-toc-part-iii-a-big-ol-waste-of-everybodys-time&quot;&gt;Part III: A big ol’ waste of everybody’s time&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h5 class=&quot;no_toc&quot; id=&quot;foreword&quot;&gt;Foreword&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I want to say a massive thankyou to my girlfriend Lucia. Without her I would have been alone and terrified, and this story would probably have gone quite differently. You’d think there’s not much she can do from San Francisco.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;part-i-lies-and-intimidation&quot;&gt;Part I: Lies and Intimidation&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h5 class=&quot;no_toc&quot; id=&quot;monday-18th-september&quot;&gt;Monday 18th September&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A productive start to a new week! It’s 4am, and I’m writing from jail in Tirana, Albania. Well, I’m smoking with the warden in his office. That privilege cost me nine euro. Potable water included.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Live music roars from the stage, thirty metres south. The crowd sings and hollers, beer stalls busy. I’m at an open-air concert in the heart of the city, lounging as comfortably as one can on a plastic couch; journaling, taking photos, enjoying the vibrant atmosphere. I’m enjoying this different perspective on the city. I find myself marvelling at the seamless organization, the fantastic music, the joy one night can bring. I contemplate the skyscrapers under construction; an optimism for this challenged city.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Policia.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I turn around back to face him. “Excuse me?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A muscular plain-clothed man looks back at me. He holds his badge forth. “I am the Policia. How is your night?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s hard to hear over the music, and we are raising our voices. “Fine. Isn’t it a lovely night. Is there a problem?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He raises one leg onto the plastic bench and leans in towards me. Behind him, the darkness of the lowly-lit stairs leading to the Opera House. Glancing around, I notice another man approaching from behind, barriering a carefree world behind us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“What’s in your bag?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Sorry, have I done something wrong?” I argue. “Do I have to consent? What are my rights? What the fuck is this?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think back to a recent acquaintance I made. I rode five hours with a Dutch man, a diplomat in Belgrade, for the Delegation of the European Union to Serbia. He is on diplomatic mission is to help the West Balkans one day join the EU, by improving the rule of law in the West Balkans. It’s no secret Albania faces challenges with corruption, a deep-rooted systemic issue affecting politics, the judiciary, public services, healthcare, education, business. In terms of law enforcement; bribery, extortion, abuse of power. In my mind, this hulking policeman is the embodiment. His intimidation works.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I begrudgingly remove items from my backpack, condescendengly explaining each item. I do not want them to touch my shit. What’s in my bag? Well, fuck. With me I have all my useful junk, everything of value. All day I’ve been writing emails, applying for jobs, chatting with friends and family. The city seems a right place for it. I have my phone, my cables, my passport. Brand new earbuds. My wallet, about 30,000 LEK (300€) in cash. My togs - you never know when you’re going to need them, even in the middle of the city. A tote bag, inspected. An empty water bottle, sniffed. Half a can of Pringles, poured to the floor. On reflection, the most valuable item in there was my journal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A small snus container, the culprit. I’ve been using it to quit smoking. A snus pouch is a small, teabag-like sachet that contains tobacco product, a white powder. Swedish stuff. 100% legal. A snus container has two compartments: the bottom compartment holds the snus itself, and the top compartment is for discarding used pouches. This is what it looks like.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Editor’s note: Image coming one day. For now you can see an example product here:
&lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Nicotine_pouch&quot;&gt;Wikipedia: Nicotine pouch&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
He picks it out of my backpack’s front pocket. Despite all those muscles, he simply couldn’t get it open. Pulling and twisting, not a budge. Begrudgingly I take it from his hands and pop the top flap open, revealing three used snus pouches. “This is snus,” I explain. “Nicotine. What else do you want?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Muscleman inspects it closely. “This is cocaine?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“NICOTINE. LEGAL.” I scowl.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Where did you buy this from?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I look at him blankly, confused by the line of questioning. “Is this man stupid?” I wonder. The second officer takes my passport off me. Soon three more officers join the scene, also working in the field. They pass around the snus container. “Cocaine” “cocaine” “cocaine”, I understand. What are we, parrots? They pick at a pouch, and the nicotine powder spills out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With a deep sigh, I clarify. “This is a nicotine pouch. It is a no-smoke tobacco product. You can buy this here in Albania at any tobacco store. You place it under your lip, and it releases nicotine. It smells like mint because it has a mint flavouring. You can see it here on the packaging.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I reach for my phone and show them pictures of the product. A quick Google translate later, I present a web page in Albanian, explaining the product its legal status.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“We have to take it to the lab to test it for cocaine.” says Muscleman.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As if he’d just remembered something, the offending officer closes the snus container and starts to pry open the bottom compartment again. Pop. There’s the marijuana, a few flakes, half a gram. Jackpot.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They’re pestering me a bunch of questions about the weed, about the cocaine. “What is this? Where did you buy it from? Who sold it to you?” Now I don’t talk any more, I’m shitting myself. My internal monologue is blowing up. “How the fuck did you get yourself in this situation? Were you doing something wrong? Why did you let them search you? You didn’t – he just took it from your bag! Is that legal? Is any of this legal? Fuck, I don’t even know if snus is legal here! Why did you bring the weed? You don’t even smoke!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Editor’s note: I don’t even smoke. Long story, I’d carried it since Croatia and pretty much forgot about it. I intended to gift it to someone during my travels.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
A police car is coming to take me to the station. This is going to be a problem.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“What, am I supposed to bribe these guys? How much do I bribe them? Twenty euro? Offensive. Fifty euro? Two-hundred? Fuck, that’s a lot of money. Shit, I might have told them I’m in Tirana to see the dentist. I’m dressed way too nicely. I’m probably the best-dressed person in Tirana right now. They think you have money. This is going to turn into an extortion case, isn’t it? At least it’s not the mafia, right? Why did you decide to wear your only shirt today? Why did you come here with all your valuables? You’ve been working on your laptop all day, right. And you were just on the phone with your girlfriend Lucia. Lucia? Lucia!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lucia and my sister Jade both receive a flurry of cryptic messages at 11.45pm. Lucie jumps on the phone. They let me talk for twenty-six seconds, before kicking me off. I fight for my right to “talk to my lawyer” and call her back. We get a few minutes where I can explain the situation, in all uncertain terms. I have no idea what’s going to happen when they take me to the station. “We will just fill the paperwork, twenty minutes and then you can go.” Really? I thought it’d take longer than that to harvest my organs. How can I feel comfortable putting my life in the hands of people who are actively lying, knowingly misaccusing me in a country where the Police are nicknamed &lt;em&gt;the Mafia&lt;/em&gt;? They kick me off the phone, and Lucie calls right back. We steal another minute.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Two new officers arrive on the scene, cuff me and lead me to the police car. We drive a few minutes to the station in relative silence. They uncuff me and sit me at a desk the middle of a long, off-white concrete painted hallway without a single painting or decoration. Around me lie a handful of doors; in front of me, a door with a bar grill window. To my right, a new officer sits down in front of a stack of paperwork. I’ll call him Mr Illiterate, given how slowly he writes. The man who cuffed me, he can be Officer 13565, as displayed boldly on his uniform. 13565 wouldn’t tell me his name. He stands in front of me. His partner moseys around, and mingles with the new cops that have come out to greet us. Muscleman joins the party shortly later. Three or four other cops float around, I don’t know what the fuck they’re doing. Apparently they’re working.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I call Lucie for the last time at 12.02am. Lucia advises we had about two minutes of actual conversation, a frantic exchange where I briefly explained the situation. She describes the atmosphere as tense and chaotic. She talks to one of the officers, who maintains his aggressive demeanour. “This is Police station number 3!” “We are going to send it to the lab to test it for cocaine!” “He has marijuana, he is going to go to jail!” I have advised Lucie to get in contact with Jade and Dom, and together they will figure out what to do. She might need to get me a lawyer. For the remainder of the call they took away the phone, but the call kept running. Eventually they hung it up. That would be the last time I talked to anyone on the outside.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is a camera in one corner of the hallway, the type with a swivel head. I ask why it never moves. Mr Illiterate assures me it’s on. Bullshit, where’s the red light? It’s not on, is it? I put my empty water bottle on the table and ask for some water. “It’s not possible to drink the water here,” they tell me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mr Illiterate has been slowly filling out the police report. He never even took a picture of my passport. He takes a break and offers me a cigarette. He asks me the odd question. I refuse to tell him my father’s name. By now, I’m thinking, we all know the snus is legal. You can literally see what its made of on the back of the fucking container. I realize they only care about the marijuana, and are using “cocaine” as a scare tactic. My phone is going nuts on the table, notifications on, ringing. A friend calls. Another friend calls. Lucie calls repeatedly. They won’t let me answer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They ask to search my bag again. I start pulling items out on the desk, dictating for them. “This is my shorts. This is my headband. This is a box for headphones. Here’s the receipt, too. You want to see? I went shopping today! And here’s my shopping bag.” I pull out everything down to the bottlecap, the shell, the tissue paper. I pull out more and more tissue paper. “Because,” I explain, “you never know when there’s going to be toilet paper in Tirana. I bet you don’t have any here. Wonder how you lot wipe? Smells like shit in here.” I’d later find out they don’t have any toilet paper; they piss and shit in a plastic hole in the ground. Muscleman suspiciously picks at a large clump of tissue paper. I eagerly spread tissue all across the desk for his colleagues to see, there is no drugs hidden in my toilet paper.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After half an hour, someone hands me a 300mL bottle of water from the mart next door. It’s too hot in here. I down it in one go. “How much costs another one?” But the mini-mart is now closed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;13565 me tries more questions. “Where did you get it from?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I play with it. “What do you mean? I told you already, this is legal nicotine. You can buy this in the tobacco store.” I turn to Muscleman. “You must be the only policeman in the world stupid enough to think this is cocaine. By the way, what do you mean you’re sending that off to the lab? You don’t have a lab here. You don’t even have running water in this building!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Yes, we are sending it to the lab to be tested!” Muscleman assures me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;13565 tries again. “Where did you buy the marijuana?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I don’t know what you’re talking about.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Why won’t you tell, what is your father’s name?” he asks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I know it doesn’t matter, it’s just for your report. But I don’t feel like telling you until you give me back my phone.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I start to pack my things away again. I have expressed that I am uncomfortable with them touching my stuff, because I think they are going to steal from me. Any excuse to kick a fuss. I leave the tissues strewn across the table. I leave my wallet wide open, this time with quite a bit more money in it. I leave my old headphones too, next to the brand-new box and receipt. I ask to use the toilet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I come back an it’s untouched. By now I’m convinced they want more. They’re going to take my organs. At some point, they tell me I must go into the jail cell. I simply refuse. Eventually Mr Illiterate finishes his paperwork, and 13565 has no further questions. 13565 and his partner drive me to another building, the headquarters “…to see your lawyer and police officer. It will take one hour.” Bullshit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We walk up the stairs towards a large uniformed man. Without thinking I call at him, “Hey, this is bullshit, these guys are arresting me for literally nothing, they won’t let me speak to my lawyer, they won’t let me speak to to my girlfriend!” Of course, the jail warden doesn’t speak English. They close the bars on us and hand over a copy of the police report. They converse in Albanian. I consistently interject, and remind them again – I need to use a phone, I need to call my lawyer, I need to call my embassy, I need to call my girlfriend; she is worried that you are the mafia. They keep my phone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;13565’s partner beckons, and I stick my hands through the bars. The others give him shit as he struggles, a half-minute to undo my shackles. Normally I can’t understand Albanian, but this time I understood word-for-word. “What the fuck are doing, bro?” “I can’t, it’s stuck!” “Just unlock it?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The jail warden props me against the wall, four officers watching, and starts patting me down. What the fuck are you looking for? Here, you want my glasses?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The warden then searches my bag, the contents of which by now have been completely jumbled up. He rummages around, and produces a large item. For the second time in my life I understand Albanian. “What the fuck, there’s a laptop in here!? How did you miss the biggest god-damn thing in his backpack?” He yells at the embarrassed officers behind the bars, and I make sure to wink back. They double-check inside my laptop case to make sure I’m not hiding drugs in the keyboard, and hold on to my laptop.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;part-ii-jail&quot;&gt;Part II: Jail&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The warden takes my backpack to his office, and shows me to my cell. Same as the last station – this time I’m guided through the door with the bar grill window. Inside sit a couple other fellas, young local men. They smile. “So what’d they get you for?” We exchange stories. “Yeah, these guys are the mafia. They just do what they want”. Viktor was picked up outside his apartment building, carrying a little bit of weed. The other, Florian – I forget his story – but he was the same, a little bit of weed. He’s a lawyer. “They’re not going to take your stuff, they are too scared. You won’t have any problems; they can’t do anything about a little bit of weed. They will let you go,” he advises.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By now I know everything is going to be fine, but there’s still one small problem. I can’t relax because my girlfriend thinks I’ve might’ve been kidnapped by fucking Mafia. Not out of guilt, but concern - I realize, I’m going to be in here for a while. While I’m safe in the cell, she’ll be outside worried dead. Until the moment I give word, she’s going to be working my case; reading and calling and trying to figure out what the fuck is going on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The warden pops his head in and speaks to me, Florian acting translator. He can’t read my name on the papers! I start to spell, but the warden gives up and calls us into his office. The desk has two large ledgers on it. A sink lies in one corner of the room. I sit facing Florian, in front of the ledger, the warden to the side. Florian picks up a pen. “K-A-R-U-I”, I spell. “B-O-C-K-M-A-N.” The warden offers us a cigarette. Date of birth, slightly wrong. Father’s name, slightly wronger. Under instruction from Mr Illiterate Senior, Florian fills the rest of the ledger. We ash into a plastic cup with a little bit of water.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Florian explains to the warden, I need to call my embassy, I need to call my lawyer, I need to call my girlfriend; she is worried that I am kidnapped by the mafia; I have not told her everything will be fine. No phone here. I point at a half-empty water bottle on the table, and the warden nods. I down it in one go, and move toward the sink. The warden speaks up – you can’t drink the water here either. I ask for my notebook, and he agrees.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’re ushered back to the cell, a place with nothing but time and good company. I take notes. Prior to the collapse of the communist regime in the 1990’s the police were unwaveringly loyal to the regime. They were instrumental in enforcing the regime and maintaining control, with no transparency, accountability, or oversight. They were tasked with repressing political dissent and opposition,[problem, not tasked with this] harassing and imprisoning at will. They perpetuated a culture of fear and repression. Bribery, off-the-books payments, nepotism, and embezzlement were commonplace, tools for expediting bureaucratic processes, to gain access to services, to avoid legal consequences. Corruption was seen as an expected, even necessary way to navigate the bureaucratic systems.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Following the social and political collapse of the communist regime in the 1990’s, the country experienced a period of significant social and political upheaval, creating an environment conducive to the growth of organized crime. Notable activities included drug cultivation and trafficking, particularly cannabis, as well as human trafficking, smuggling, and theft. Corruption, collusion and infiltration between members of law enforcement and organized crime groups facilitated criminal activities, protecting criminal networks, and further eroding public trust in the police.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The warden peers his head in, and Viktor is taken away to be processed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With international support, the Albanian government, recognizing the severity of the problem, initiated efforts to combat corruption within law enforcement agencies. This included measures to strengthen internal oversight, improve training and professionalism, and implement anti-corruption reforms. Today, Albania is undergoing major judicial reform aimed at overhauling the judicial system, addressing issues such as corruption, political interference, and inefficiency. In the police force, Albania is now vetting and screening police officers, providing anti-corruption training and implementing transparency and accountability mechanisms. They have made significant progress, and the mafia no longer run rampant on the streets. However, these challenges have been deeply rooted, and clearly these problems still exist. The same corruption still exists, but now you just can’t see it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We become quiet, as commotion stirs outside. The warden peers his head in, and holds two fingers to pursed lips. We join him in his office for a cigarette. Florian tells me a large group of illegal immigrants have arrived; they now occupy the holding cell. We finish our discussion about corruption, with the warden explaining that he does not take bribes. The warden offers for us to stay, so as not to share a room together with the immigrants.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Around 3am, Florian is taken away by another officer. I ask this officer if I can make call; no luck. I’m advised I must wait for a “Licensed Translator” to arrive before I can be processed. I open my wallet, and the warden allows me to stay in his office and write, passing the time together over cigarettes and water. By the end, it cost me nine euro for the privilege.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;part-iii-a-big-ol-waste-of-everybodys-time&quot;&gt;Part III: A big ol’ waste of everybody’s time&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The morning glow peeks through jail cell’s the crusty barred window. A couple hours’ sleep on the half-broken chairs did its job, I can’t sleep any longer. The metaphorical clock passes. I say hello to the new warden. He doesn’t speak English either.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Eventually I am taken to be processed. I collect my bag from the warden. They lead me to an office, not more than ten metres from the holding cell. “New Zealand”, I understand, and the man inside shakes his head and points to his side. They lead me to the next office. Three men sit at their desks, a small room. A young man beckons me to sit down beside him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m all smiles. I have been preparing for this moment. “Hi, how are you?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I am good, and you?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Who are you?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I am Officer Kola. Narcotics department.” Kola? Is that a nickname?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“What time is it?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“9:45.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Where is my lawyer?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“He is coming. Here in a few minutes.” Sure, bro. “Passport.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I notice my phone on his desk, right in front of me. “I need to make a phone call.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“You cannot use your phone here. You will be out of here soon.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I need to charge my phone,” I scowl.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I produce a cable, and fumble around with my phone. Miraculously, it’s still on. I hurriedly message Lucie; “I’m ok. Not done yet. Going to meet Lawyer soon. They found 1g weed, that’s the main issue. I think I shouldn’t even get a fine. Talk to you soon. Story coming.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I skim my messages from Lucie. “You’ll be fine, they’ll probably let you go in the morning. In contact with the New Zealand Embassy in Rome. The Embassy will contact you. Here’s a list of lawyers in Tirana.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Enough,” barks Kola. “You cannot use your phone here.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I message Jade, “ASK LUCIE”. He moves to shoo me off and I leave it to charge. For the first time, I truly feel relaxed. I hand Kola my passport, and he starts tapping at the keyboard. For a few minutes there is silence between us. He offers me a cigarette.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I study my surroundings. Inside this room lies three messy desks, a few computers, a dusty bookshelf. A large printer sits on a small table in the middle of the room. A small painting hangs on one wall, slightly crooked. Alongside stacks of papers, I see my laptop, snus container, and two plastic evidence bags on his desk. An officer nudges me, the leg of my wooden chair pinching an evidence bag on the floor, and I’d notice the jumbled stack of evidence behind me. A piss in a cup. In one corner, a man sits at his computer, same age as I am.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“What is in this bag?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“What do you think this is? Haven’t these idiots taken it to the lab yet? Why are you asking me?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;His face remains still. “Anyone can find out what this is with a quick Google search. There is no need to send it to the lab.” He puts down the snus and lifts the other bag. “And what is this?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I don’t understand what you are talking about. I need a, ✌Licensed Translator✌.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“We do not need a translator, we can –”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Oh,” I interject, raising my voice. I’ve never grinned harder. The sarcasm is dripping out of my mouth. “There’s no Licensed Translator? You mean to tell me I have been waiting in this jail cell for ten hours, waiting for a ✌Licensed Translator ✌to arrive, yet we do not need one? Problem is, I don’t understand you!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are other officers loitering around in the background, at the other desk, inside the room, outside the room. “I am not your enemy,” he says. “I have to follow the procedure. We are not going to charge you with anything. If you tell me it is for personal consumption, you can leave.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I have to follow the procedure too. Tell me, where is my lawyer?” I say angrily, cracking another wide smile.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“He will be here in two minutes.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I keep quiet. Kola’ asks some more questions, innocent ones too. “How long have you been here?” 
“What are you doing here in Tirana?” “What is your father’s name?” I start to feel sorry for Kola. He is just doing his job, but his colleagues brought me here. Each time I throw him more shit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kola relaxes from his keyboard, and the printer starts to buzzing. Bzzz… “Yeah, I’d love a coffee thanks.” …Bzzz… I pass him his machine-made espresso and take a sip of my own. …Bzzz. The printer eventually stops, and I hand them to him. Eighteen pages. These are for me!?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Like many of the people I have seen here, Kola wears plain clothes – black t-shirt, black pants, black shoes. In stark contrast, I am wearing an off-white linen shirt, my favourite pink shorts. If not best-dressed in Tirana, certainly in this police station. That is, until my lawyer arrives.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Petrin walks in, and Kola hands him the eighteen pages. They obviously already know eachother. Petrin and I take some time alone. He explains to me that this is a very simple case, and they’re going to let me go. In terms of marijuana, Albania has some of the harshest penalties in Europe. New reforms around legalization of medicinal cannabis passed just months ago, and there are now proposals for total legalization. Police still firmly treat marijuana strictly, though there are no penalties for possession of less than three grams as long as it is for personal consumption. The system has a big problem: they must follow the same procedure, whether it’s one gram or one hundred kilos.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We start to go through the papers together. He translates sentence by sentence. The first two paragraphs consist of explanatory information gleamed from my passport, some references to laws.. Then it describes how I was arrested – in possession of suspected cannabis, in possession of suspected nicotine. Nicotine?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I take Petrin through one part of the story – the accusation of cocaine. He suggests I can ask to have it altered if I want, but that, though it would not really matter, from a legal perspective, altering the page to suggest I might have had cocaine could only be a bad thing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I take Petrin through the rest; the approach, the accusation of cocaine, the first officer who rubs his thumb against his two fingers. I discuss the denial of water (to someone who is, in their view, probably on drugs), the denial of contact, holding me for far longer than necessary. He explains that there is no process here by which I can add this information. He suggests I can always send a formal complaint later, otherwise I would have to sue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We go through the rest of the pages. On each page, the first two paragraphs are repeated. Then there is a little section about the formal procedure that has or will be followed, and my acceptance of it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;… The suspected nicotine has been bagged in an evidence bag, in accordance with some standard… Fine, I’ll sign.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;… The suspected marijuana has been weighed. It weighs 0.7 grams, excluding our plastic evidence bag… Fine, I’ll sign.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;… You have the right to remain silent… Excuse me, I have rights? Nobody has told you your rights?… Fuck this, I’ll sign.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kola comes back and I talk freely. I briefly run him through the same story I’ve told Petrin, and advise him I will be submitting a formal complaint for unethical, probably illegal conduct leading up to my arrest and detention. For the first time, I see him crack a little smile. He offers me another cigarette as we chat about the absurdity of the situation, of the system. “Just change fucking procedure then. All you have to do is change a few words - three grams walks without question. Or change your internal police policy! Make it a 50 euro fine or something, at least justify all this wasted time! Or better yet, why don’t you just tell your field brutes not to waste their time with people who are carrying less than three grams?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The police officers who arrested me knew I was going to walk away with no charges. Muscleman, 13565, Mr Illiterate, and all the other officers involved in my case. How many police resources have been wasted on me? How many policeman were involved, how many man hours? Eighteen pages of paperwork – someone at the prosecution office is supposed to read these. A lawyer, a civil servant – it’s not my responsibility to pay him! Twelve hours of my personal time. But not just my time - my girlfriend was up all night searching for how to defend me. My sister, too. I have in my inbox, emails from the New Zealand Embassy in Rome that I shall reply to. Lucie tried, Jade tried, the Embassy tried, but nobody could reach the police station. They send how many police officers to detain and arrest me, but not a single officer to answer the phone? That this happened to at least two other people last night; that this is normal; that this happens on a completely regular basis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Later I would find out, my girlfriend tried to call the police headquarters multiple times. The New Zealand Embassy advised me they “attempted to contact the police station in Tirana to understand the situation and to receive an idea of what the process is but had no success so far.” How many police officers to arrest me, but not even one to answer a phone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I sign all the paperwork except for one. I consent for my piss to be tested for narcotic content in the lab. But I refuse to consent to giving a urine sample. I had argued with Petrin. “It doesn’t matter. Positive for marijuana, personal consumption. Negative, you were going to smoke it. Positive for heroin? Where’s the heroin? There’s no evidence.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I don’t want to piss in a cup. Let me refuse, they will make me anyway, and I will piss all over it!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They gave me a plastic cup anyway. Kola tells me, “Just a little is enough.” I haven’t pissed in six hours. Another police officer took me to the bathroom and waited outside. I fill it to the brim, tighten the lid, then wash it in the sink. The officer outside holds a plastic evidence bag open. I bend down, place it on the ground, then shake the water off my hands.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Laughing his ass off, Kola gives me his number. “You can contact me about anything, it does not have to be about this case.” Petrin and I head out for coffee.&lt;/p&gt;

          </description>
          <pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
          <link>http://localhost:4000/Arrested-by-the-Albanian-Mafia.html</link>
          <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/Arrested-by-the-Albanian-Mafia.html</guid>
          
          
        </item>
      
    
      
        <item>
          
            <title>Saviour</title>
          
          <author>fakeemail@gmail.com (Kauri's BS)</author>
          <description>
            &lt;h5 id=&quot;thursday-28th-september&quot;&gt;Thursday 28th September&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sometimes I feel blue, then I think of you,&lt;br /&gt;
But sometimes my heart only aches;&lt;br /&gt;
I think back to days we’d only just met,&lt;br /&gt;
The trenches we did not foresake.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
I have not forgetten the way that you scold,&lt;br /&gt;
Nor have I the way that you tease,&lt;br /&gt;
Today I cover my mouth when I burp;&lt;br /&gt;
Amendments for love, I appease.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
I think of you in your cute yellow dress,&lt;br /&gt;
An angel, a golden-day glow,&lt;br /&gt;
I picture your smile, your damn-sexy aura,&lt;br /&gt;
I feel myself aching below.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
I crave it, the touch of your strong slender body,&lt;br /&gt;
Your body, the way that it curls;&lt;br /&gt;
I dream of our bed, the littlest spoon,&lt;br /&gt;
Your warmth, shielding a grey world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
‘Cause inside a darkness, a fear of myself,&lt;br /&gt;
A fear of the trenches too deep;&lt;br /&gt;
I envy the others; it all seems so simple:&lt;br /&gt;
The lies, the secrets we keep.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
When I think of you, I do feel alive,&lt;br /&gt;
I feel your love colourful cures;&lt;br /&gt;
Hold you in my arms and never let go,&lt;br /&gt;
And when you return I’ll be yours.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Love,&lt;br /&gt;
Kauri&lt;/p&gt;


          </description>
          <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
          <link>http://localhost:4000/Saviour.html</link>
          <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/Saviour.html</guid>
          
          
        </item>
      
    
      
        <item>
          
            <title>LNCwJoe</title>
          
          <author>fakeemail@gmail.com (Kauri's BS)</author>
          <description>
            &lt;h5 id=&quot;late-night-chats-with-joe&quot;&gt;Late night chats with Joe&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;tabletop-chats--story-summary&quot;&gt;Tabletop chats &amp;amp; Story summary&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gorgeous.
Yeah, sure.
What about the trees?
So yeah, every orange tree is different.
They’re all like kind of set up.
There’s some that are seedless,
so they’re better for eating.
Some that are like sweeter juices and stuff.
They’ve got Japanese bubble tree just down there.
Pomegranate diamond.
I’ve got all the grapevines.
Yeah, it’s such a beautiful diamond.
Yeah.
I think it’s like weird because this hostel
I think is more made for guests.
It’s not really made for volunteers because
it’s actually not that easy on work.
So if you are little or something,
you have to work a lot.
Because I think in most one really big advantage
of volunteers is you can just use them longer.
I think you also get really fucking cheap labour.
So cheap €3 less than that.
It’s just another room in the hostel.
I think it’s that’s the idea by you’re the boss, Jay.
You can just make the decision.
Just do it, just run it.
I think the problem is that this place I think
they should have a person like with Androp here I
think there’s the biggest problem here that they don’t have
someone who always here because they are coming at five
or six and that’s not enough.
And they could pay them because they have money.
Yeah, they will find a way.
But I think that they really need someone they
should have some cleaning because most of the hostels
have someone who cleans and does toilets and stuff.
I think it’s it’s not the best that
doesn’t have anyone because basically we do everything.
You just need someone who’s been here for even
just over like a month and a half.
Yeah, because everyone is here for maximum
stay here for more than I’ve not
left the hostel to event like here.
Yeah, because Tirana is not that interesting.
No, I love is that they love their country
so much and I think it’s not in an
unhealthy way because lots of countries love their countries
in a way that we are the best.
No other countries allowed in our country
because they are like births or something.
They love their country.
They love Albania but they love
seeing people from other countries.
They love people come from other countries.
I think it’s very nice.
Yeah, I think that kind of varies as well, but
yeah, I’ve certainly found it when me and Billy were
out like wild camping in Sarande and all the locals
waving peace when we were out in the rural I
don’t know, in the town, to be fair, all the
shopkeepers were really like fed up guys in the park.
That’s why for the last like 9 hours they just sat
under a tree because it was raining so much and then
all the guys would usually hang out in the park.
We’re all together so like sharing beers.
None of them spoke any English
really, apart from one guy.
It was so cool.
We’re all doing drawing together they
spoke something off the back.
This is you use for crack?
No, I remember.
You need anything like weird crack,
place to stay, just come.
I actually invited one of the
guys back to Brighton with me.
My girlfriend asked me to write her poem.
I said something silly, I said what do
you want me to do for you?
And she said, I want you to write me a poem.
And this was months ago and I gave a shit
about no way, but I’m going to write her.
Maybe I was thinking a love poem.
But it doesn’t actually have to be a love form.
Can be anything.
Yeah, she’s read that.
She’s read that of course.
Actually she’s read most of my stories.
She helped me write one in German.
Where are you from?
I’m from New Zealand.
Yes, I know.
I talked to them as well.
Yes, they were nice.
Sorry, I was busy working on my laptop at the time.
Yeah, for you guys.
Really? Well, yeah. Yeah. Sorry.
Where did you meet them?
I went to Scorpio. To where? Scorpio.
Scorpio, Macedonia.
I haven’t seen Macedonia on a map yet.
I know, it’s just east of him.
I can’t even picture it was so nice.
We were just hanging around like seven people
go to the canyon there and everything and
then went together to offer time together.
And now they are here.
Some of the guys from there will come here.
I’m very happy because they are very nice.
How long they stay?
A day for tonight. Cool.
Tomorrow see I’ll probably hang out there.
But you’re going to stop working here and stay here?
Is that the idea?
But tomorrow is my day off.
Tomorrow.
I’ve got a day off tomorrow. Yeah.
So I thought I might spend the day like painting.
Oh, that’s a good idea.
I think it would just be a nice thing to leave.
I mean you have to do it.
Yeah.
Promised you lee.
I’d make him like a clay head at those days.
Yeah, from them.
Are the gifts going to happen?
I’ll do it before I go.
You have to promise and say yeah,
I’ll do it in like four years.
No, you do it in 100 years. It’s not going to be.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s really funny.
Oh, no. But yeah.
So I’m going to make him the head paint in
there and maybe make head of Brainer as well.
Yeah, maybe their son be met. Their son?
His son, yeah, her son Brainer.
Well, both of their sons.
The little one yeah, he’s funny.
So for the beans, isn’t he?
The little one is 14 as well. Oh, sorry.
The youngest son.
The youngest one. Yeah.
I have seen one he’s once, but no, I haven’t.
Oh, yeah.
For a little bit of context, sitting outside
a outdoor open airplane and enjoying enjoying the
atmosphere in CSL and talking with my going
out and doing things in the city.
I bought happy with it.
And I’m sitting there writing and I’m just get showing
them back and they signed he takes he’s like, no.
And it’s got three such as top yeah.
Cooking shows.
It’s like you make sure that’s and pops it up and shit.
Look this off.
Grab a weed to jail.
I call my girlfriend.
This is at the park.
Yeah.
There was an open air concert on Sunday night. Saturday.
Sunday night.
Calling no.
Where is it?
I called my girlfriend.
She’s like, no idea what’s going on.
And I had jail.
Then jail make a oh, it’s not detecting the
audio would be really lovely if it was.
I’m gonna put it there for now.
Hold on to it.
What was I saying?
Was I saying I was calling my girlfriend. Yeah.
They let me call my girlfriend again.
The first call I made outside was at 11:45 p.m..
The last call I made to my girlfriend was twelve two.
The last time I talked to
anybody outside was twelve two.
And we talking shitting ourselves.
Like, are these guys a fucking
are these guys a fucking mafia?
Actually, we were wondering this outside
are these guys are fucking mafia?
Pardon?
What was the room?
Okay, so it was a bland white hallway.
Like dull concrete walls, 10 meters, 15 meters long.
There’s a few doors I can kind of see.
There’s a door in front of me with a bar drill.
So I’m like, okay, this is actually probably
a jailhouse or a police something rather are
they going to fucking steal my shit?
Are they trying to extort me?
The ones the ones outside who were giving me trouble?
Initially, no.
Some guys came from a cop car. Yes.
And I mean, I kind of knew it was legit, but
like I well, at least I knew they were legit police.
I thought they were trying to escort me.
Like, seriously.
I mean, he’s a wealthy tourist.
I’m the best fucking dressed person
in this entire city right now.
In fact, I’m dressed exactly
like this with my backpack. Yeah.
Exactly as I am now.
Yeah.
What else happened in that channel?
So oh, yeah, on the phone call with my girlfriend.
I mean, on the phone call with my girlfriend.
I am high for the audio’s record.
Sorry, this was an important wasn’t that important?
I was a little bit high.
I’ll cut this out of the audio actually.
My girlfriend’s been working on writing
a biography of her grandmother.
Like what the fuck? I didn’t know this.
She just told me about it now.
She’s been working on it for a year apparently.
I know she hasn’t done anything on it.
She would have told me about it if
she was that she’s transcribing some audio files.
She’s got some interviews from her grandmother that she’s
recorded in the past and she wants to script.
I didn’t ask her this actually but I
got the impression at the beginning we’re going
to take a biography, take some audio recordings.
That’s when she started working. Yeah.
So much.
Say if your grandparent passes away
when you’re like twelve yeah.
You’re not really of the right state of mind to
understand what they’re talking about as you get older.
My grandma was quite interesting.
She just stayed at home with
the time, never really left.
Have you guys seen the snowman film Christmas where it’s
like we’re walking in the air and they die on
they live in the house that film is based on. Yeah.
So the guy who wrote it
was like postman for the village.
Used to deliver post to the house and he got like
inspired looking at a cottage just underneath at the bottom of
this hills and windmills at the top of the hill.
Jackie Jill, she just like stayed there,
did her gardening, had a nursery.
She’d sell lots of plants and stuff so the
last call sorry the last school to my girlfriend
was at twelve two and one of the things
she understood while she was on the phone and.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yeah.
We have to take it to the lab to test it.
Yes.
She understands it’s marijuana.
Um, okay.
I actually grabbed my phone quite a few times.
I kept managing to kind of, like, wrangle it back.
Not physically.
What would they take off the table and
have a look and then put it back?
They never had a look, right? Had a look once.
And I’ll tell you why.
But they would take it and put it on the table.
Just take it back because it’s right in front of me.
Yeah.
And then the next time okay,
but you’ve got it over there.
But just let me charge let me put it on.
Put the battery on.
I kind of move to put it on and then
just take my phone with me and put it back.
And I’ve been holding onto my bag this
entire time when I was arrested outside.
Um, okay.
So they asked to search me again,
you know, to search my bag again.
I’ll do it myself.
And my deodorant and, like, toggs I still carry
my toggs with I always do this right.
You never know if you’re going to swim.
What else did I bring out of my dad?
Bring out, like, receipts for
the headphones I just bought.
Here’s the box picture.
My passport.
They’ve taken my passport.
They’re, like, writing down the details.
They’ve taken my passport and
they’re writing down the details.
This one guy I call Mr. Elizabeth.
He’s writing down.
They didn’t even take a picture of it.
We’re going to send this off to
the lab to get it tested.
You’ve got a lab?
I guess you get drug tested. It’s quite cheap.
Now, don’t you like those little tabs that
you put, like, a little bit on water?
What do you mean?
You’re going to send it to the left running water?
Oh, yeah.
I put down my bottle on the table and
I asked them, I can have some water?
No, you can’t drink the water from this pollution.
You have a lab.
You don’t have fucking potable water.
You have a key.
I think I’ve got one in my pocket, actually.
It’s like a cheap yeah, you just
had to probably an hour or so. Okay. Yeah.
See you guys. Once more.
Water. Yeah.
Tired?
Traveled a lot today.
You?
What else can I tell you?
That was all I was going to say.
Up to jail, which is the third part of the story.
Sorry. Jail.
Jail is we’re up to part two.
No, sorry.
We’re up to part three.
Part three?
What’s the title?
I’m blanking on the table of the title of this section.
Part three a big old waste of fucking time.
Um, we’re up to part three.
A big a big Old Waste of fucking time.
Anyone’s? Big one.
Thank you.
Have you seen that?
Jesus.
Sorry.
I know this is my responsibility to talk part three.
They go fucking time? I think so.
They they finally take me up
945 in the morning, find out.
I take my bag, I take my shirt, I’ll say bye
bye to the warden and they take me to his office.
They take me to the first actually, they take
me to the first office and I hear them
chatting New Zealand and the guy inside shakes his
head and points the other way and wondering, do
you even know where the fuck you’re taking me?
You take me to the office next door and the
guy calls me sitting at a desk in the corner.
And there’s another desk in this room and there’s
a big desk in the middle of it.
Kind of got diagonal with a printer in the middle.
Dusty bookshelves, stuff all over the tables.
He’s sitting in a computer and he calls
me and I come step beside him.
Not right beside him, kind of like angled.
Okay.
This whole time there’s kind of police officers in
the background and they’re chitchatting and kind of moving
around and listening, whatever they want to do, standing
outside the doorway doing fucking nothing.
There was one guy that just
doing nothing the entire time.
That’s so funny.
Must have been that story, like, the guy
that had that massive drug bus, 260 people. Yes.
The officer that booked me, he claimed
he was very instrumental in this.
Officer Kohler, Narcotics Department.
Introduces himself, or I ask him
rather did he say anything? Pardon?
Did he tell you anything about it?
His name? No.
Like the story of the people he
got called for the drug bust.
He didn’t tell? No.
I think I said, what did he tell me?
He did tell me a little bit.
Good question.
I I haven’t thought about this at all since I left,
since he told me, like, he told me about it.
So we kind of know what would happen, I guess,
in the UK, if there’s a big drug bust like
that, someone would be kind of put in a prison.
It would all be logged. Do you know what I mean?
It would all be kind of above board in a weird way.
He did say all 300 silence.
Right?
They just put them all in jail.
That would not happen anywhere else.
Or that would not happen.
Like in New Zealand, for example, if there is 260
people in the truck bus, like most of them walking
through, yeah, she’s put them all in jail.
Holy shit.
I guess if it was that big, I feel like
in the UK they might put them all in.
Yeah, but there’s a lot of people
you just shouldn’t be able to prosecute.
A lot of people just they were in the wrong place.
And to just throw in jail as well, there’d be
a lot of people just kind of hanging out there.
That’s a good point.
They’re working on they’ve just legalized
medicinal cannabis, like, a month.
Yeah, they’ve done UK as well. It’s amazing.
My sister’s got epilepsy quite, like, severely and she’s taking,
like, CBD oil now and it’s just world good.
Literally, her seizures dipped.
So much fucking about.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So much.It’s so nice, for sure.I guess epilepsy is kind ofthe main thing really, isn’t it?Does a lot of good but yeah, especiallythat so much more developed for sure.I’m really be excited for like for itto get into like mental health stuff.So a lot of stuff likeschizophrenia and paranoia or whatever.You’re given opiates which I think dullyour mind too much, I think.I thought what do you call this?Like recreational?Yeah, it’s really fucking bad.Depends how your brain works anddepends on the weed as well.Believed to be contributing to causing it.It depends who you are.I mean weed weed does bring on schizophrenia for sure, butit can be quite calming for your mind as well.You get a lot of different types of weed.Like you get sativa and indica.Indica is a lot more like just that weird headyfeeling where you’re a bit confused and you kind ofI don’t know, that kind of slightly scatty feeling.The anxiety but also the kindof dreaminess and the spaceiness.You get the indicator and this teeth that’sa bit more of a body high.Like relaxant.I think it’s better weed really.You can kind of function on it but italso just makes the world seem quite inspiring.I think that’s the thing that’s great for peoplewith schizophrenia to inspire them before I got arrestedand it has only fueled it wicked. Yeah.Of course I worked on nothing but that story.I think weed is brilliant.I used to smoke a lot of weeds.Now I’m actually coming back to working when Isay working for jobs for a few more daysand I have totally revamped my resume.I tidied up these couple of letters. Yeah, nice.And I just put together a little portfolio.I’ve got two more sentences to write for my resume.I totally just need actually no, thisone just goes straight out the door.I tidy up this resume pretty much PDF there.And another job.Another job the same.No, the other job is not the same.Bridges.Bridges are cool.Bridges are cool.I just know nothing about Kyle.It’s like different field, isn’t it?I don’t know how to design bridge.Bridges are so complex.I love suspension bridges though.Yeah.I think the engineering of bridges is insane.It’s really like captivating sometimes.Love those old like do you get fire dumps?I guess New Zealand architectureis quite modern, isn’t it?No, it’s not.Sorry.Yeah, but please tell me because that wasjust my like in the central business district.Yeah, sure.But this is like tidy. Yeah.And then the CBD, the central business district.Yeah.I should say it was only because I talkedto someone who did like a year like studyin New Zealand and they just stayed in thecapital outside of the heart of the city.Yeah.Side of the cities.Once you’re in the countryside, is there still, like, alot of kind of Maori influence in the countryside?Influence, yes.But what do you mean by likewhat do I mean by influence?Sorry.No, that’s all right.Maori influence. The Maori? Yeah.This is something I don’t like when I’m hired.Yeah, it’s a big thing as well.Of course. Yeah.Oh, my God.And but really, really?I need to use my phone.I need to speak to my phone.10 hours.810 hours.Yes, I was in the jail cell for ten.I wasn’t in the jail cell.Mostly I was in the water smoking cigarettes.I love the culture, cigarettes.And people just offer them, like, randomly.I bought, like, a kebab the other day, and the guyjust came out after I’d finished and gave me a cigarette.Quite nice.Anyway, I couldn’t couldn’t tellwhat’s nice about the water.Quite like officer column Scalar about.That was where you’re at.But then you said, wow, wanted toask him if it’s a nickname.He had it on his badge.He had it on his badge.That’s what they said.I wonder if any of them tried your snooze, you know,and they took it to the back and they like, brokepies and I wonder if they like, probably not.When I was outside in the park, we didn’t putone in my mouth, kind of since you use butthis one looks you have to have it fresh.Then three old ones at the top.I’ve never had it before.Yeah, never had it sneezed.This is a pretty can I try it tomorrow?It might keep me up.I think I think this is a pretty is it quite mellow?This is another strong one.I think it’s a five out of eight,for whatever that’s worth it you’ll get nice.I might have it tomorrow morning.I don’t think it should keepnicotine and you’re smoking cigarettes?Yeah, smoke quite a lot of cigarettes.Reminds me of these nicotine lozenges.Yeah, just just don’t swallow it.There was a guy I knew a guywho swallowed it and straight to the hospital. Really?You have to wash the what is it?Oh, my God. What is here?They need to wash his stomach out.They have to wash his stomach out because you die.I think this is not the strong but it was avery strong one he swallowed, and he could have died.Really?For example, if a dog or somethingeats it is to just die.Shocks your body. I have a question.If I don’t put it in the bed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yeah. Your stomach? Yeah.They have to wash his I think this is notthe strong, but it was a very strong one.He swallowed and he could have died. Really?For example, if a dog orsomething eats it shocks your body.I have a question.If I don’t put it in the bed buta dog will never eat it on purpose.Dog such a would eat it. Really?Maybe a Labrador.Yeah, but yeah, I knew some peoplewho just push it in the ass.I knew a girl who pushed it in his pussy,and she got such a nicotine shock that she wentstraight to the hospital because she was so shocked.She was like this, she couldn’t even move.You’re putting me off this sneeze but inthe mouth, it’s not like a strong one. I love it.Tomorrow sounds like quite strong.I think this is not strong, actually, but ifyou put it in your mouth, it’s actually nothing.I mean, sometimes I use it, soit’s I’m pretty experience with it.I’ve been using I’ve been using it on and off.I’ve been trying to quit.Trying to quit.I should yeah.I feel bad for a couple of times.There’s a top compartment.I don’t think a dog would eat that.It seems so sort of smells so toxic with the menpol.I don’t know.Officer Colbert in jail.I asked him what time it is.It’s 945.I asked to call my lawyer.I asked what his mind says, it’s about five minutes.And tell them I need to talk to my girlfriend.She thinks I can keep that for the mafia and says,you can’t use your phone and here, you’ll be done soon.Yeah, okay.At least let me charge and I take charger.I take a charger.Let me charge my phone and okay.I got to plug it in.It’s got six battery left.They put on airplane mode for me, which is actually kindof like I’m sure it was on an airplane before.And I quickly messaged, like, afriend like her, okay, I’m fine.I’ll be out of here pretty soon.I’m about to see my lawyer.Don’t worry about me. Sorry. Coming.I’ll talk to you soon.Story coming.And I quickly and I messaged my sister.I just said, Ask Lucy, and put my phone away.And he asked for my passport.He starts taking down notes, and he asked mea few really basic questions, given some shit aboutmy father’s name again, I should have anyway.And he eventually shortly pulls up one ofthe evidence blanks that’s sitting on the table.He asked me, what is this?And I might have said, a little bit.They kept you there for, like did yousay it’s like, 11 hours or something?I would have been in jail.I got picked up at about 111130, and I got out at 1145.Yeah.I don’t even know what this is.I’ve just been assumed. 12 hours?Yeah, that’s a long time.That was midday.Was it midday you got taken in?Or was it like midnight? Midnight. It’s midnight.So you’re up until the next day.That’s pretty savage.What did you do when you got out?Was that when you got here?Was it straight off, really?I went to the hospital, literally around the corner.And I sat down and I was like,fuck, all my shit is still here.Actually, somebody touched my stuff because thewaistband clip, it was clipped together, right?But nothing was there.That’s nice.Picked up my bag.Makes me wonder about, like, the Bathhost Stateacts like we stayed above just around thecorner, and me and Billy were sat.We’re like, we really need some camping gear.Like, whatever.I’m going to walk to the camping shop.It’ll be 2 hours, but it’s the best onein Toronto by the looks of the reviews.I was literally I was sat inthe garden talking to Billy about it.And then this guy was like having a cigarette.He works at a hostel.Just like at the end of the table.And I was like, hey, dude, I don’t suppose youknow anyone selling like cheap camping, like tents and stuff?He was like, I sell tents.I’ve got two tents.I’ve got a load of sleepingbags, roll, mads gas canisters.It’s just one of the guys who worked there.Yeah, well, let’s give you €100 for the lot.And literally yeah, sorry, there was two.We got 110 gas canister gas,but wasn’t fit the gas canister.So I told somebody the cards, theydidn’t fucking fit in the thing.So we got a sleeping bag, a roll mat and a tent.Yeah.It just made me think, like, that guyprobably just fucking nicked them from a hostel,stored them in the storeroom, and then justsold them to other people who came in.It just didn’t cross my mind when we bought it.But thinking about it because he ripped off as well.How many times could you get away with it?Yeah, how do you get away?Like, how many people’s stuff did he steal?I suppose maybe just steal once, I think. Yeah.Lots of people there say if the host load isreal on it as well, then someone lost my tent.They’ll be like, fuck.We checked the CCTV.We’ve done everything, whatever.We’ve only got one camera in the garden.We haven’t seen anyone take it.I’d be like, fuck it.Some guests just run off my stuff.No one would ever check in on the hostel too much.Yeah, that guy just fucking nicked all ofour camping gear and sold it to me.Poor wanker.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;55.46&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Really fed up guys in the park we hadto wait for the bus like 9 hours.They just sat under a tree because itwas raining so much and then all theguys would usually hang out in the park.We’re all together so we’re like sharing beers.None of them get any English really apart from one guy.It was so cool.Kind of like we were all doing for growing together.They spake something off the back.This is you use for crack?No, I remember.You need anything like we crack place to stay?Just come.I actually invited of the guys backto Brighton with me very much.Yeah that was really nice exchange.Yeah when I went to Iraq fromoffrid I have to change buses.Which city was it?My girlfriend asked me to write her poem.I said what do you want me to do for you?And she said I want you to write me a poem.And this was months ago and I gave a shit about noway but I’m going to write her maybe I was thinking alove poem but it doesn’t actually have to be a love poem.It can be anything.Yeah she’s read that.She’s read that of course actuallyshe’s read most of my stories.Do you have like she helped me write one in German.Where are you from?I’m from New Zealand.Yes I know I talked to them as well.Yes, they were sorry I was busyworking on my laptop at the time.Yeah amazing.Definitely like getting on really well. Yeah.Sorry where did you meet them?To where? Scorpio. Scorpio? Macedonia.Oh, I haven’t seen Macedonia on a map yet.I know, it’s just Easter member I can’t even pictureit yet like not very nice group just hanging aroundlike seven people go to the canyon there and everythingand then went together to offer and spent lots oftime together and now they are here.Some of the guys from there will come here.I’m very happy because they are very nice.How long they stay for?Two nights cool. Yeah.Going out for drink or something?Yeah do it.But you’re going to stop working here and stay here?Is that the idea?But tomorrow is my day off tomorrow.I’ve got a day off tomorrow.Yeah so I thought I mightjust spend the day like painting.Oh this is a good idea.I think it would just be a nice thing to leave.I mean you have to do it.Yeah promised you leo, you can likea clay head at this stage.I hate it when people promise me thingsand they deliver on them like this gift.Are the gifts going to happen?I’ll do it before I go.Yeah I’ll do it in like four years.No you do it in 100 years.It’s not going to be so I’m going to make himthe head paint in there and maybe make head of brain.Yeah, maybe their son be met. Their son?His son, yeah, her son Brainer.Well, both of their best friends.The little one yeah, he’s funny.The little one is 14 as well. Oh, sorry.The youngest son.The youngest one.No, I haven’t seen I mean, I haveseen one his once, but no, I haven’t.So for a little bit of contextbecause I never I’m sitting outside openair concert and enjoying enjoying the atmosphere.I’ve been working with my family and talking withgoing out and doing things in the city Iwouldn’t throw fucking so happy with it.And I’m sitting there writing and the police don’twant to see what’s in my self explanatory.And I forgot three that just popped off the top.Yeah, good game.Let’s go get fucking shitting.And then we should pop that up again.Flip this off, grab WEEDO.Take me to jail.I call my girlfriend.I call my girlfriend while we’re outside.This is at the park half a kilometer west. Yeah.There was an open air concert on Sunday night.On Saturday?Sunday calling no where else?I call my girlfriend, she’s like,no idea what’s going on.And they take me to jail.And welcome to jail.More to be interesting things.I make a phone call tonight.Oh, it’s not detecting the audio wouldbe really lovely if it was.I’m gonna hold on to it.What was I saying?They let me call my girlfriend again.The first call I made outside was 11:45 p.m..The last call I made to my girlfriend was twelve two.The last time I talked toanybody outside was twelve two.And she we’re shitting ourselves.Like, are these guys a fucking mafia?Actually, we were wondering this outside.These guys are fucking mafia.Pardon?Okay, so it was.&lt;/p&gt;

          </description>
          <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
          <link>http://localhost:4000/Late-Night-Chats-with-Joe.html</link>
          <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/Late-Night-Chats-with-Joe.html</guid>
          
          
        </item>
      
    
      
        <item>
          
            <title>Die Kleinen Dinge&lt;br&gt;Ein Schreiben an Lucia&apos;s Vermieter</title>
          
          <author>fakeemail@gmail.com (Kauri's BS)</author>
          <description>
            &lt;h5 id=&quot;donnerstag-15-juni&quot;&gt;Donnerstag 15 Juni&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sehr geehrter Georg,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Ich habe über unseres Gespräch am Mittwoch nachgedacht. Das Gruppentreffen war notwendig - Lucia und ich habe die Köchen in ein inakzeptabel Status verlassen; nicht leer bins, ein paar schmutzig Tellern bei den Spüle verlessen. Es war den Weckruf wir gebraucht haben nachdem eine außergewöhnlich fleißig Nacht.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Sie sind Recht; wir solten die Küche die ganze Zeit fleckenfrei verlassen, aber insbesondere wann sie werde aus dem Urlaub zurückkehrer. Obgleich, Ich hoffe sie haben zum Häus mit fraiche lebensmittel zurückkehrer schätzen. Weil wann Sie letzte Mittwoch für Urlaub verlessen, Lucia habt Zuhause Rückkhern zu finden ranzig Milch, verrottend Paprikas in den Kühlschrank, und die Apfel, mehr ahnlich Kompost. Ahnlich die Restlichen, Sie werde wahrscheinlich nie wissen. Es ist nur eine der kleinen Dinge.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Sie sind Recht; als ein Gast für eine Woche, ich solte über der kleinen Dinge um das Haus mehr aufpassen, um die Tastache zu kompensieren, dass ich trinke deine Kaffee und miete nicht kaufen. Nachte Zeit ich werde sicherstellen zu sagen ihnen wenn ich die Toilette putzen, wenn ich gefallene Wäsche weider aufhänge, oder wenn ich wasche die schmutzig Tellern das Sie auf der Arbeitsplatte verlassen. Ich werde ihnen die Quittung für die Milch und Hafern und fraische Gemüse ich gekauft habe zeigen. Ich werde weiterhin zu anbeiten ihnen Abendessen, auch wenn die letzte zwei Zeit sie habe nicht ein Bisschen gegessen. Ich möchte nicht ein Schmarotzer weidergelten!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Sie sind Recht, in eine Garage mit acht Fahrrades und eine rostig Tischtennisplatte, Lucia&lt;strong&gt;’s&lt;/strong&gt; Fahrrad ist sehr unbequem; es viel zu viel Platz einnehmen. Beraten Sie ihr, wegbringen Sie es! Oh, und stören Sie nicht zu anbeiten irgendwelche auffällig Ausweg &lt;strong&gt;either&lt;/strong&gt;. Und wenn sie beherzigt es, und dezidiert das gleich Tag zu finden ein Ausweg… “Oh, was mascht du? Ich habe nicht es gemeint zu jetzt es machen!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Es ist nur ein kleinen Dinge, die weg Sie sprechen zu Leute. Intolerant, gefühllos, gefühllos; dennoch irgendwie so emotional. Es must nett sein zu Mitbewohner-Vermeiter sein. Du bist gleich, Sie sind überlegen. Was auch immer bequemer? Ich empfehlen Sie aus das Has von Deine Mutter und Fater nicht ausrücken - vile wenn Sie alles die Macht nicht halten, Sie sind am Arsch.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Ich aufgehe ich genau nicht gesagt habe, danke für die Gastfreundschaft. Nachte Zeit ich werde die Mülleimer für ihnen auch leeren.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Grüße,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Kauri&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
P.s: Enschuldigung ich habe nicht ihnen gezagt über meinen kommend Reiseplans bis Sie gefragt.&lt;/p&gt;

          </description>
          <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
          <link>http://localhost:4000/Ein-Schreiben-an-Lucia's-Vermieter.html</link>
          <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/Ein-Schreiben-an-Lucia's-Vermieter.html</guid>
          
          
        </item>
      
    
      
        <item>
          
            <title>The Little Things&lt;br&gt;A Letter to Lucia&apos;s Landlord</title>
          
          <author>fakeemail@gmail.com (Kauri's BS)</author>
          <description>
            &lt;h5 id=&quot;thursday-15th-june&quot;&gt;Thursday 15th June&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dear Georg,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
I’ve been reflecting on our conversation on Wednesday. The group meeting was really needed – Lucia and I did leave the kitchen in an unacceptable state; unemptied bins, a few dishes forgotten by the sink. It was exactly the wake-up call we needed after an exceptionally busy night.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
You are right; we should leave the kitchen spotless at all times, but especially when you are coming back from holiday. Though, I do hope you appreciated coming back to a house stocked with fresh food. Because when you left for holiday last Wednesday, Lucia arrived home to find rancid milk, peppers rotting in the fridge, and the apples, more like compost. Like the rest, you’ll probably never know. It’s just one of those little things.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
You are right; as a guest for one week, I should take more care of the little things around the house, to make up for the fact that I drink your coffee and don’t pay rent. Next time I’ll make sure to tell you  when I clean the toilet, when I rehang laundry fallen to the floor, or when I wash the dirty dishes you’ve left on the counter. I’m going to show you the receipt for the milk and oats and fresh vegetables I buy. I’ll keep offering you dinner, even though the last two times you didn’t eat any of it. I sure wouldn’t want to be called a freeloader again!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
You are right; in a garage with eight bikes, two cars and a rusty ping-pong table, Lucia’s second bike is incredibly inconvenient; it’s taking up far too much space. Berate her, take it away! Oh, and don’t bother offering any obvious solutions either. And when she takes it to heart and decides to find a solution the same day… “Oh, what are you doing? I didn’t mean for you to do it right now!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
It’s just a little thing, the way you talk to people. Intolerant, unempathetic, callous; yet somehow so emotional. It must be nice being flatmate-landlord. You’re an equal, you’re superior. Whatever’s more convenient? I suggest you don’t move out of mum and dad’s old home – because when you don’t hold all the power, you’re fucked.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
I realize I haven’t properly said, thanks for the hospitality. Next time I’ll empty the bins for you too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Cheers,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Kauri&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
P.s: Sorry for not telling you my upcoming travel plans until you asked.&lt;/p&gt;

          </description>
          <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
          <link>http://localhost:4000/A-Letter-to-Lucia's-Landlord-copy.html</link>
          <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/A-Letter-to-Lucia's-Landlord-copy.html</guid>
          
          
        </item>
      
    
      
        <item>
          
            <title>Hitchhiking 600km for a dentist appointment</title>
          
          <author>fakeemail@gmail.com (Kauri's BS)</author>
          <description>
            &lt;h5 id=&quot;foreword&quot;&gt;Foreword&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Actually, this one is an English translation. You can read the &lt;a href=&quot;/Fahren-600km-mit-Anhalter-für-einen-Zahnarzttermin.html&quot;&gt;German Original here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;wednesday-7th-june&quot;&gt;Wednesday 7th June&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Three weeks ago I sent an email to a dental practice in Munich. To this dental practice, to eight others too. These practices replied immediately. Rather generic and impersonal response, to a rather specific email. Suspect, for a Friday afternoon….&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I put it on the back burner, and waited two weeks. The responses were overwhelming - with a grand tota of… zero responses. So, in the middle of some Polish bush, using the last of all my batteries, I started calling each dental office. No answer, no English, the dentist is on vacation. I book an appointment, 21st June, for a short initial consultation… 21 June!? How long might I have to wait for the actual procedures?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I thought back about Alldent. Immediate answer. I could have a booking just two days in advance. I’ll come to Munich to see Lucia. Oh, I find out, Lucia will not be there. Fuck it! How many people can say they hitchhiked 600km for a dentist appointment?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was not a simple 600km. Challenges with hitchhiking, a hammock torn in two, an epic battle with the mosquitoes - but these are stories for another time. On to Munich! To make good time, in the morning I took the regional train to the city. Remember, I gave them all the information - a report from my dentist in New Zealand, including Xrays, technical details for the implant buried under my gums, and an explanation of the remaining procedure - Restoration and Crowning. It’s an international standard system.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I arrive early, fill out the paperwork, and sit in the lobby for 30 minutes. They finally call me to the dentist. We talk and, within 30 seconds he tells me, “We can’t crown a third-party implant. It’s a liability issue, a risk we’re not allowed to take.” 30 seconds, 30 euro. Fuck off, why didn’t these wankers just tell me that on the phone!?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, long story short, I am now in a youth hostel waiting for Lucie. I have to stay in Munich tomorrow for another appointment with another doctor. We talked a lot on the phone, and at least they implied that they could complete the procedures. Wish me luck!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;friday-9th-june&quot;&gt;Friday 9th June&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Future update: It was good! There is a few details to sort out, but I think I will continue with them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;sunday-25th-september&quot;&gt;Sunday 25th September&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The last dentists in Germany wanted three-bloody-thousand euro! After scrutinizing their quotes, I decided to wait. Just ten-thousand kilometres later…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here in Tirana, Albania I was given a fixed quote at 1/3 of the price. Fast, good communication, excellent quality of work. Within a week of arriving I had my brand new tooth. I’m currently volunteering in a beautiful hostel here in Tirana, with a big new smile - but that’s a story for another time!&lt;/p&gt;

          </description>
          <pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
          <link>http://localhost:4000/Hitchhiking-600km-for-a-dentist-appointment.html</link>
          <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/Hitchhiking-600km-for-a-dentist-appointment.html</guid>
          
          
        </item>
      
    
      
        <item>
          
            <title>Fahren 600km per Anhalter für einen Zahnarzttermin</title>
          
          <author>fakeemail@gmail.com (Kauri's BS)</author>
          <description>
            &lt;h5 id=&quot;vorwort&quot;&gt;Vorwort&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wirklich, diese Geschicte ist ein Deutsches Original. Falls sie konnen auch ein Rechtschreibfehler oder Grammaticalischproblem finden, ich werde Sie eine Medaille geben.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;mittwoch-7-juni&quot;&gt;Mittwoch 7 Juni&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Drei wochen hinter ich habe ein Email zu einer Zahnarztpraxen in München gesendet. Zu dieser Zahnarztpraxen, zu acht andere auch. Dieser Praxen haben sofort geantwortet. Eher generisch und unpersönalich Antwort, zu ein sehr spezifisch Email. Suspekt, für ein Fritag nachmittag…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ich haben das auf Sparflamme stellen, und zwei Wochen gewartet, zu sehen viele Antworten, eine große Summe von… null. So, in den Mitte von manche Polnischer Busch, mit den letzten von meiner Batterei, ich fing an alles die Zahnarztpraxen anrufen. Kein Antwort, kein Englisch, der Zahnarzt ist im Urlaub. Ich hole ein Termin… 21 Juni… für erst eine kurze Initiale Beratung… 21 Juni!? Wie lang denn muss ich warten für die richtige Abläufe?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ich habe züruck über Alldent gedacht. Sofort Antwort. Ich könnte eine Buchung nur zwei Tagen im vorous haben. Leck mich am Arsch, ich werde nach München kommen zu sehen Lucia. Oh, aber, Lucia werde nicht da sein. Scheiß drauf! Wie viele Leute konnen sagen Sie 600km per Anhalter gefahren für einen Zahnarzttermin haben?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Es war nicht ein einfach 600km. Aufgaben mit Anhalter fahren, eine Hangingmatte in zwei gerissen, ein epischer Kampf mit die Mücken. Aber diese sind Geschichten für ein anderes Zeit. Nach München! Zu machen am Morgen gut Zeit ich habe das Regionalbahn nach die Stadt genommen. Bedenken Sie, ich habe alles Information ihnen gegeben – einen Bericht aus mein Zahnarzt in Neuseeland, mit Xrays, mit technische Erläuterung von die Implant unter meinem Zahnfleisch begraben, mit Erläuterung von die restlicken Verfahren – Restoration and Crowning. Ein internationals Standardsystem.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ich früh komme an, fulle den Papierkram, warte für 30 Minuten. Sie fragen mir endlich, der Zahnarzt kommt. Wir reden und, immerhalb 30 Sekunden er erzählet mir, “Wir konnen ein Drittzahnimplantat nicht Kronen. Es ist einen liability Haftungaspekte, ein Risiko wir nicht nehmen konnen.”  Leck mich am Arsch! Warum haben diese Wischern mich nicht bei das Telefon sagen?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, lang Geschichte kurz, ich bin jetzt in ein Jugendherberge, warte for Lucie, und muss morgen in München beliben für einen anderen Termin mit einen anderen Doktor. Ich habe viel angerufet, und Sie haben mindestens impliziert das Sie die Verfahren machen konnen. Wunschen mir Glück!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;freitag-9-juni&quot;&gt;Freitag 9 Juni&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, lang Geschichte kurz, ich bin jetzt in ein Jugendherberge, warte for Lucie, und muss morgen in München beliben für einen anderen Termin mit einen anderen Doktor. Ich habe viel angerufet, und Sie haben mindestens impliziert das Sie die Verfahren machen konnen. Wunschen mir Glück!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;sonntag-25th-september&quot;&gt;Sonntag 25th September&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Die letzte Zahnarzt in München mochten drei thousand euro, und nachdem ich habe ihre Angebot unter die Lupe genommen, ich beschloss zu warten, zu warten nur zehntausend Kilometer mehr.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hier in Tirana, Albanien, ich habe einen fixed Festpreisangebot erhalte, nur einen Drittel von den Preis. Schnell, gute Kommunikation, exzellente Qualität der Arbeit. Innerhalb einer Woche, ich hette mein brand neu Zahn. Jetzt ich Freiwillinger in einen schön Jugendherberge in Tirana zu arbeiten, mit ein groß neu Lächeln - aber das ist ein Geschichte für ein ander Zeit!&lt;/p&gt;

          </description>
          <pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
          <link>http://localhost:4000/Fahren-600km-mit-Anhalter-f%C3%BCr-einen-Zahnarzttermin.html</link>
          <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/Fahren-600km-mit-Anhalter-f%C3%BCr-einen-Zahnarzttermin.html</guid>
          
          
        </item>
      
    
      
        <item>
          
            <title>Asymmetrical Warfare</title>
          
          <author>fakeemail@gmail.com (Kauri's BS)</author>
          <description>
            &lt;h3 id=&quot;part-i&quot;&gt;Part I&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I didn’t even bother with my bugnet. The initial wave may have just been the scouts, but my defences were ready. For thirty minutes, the aerial ninjas intimidated and mercilessly drew blood, however their ranks sustained heavy casualties. Those stealthy enough to remain undetected flew home on a full belly, but after hearing of the decimation of their peers, the full ranks decided not to advance. Only the occasional hungry nomadic wanderer stumbled through, with whom I shared an intimate connection, freely offering sustenance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;part-ii&quot;&gt;Part II&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;\assets\images\warfare_jogenheim.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;warfare_jogenheim&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;12am at Jogenheim National Park, Norway.&lt;/figcaption&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Two unwitting fools sought out the perfect campsite stumble around the foothills of the mountain they’d climb tomorrow. He left to gather some wood, and returned to find her bewildered, surrounded by a cloud of nightmares. This was their territory. Wherever the fools went, nightmares followed. There was no escape.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Tonight the warriors would not sleep under the stars, nor would they forfeit. They camouflaged their skin with a heavy-duty gel brought from New Zealand, brought just for this day. They set up their fortress, the primary defensive structure, where they would take shelter during the night. But the weary warriors needed nourishment, and their fortress sat idly by.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
They got to cooking, but the smell of another juicy meal only lured more attackers. Their numbers were overwhelming. In one casual leg-slap, five passed, five more joined. They darted into the most unwelcome of places. One had to take care breathing, lest they may find themselves breathing more than air. The pasta, one could no longer call it vegetarian.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Entering the fortress was no easy task. To prepare, they packed their bags completely and waited a while, twenty metres away. The lure worked. They made a mad dash, with her diving headfirst, followed by flying bags, a second pair of lanky legs, a zipper furiously closed, a copious, contagious laughter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Peace.&lt;/p&gt;

          </description>
          <pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
          <link>http://localhost:4000/Asymmetrical-warfare.html</link>
          <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/Asymmetrical-warfare.html</guid>
          
          
        </item>
      
    
      
        <item>
          
            <title>Marseilles is not the same as Versailles</title>
          
          <author>fakeemail@gmail.com (Kauri's BS)</author>
          <description>
            &lt;h5 id=&quot;thursday-13th-april&quot;&gt;Thursday 13th April&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was sitting atop a little hill in the middle of a roundabout, making lunch, overlooking the quiet roads, enjoying the view of the distant rolling hills. “Wait, is that a pack cover? That’s a bloody hitchhiker!” He stepped out of the car near the roundabout, a young Frenchman. We chatted over a couple dry sandwiches. He had a week off work, to go hiking, camping and surfing. We were both headed to Bordeaux and the West Coast, and decided to try travel together together… I figured, surely with two people, two guys none the less, it &lt;strong&gt;must&lt;/strong&gt; be harder. I was utterly stunned when literally the first car to drive by stopped.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Seems many people in this area only speak French, so having Arthur to translate was a big bonus. He is a brilliant conversationalist, always talking to people and making them laugh. We are similar in many ways, and got along well. After waiting for fifteen minutes on a bus with no driver, we decided there must be cameras; they’re just fucking with us. That’s what we’d do, if we had control. Fuck with people. I pull out one of Callum’s standard lines; “What would you do if you were a dictator?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course, it’s important that people are highly educated. Everybody would have to study math for one hour a day. It’s important that the government is transparent with its people. The government website would have the answer to literally anything you, a citizen, might need. All the laws and the regulations, the bus timetables, the answers to the weekly math test. It’s all there, everything, on the home page. The only page. Ctrl-f would zoom in.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We were dropped at a major toll booth and waited for ~15 minutes for someone to stop. Arthur chatted up the driver, then asked me, “Do you want to go to the coast, or do you want to go to Marseilles?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With a little hesitation – “Fuck it – let’s go to Marseilles!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We squeezed into this raggedy little car, five people, my head cocked against the ceiling. Almost immediately, we took a wrong turn. We were headed backwards, to Lyon, where Arthur had started his journey. It didn’t take me long to realize Versailles and Marseilles are not the same place…
Fuck it, be like the wind.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our driver was kind, and dropped us near the base of Mont Carpiagne. A fair deal, in exchange to listening to your mix tapes for two hours. It took us three hours to the peak, including detours and exploration. But considering that, despite our giant backpacks we kept pace with a large group of joggers, your mileage may vary.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With a stunning 270° sunset – sunrise view of the city, and pitched camp nearby, the wind battering us, howling. I strapped up between the legs of a power pylon, uneven ground, with one end of the tarp a good metre above the ground. I knew it was a bad idea – but determined to have the coolest-ever-hammock setup, and armed with Arthur’s rock-stacking alternative to pegs, my stubborn ass stood ground.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;\assets\images\marseilles_hammock_sunset.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;marseilles_hammock_sunset&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Look out for the stubborn monkey!&lt;/figcaption&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;friday-14th-april&quot;&gt;Friday 14th April&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3.00 am – One of the tarpaulin tie-downs snaps. The flapping tarp wakes me up. I secure it to my backpack.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3.15 am – The adjacent tie-down breaks. The lazy fucker I am, I knot it around my feet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3.45 am – My butt is freezing. Something has shifted, I’m not certain how. I restack some rocks upwind.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;6.00 am – I need a piss. I can’t leave my hammock without the tarpaulin going haywire, so I decide to pack down. I notice, those rocks I restacked… one of those lines is broken too, but by some miracle it still held together. I’m not sure even I understand how that could happen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;6:05 am – I discover the fourth upwind line has broken too. This one broke in-between the shock cord, which is how it’s intended to work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
The next day, the lady in the outdoor store is confused as to why on earth I need ten metres of this specific camping line. She was rather sweet, and gave us an amazing camping recommendation!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We climbed back down the mountain towards the city, wandered the streets of Marseilles, went for a swim, and retired in the prettiest hostel I’ve ever seen. [Editor’s note: I really should have written more about Marseilles, but alas.]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;saturday-15th-april&quot;&gt;Saturday 15th April&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We went on to Montparnasse and did much of the same – though far prettier a city! We set up camp  at a local rock-climbing place, just a short bus ride on the city outskirts. After a few drinks at the top of the baby cliff, Arthur said something I shall not forget. “Your mind is like a garden. The more you nurture it, the more it will grow, the more resilient it will become. You must plant it with solid, diverse, healthy plants, such that even in absence of conscious effort, it can continue to flourish, a stable ecosystem.” Easier said than done?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;sunday-16th-april&quot;&gt;Sunday 16th April&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Arthur and I split ways in the morning. It’s late here at the train station in Perpignan, “the centre of the universe”. I’m prepared to find these secret hot pools, deep in the Pyrenees Mountains.&lt;/p&gt;

          </description>
          <pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
          <link>http://localhost:4000/Marseilles-is-not-the-same-as-Versailles.html</link>
          <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/Marseilles-is-not-the-same-as-Versailles.html</guid>
          
          
        </item>
      
    
      
        <item>
          
            <title>Draft&amp;#58; Today I Fucked Up&amp;#58; Hammock</title>
          
          <author>fakeemail@gmail.com (Kauri's BS)</author>
          <description>
            &lt;p&gt;Needs a better title&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;friday-26th-june&quot;&gt;Friday 26th June&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, technically I fucked up three weeks ago when I put my name on the delivery for a rather special type of fabric. Or maybe I fucked up when I put a little hole in my hammock, or when I thought Decathlon had the solution. In any case, a culmination of little fuck-ups has led me to sleeping on the ground for the next month.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Travelling by hitchhike, you have to be flexible. I don’t always know where I’m going to sleep. Sometimes it’s with friends, sometimes with strangers, but my hammock has been the shining star. Though I usually take time to find a beautiful spot, in a pinch it sets up almost anywhere with two trees. And if there’s no trees, then a power pylon… but that’s another story. It’s quick to set up, warm, more comfortable than my own bed. By -5° I’m getting too cold. Made of a particular material specifically designed for hammocks - strong, lightweight, breathable. Flammable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;\assets\images\hammock_example.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;hammock_example&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt; A pretty typical hammock setup. Tarpaulin above for the rain and wind, underquilt beneath for insulation.&lt;/figcaption&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first fuckup occurred in Salzberg, Austria. I stayed in a hostel a couple nights to sort out some admin. Regrettably, I hardly saw the city, other than on a couple runs. Regrettably, I forgot to stock up on gas for my camping stove; key for dinners and coffee. I was running critically low, and didn’t even realize.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first night back on the road, I headed to Obenburgau, at the base of of Schafberg, a mountain in Austria. Tomorrow I’d do a mountain crossing - but tonight, well, I’d found in the foothills a cave overlooking a roaring waterfall. There’s no good trees in this cave; fuck the hammock.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;\assets\images\Hammock_schlafberg_waterfall.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;hammock_schlafberg_waterfall&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;In hindsight, I should have considered the hearing damage - though it didn&apos;t stop me falling asleep!&lt;/figcaption&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now I’ve just noticed the gas situation. I’m hungry, I want some bloody pasta! No problem - I’ll save it, I’m going to build a campfire instead. Tomorrow will be Saturday, and you’d better make pace tomorrow and get to the other side of this mountain - because on Sunday, because fucking Germany, everything’s closed. The Monday’s a public holiday too. I’ll save the last dregs of gas for coffee tomorrow morning.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;saturday-27th-june&quot;&gt;Saturday 27th June&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;discuss the hike more!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Schlafberg – gorgeous, gruelling. One-way crossing, lake-to-lake. Nice to get the legs properly working. Not so many people on the trail, but you get to the top, and there’s everybody and their mum. Literally. A cable car takes you to the restaurant at the top! A skifield in winter, bustling it seems. And for good reason – 360 degree views of the Lakes, the Alps, Austrian towns.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Magnificent views from the top! I hiked down the other side to St Wolfgang at reasonable pace too, to catch the shops before they closed. Time crunch to make it back to town, St Wolfgang. There’s an outdoor store there, I’ll top up my gas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Actually, I do take an hour-long nap on the trail. I hear noisy, obnoxious people draw closer – and decide not to be stuck behind them. At one point I waited for a few moments for some others to catch up, at an intersection between an unpaved road, and a typical forest path. I asked them which was faster to St Wolfgang – more an icebreaker than a genuine question. They switched to English, and he said, in all seriousness, “We are going this way, but considering the shoes you’re wearing, maybe you should go the other way.” HI was, jogging down a gnarly mountain with my giant backpack, and I’m told my shoes are inadequate? Do I look like such a rookie? They only caught up with me because I took a 30 minute nap on a log! Stunned, all I could muster was a lousy “Come on?” I followed them briefly down the forest trail, then pulled a controlled jog-slide down a short, steep bypass, leaving them in the dust. Though, the rest of the walk I only felt embarrassment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I made it to St Wolfgang before the outdoor store closed. And who would have known, the only outdoor store in this down doesn’t sell gas. Bother. Well, There’s one supermarket here - I’ll eat cold for the meanwhile – better stock up! What do I need - fresh fruit, cheese, bread, spread, salami… Those few minutes writing down a shopping list ticked me over to 5:01pm, and supermarket closed its doors. For fucks sake.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I went for a swim in the lake, then ordered myself a large pizza.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;monday-29th-june&quot;&gt;Monday 29th June&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The mesmeric lighting, comforting warmth, smoky atmosphere, delightful smell, the humble crackle. Fuck, I love fire.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m strung up in my hammock in a nicely wooded area, nearby some creepy abandoned building in Germany. I’ve gotten pretty good at cooking myself one-pot meals. Recipe: Fry onions, capsicum and garlic until onions turn gold. Add herbs &amp;amp; spices per preference. Add water and bring to boil, add carb of choice, stir, boil, drain. Optional extras include pasta sauce, cheese, salami, chickpeas, beans, vegetables of choice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most of the time I’m carrying two-to-three day supply of food. I ate the last of my fresh food today. I’m hungry. These days I’m always hungry (Editor’s note: hungry in a good way - I’m not bloody starving myself!) Cold coffee and cheese-salami this morning just hasn’t cut it. Let’s fucking cook us a meal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All that to say, I made a little campfire. It was a crackly one, and I definitely built it too close. One stray ember put a garlic-sized hole in my hammock, an onion-shaped tear in my eye. I’m going to sleep in my hammock, a paranoid statue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;sunday-4th-june&quot;&gt;Sunday 4th June&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The last week I’ve been in Poznan, Poland to celebrate my friend Sachin’s graduation. During that time I ordered a sheet of Hexon 1.6, hammock material, to Lucia’s place in Munich. With it coming from the USA, the shipping time is uncertain. So, the other day I popped into a Decathlon for some repair patches.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;\assets\images\hammock_graduation.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;hammock_graduation&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;kjhlkjh&lt;/figcaption&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This evening I found a lovely spot by a river beach near Bamberg, Germany, and set up shop. I went for a run upstream, then swam back down. Then I retired into my hammock, and – RIIIIP!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;\assets\images\hammock_tear.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;hammock_tear&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;&quot;I&apos;ll just use a Decathlon repair patch.&quot;&lt;/figcaption&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In slow motion, I felt myself fall, my ass hitting the soft sandy floor. Defeated, I lay down on the ground beneath me, contemplating my choices in life, blissfully unaware of the brewing storm - the Battle Against the Mosquitoes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;date-must-have-been-a-weekday--1-day&quot;&gt;date? must have been a weekday + 1 day&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After a couple nights on the ground, I made it to Munich, where I waited out the timer. In this time I co-authored a research paper, aced my GMAT (General Management Admissions Test, generally used for MBA admission) and found a new bone to pick with Lucia’s pretentious landlord-flatmate. Oh, and I ordered a replacement keyboard for my surface, too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s been too long in the city, I’ve been itching to head back into the Bavarian Alps. I’ve studied the maps as usual, and there’s so many options for multi-day hikes. I need my hammock material. I pack my bags and plan to go bivvy mode, but the material, it arrives! Well, it being a slip of paper in the mailbox. Excuse me? I was at home, ya lazy bugger. Alright, let’s go to the PO Box three kilometeres away.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;\assets\images\hammock_bivvy_mode.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;hammock_bivvy_mode&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;funny caption&lt;/figcaption&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lucia accompanies me, her name on the slip. We open the PO Box and, aha! A box, printed with “the United States Postal Service”! It’s rather large and heavy, for a bit of material. Precious stuff, amirite? We head to a coffee shop nearby to relax, bringing the average age down at least a decade. We chat, and then open the box, full of paper shreds threatening to blow away in the wind. The waitress finally takes our coffee order, and help us chase down the stragglers. The look on Lucia’s face as she unveils the bubblewrap. A keyboard!?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We check the shipping label, sent from Berlin. This motherfucker had used an old USPS box from a shipment from Berlin! Bewildered, I check the shipment tracking details again, to discover, despite having been made two weeks apart, both shipments had been delivered at the exact same time. That means only one thing: the hammock material must still be in the PO Box! Our coffees arrive, and we smash them faster than two bored bunnies could, and say bye-bye to the wait staff. I wonder what they thought. Worst - or best date ever?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course, we can’t open the PO Box again. Eventually we get some help on the phone, but they would have to open it tomorrow. Bear in mind, this whole time I’m carrying my rucksack, ready to jump on the next train out of Munich. And there’s no way I’m allowed to stay another night with Lucia’s landlord breathing down her neck. Fuck’s sake. We call again to get more clarity, wandering the street as we wait on hold, transferred between departments. Eventually Lucia gives them the international tracking code, and I see her face drop…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Oh, nein, nein, nein, nein, nein, nein nein!” Her tone immediately shifts to one of urgency. After some back-and-forth, she asks the other side to wait. She explains, “The mailman tried to deliver it, but couldn’t see your name on the mailbox. It’s going to be shipped back to the States; there’s nothing she can do!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I take my pack off and collapse on the sidewalk. What the fuck is this bureaucracy? The package is still in Munich but, but what? Your system is so fucking automated you can’t pull a product off the shelf? This fucking mailman - you didn’t even knock! I was there, an open window apart, working on my laptop - you can literally see me from the road! This package flew halfway across the world, to make it less than five metres away… No email, no notification, not even an update in the tracking system, which just says… “Delivered at 3:29pm.” Well fuck you too!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m writing from my farmland campsite in the mountains of Immerstadt, with the most brilliant view of tomorrow’s mountains. I do now have Lucia’s inflatable mattress, compact little thing, which I only brought after much heated debate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;\assets\images\hammock_ground_campsite.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;hammock_ground_campsite&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Tomorrow&apos;s mountain hike&lt;/figcaption&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“But I’m TOUGH! How will anyone know how TOUGH I am if I choose to bring a sleeping mat?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“…What the fuck is wrong with you?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Her argument did not resonate, but I lost that game of Paper, Scissors, Rock.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;date-&quot;&gt;date ??&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My plan was flawed anyway. It took me three hours of stitching to realize;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1) I barely know how to handstitch
2) Even if I knew how to handstitch, I don’t have the time for this; it’s going to take forever!
3) Even if I had the time to handstitch, I have no bloody idea if this is going to work at all!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bear in mind, this tear is almost the entire width of the hammock, and it goes under a lot of stress, 100% of which needs to be transferred through the patch. This wonky backstitch just isn’t going to cut it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A shitty 10€ hammock from Kiwi (a supermarket chain in Norway) carried me through the next month, until I arrived at Cologne to stay with Lucia’s family. I must say a big thankyou to Lucia’s mother, who took it into the tailor for me. And to my surprise, it’s still holding on!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;\assets\images\hammock_patch.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;hammock_patch&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;funny caption&lt;/figcaption&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;\assets\images\hammock_croatia.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;hammock_croatia&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Another sunset with my hammock.&lt;/figcaption&gt;

          </description>
          <pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
          <link>http://localhost:4000/TIFU-Hammock.html</link>
          <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/TIFU-Hammock.html</guid>
          
          
        </item>
      
    
      
        <item>
          
            <title>Experience at Milingona Hostel&lt;br&gt;Part 1</title>
          
          <author>fakeemail@gmail.com (Kauri's BS)</author>
          <description>
            &lt;p&gt;Day 1 Hitchhike in, stay in shithole
Day 2 Dentist appt 1, stay in shithole
Day 3 Shithole
Day 4 Move to Apartment
Day 5 Jail cell.
Day 6 Monday 18th September. Milingona. Temporary crowns installed. 
Day 7 Milingona: Permanent crowns installed.
Day 8 Milingona: Minor adjustment to bite, and completely happy. Technically now I’m ready to leave Tirana. Finished first draft of Arrested by the Albanian Mafia.
Day 9 Milingona: Thursday 21st September, sitting at hostel working. Talked to Joe about working there. Talk verona in morning. 
Day 10 Milingona: Man in my bed. Hike with Joe. Confusion in evening, solve. Speak with Verona about working there.
Day 11 Milingona: Saturday 23rd September: Verona busy in morning. Start working there.
Day 12 Milingona:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;part-1-title&quot;&gt;Part 1: title&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;tuesday-19th-september&quot;&gt;Tuesday 19th September&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve been in Tirana for six days now. Albania feels a little bit lawless, a mentality of, you do whatever you want. The people are remarkably calm, certainly used to the nature of chaos. People are laid-back; they take life slowly, and value their leisure highly. They seem remarkably humble, often carring big smiles. It is natural to be part of the community.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The city is a reflection. It feels rather mickey-mouse, with the most chaotic of infrastructure - mickey-mouse architecture, spaghetti power lines, a brown river snaking through the city. We joke about construction in New Zealand, but I have almost never seen a construction worker in any of these high-rise buildings under construction in the centre, and the nature of construction has some questionabilities. I believe embezzlement and corruption play some part in the failure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The bus systems make little sense - inter-city buses are private only, and like the inner-city buses, it is nigh impossible to find good information. Every ten minutes you walk across another set of garbage bins emitting a foul smell, aging trash lining the surrounding street in greater quantity than usual. Policemen stand at intersections, indiscrimiately blowing their whistle while pretending to direct the traffic. Everybody smokes - you’re weird if you don’t. It’s a cash-only society, with minimum 6€ ATM withdrawal feels. But tourism has just begun to explode in this country, and spells good for it’s future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’d probably have passed right through the city, had I not a week with the dentists. The first two nights, I stayed in a remarkably shitty hostel. At 6€ a night, it seemed rather attractive at first. The atmosphere felt like that of an asylum. The man in my room would not stop talking to me. The people in the other room, they sat in their beds all day, poking at their phones. The kitchen consisted of a boiler plate, a crusty pot, dirty dishes strewn across the tiny bench. The sink was inside the single bathroom - shower, toilet, laundry, all in one giant room, serving a potential forty guests. It was not an atmosphere for productivity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The second place was different; an apartment with cheap bunk beds crammed into the two bedrooms. After settling in, the owner warned me about the crazy woman in my room. “Yeah,” I told him, “I know. I already talked to her for fifteen seconds.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As if I couldn’t fall any lower, the following night was spent in a jail cell… You can read about that absurdity &lt;strong&gt;link&lt;/strong&gt; here. And so, the next morning I resolved to stay somewhere nice. I save money so I can spend it when I need to. But at almost thrice the price, this place better be worth it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As I stepped into Milingona Hostel…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Photo: A picture is worth a thousand words.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tucked on a queit dusty side-street behind an inconspicuous green gate, in a city largely devoid of any natural beauty, this place was a hidden gem. Beside the walkway three guys lounged around a table, lazing in the hammock, and we exchanged smiles. I ducked beneath the overhanging branches, jostling limes with the top of my head. I walked up the stairs to the warmest welcome from Rozana and Joe. I’d booked just one night - but immediately extended to two.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Photo: The building opens up to view&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After a lovely chat I’m shown to my room - spacious, air conditioned, with a charming feel. I took a much-needed shower, then joined the other guests outside, and I entertained them enough to make Fraser miss his bus. It felt like the first genuine conversations I’d had since arriving in this city.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was immediately enchanted by this place, and I’d found it at a time I much needed some inspiration.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;part-2-inspiration&quot;&gt;Part 2: Inspiration&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I walked in as a guest for one night, but ended up volunteering there for three weeks.
I’d managed to find my own inspiration before Milingona, but it certainly helped fuel it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In my time there, I managed to progress a lot of things I’d recently been putting off. I finished building a website, tinkering enough to be happy for someone else to see it. 
I transcribed, edited and published a handful of my favourite stories I’d previously written, including those in German, then wrote the longest story I’ve ever written.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I completely rewrote my cover letter and resume for Engineering, and started firing off applications. I strongly suspect my German language skills are hurting my applications. When four applications came back declined, eight more I sent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At first, I extended one night, then another.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I fit in with the guests, and developed a fondness for some of the volunteers. After an inspiring discussion with Joe, I decided I’d be interested in volunteering there. I’d talk to them about it first thing in the morning.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That night I went to bed late. As I usually do, I had my bed made, all my stuff packed together neatly, with just a draping towel to identify my bed. I choose the top bunk always. As I reached up to the bed to set down my backpack, I felt an odd sensation. I touched again and recoiled, as he jumped stiff to attention. There’s a man in my bed! After brief confusion, I turn the lights on and check: that’s my bed, my towel is there. The rest of the beds are full.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That morning I spoke with Rozana, who I learned was the sister of Verona - the owner and manager, husband Yuli.&lt;/p&gt;


          </description>
          <pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
          <link>http://localhost:4000/Milingona-Hostel-Chapter-One.html</link>
          <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/Milingona-Hostel-Chapter-One.html</guid>
          
          
        </item>
      
    
      
        <item>
          
            <title>Template</title>
          
          <author>fakeemail@gmail.com (Kauri's BS)</author>
          <description>
            &lt;h5 id=&quot;date&quot;&gt;Date&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Body text goes here&lt;/p&gt;

          </description>
          <pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
          <link>http://localhost:4000/Template.html</link>
          <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/Template.html</guid>
          
          
        </item>
      
    
  </channel>
</rss>
